{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Redemption Song (Band Version) Very Rare", "Photograph", "End of Time", "LoveGame (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Anybody Seen My Baby", "Jamming", "Playboys of the Southwestern World", "The Ocean"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["If You Ain't Here to Party", "Pretty Maids All In A Row", "Is This Love", "I Want It All"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Knockout", "Believe in Me", "Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019", "This"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["My Oh My", "My Love (feat. T.I.)", "Killer Queen", "Iron Lion Zion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Ullathai Killathe", "Three Little Birds", "3", "Loca"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["California Girls (stereo)", "Exodus", "Swear It Again", "The More I Drink"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["One Drop", "Gorilla", "Doom And Gloom", "Sway"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Vaadi Vaadi", "Turn Your Lights Down Low", "I Could Have Lied", "Wanna Be Startin' Somethin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Live", "Hands All Over", "D.O.A. (Death of Auto-Tune)", "In Case"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Badan Pe Sitare (Prince)", "Irish Celebration", "Soul Rebel", "When It's All Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Beautiful People", "This Is Me", "True Love", "Redemption Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["S.O.S.", "My Love Is Your Love", "All I Want for Christmas", "Could You Be Loved"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Candle in the Wind 1997", "Yakeen", "Africa Unite", "Beautiful People"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Zion Train", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma", "Speedin'", "Freakshow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["400 Years", "Cherub Rock", "Tiny Dancer", "Ruffneck (Full Flex) (Munchi Anonymous Revolution remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Little Lady", "Waiting in Vain (remix 84)", "Stay (featuring Mikky Ekko)", "Colours"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Everything Is Not As It Seems", "Snitch", "Home", "Trenchtown Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["One Love / People Get Ready", "Round & Round", "I Need You Tonight", "For Whom the Bell Tolls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)", "Sun Is Shinning", "Can't Buy Me Love", "One And Only"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Like Toy Soldiers", "Cama De Rosas", "Brown Rang", "Coming in From the Cold"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Every Day", "I Shot the Sheriff", "Doin' Dirt", "Something in Your Mouth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Kaya", "When I Come Around (album version)", "Feels Like Today", "Hasta ma\u00f1ana"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Concrete Jungle", "SexyBack", "Dil Jhoom Jhoom", "Anytime"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Catch Me", "Purple Rain", "Superman", "Stir It Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Karma", "Easy Skanking", "I Love You O Sayyoni", "Ek Ajanabee Haseena Se"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Samjho Na", "One", "Punjabane", "Satisfy My Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Monster", "Buffalo Soldier", "Never Gone", "Human Nature"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Strangers in the Night", "So Much Trouble In The World", "To Live Is to Die", "Vaishnav Jan To Tene Kahiye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Title Song", "Don't Forget", "When Doves Cry", "Are We All We Are"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Lovin' It", "Jhoom Jhoom", "Revolution", "Breaking the Habit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Young Forever", "Moscas en la Casa", "Mann Ka Radio", "Ray of Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Aap Ki Khatir", "Nightingale", "One Moment In Time", "Try It on My Own"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Killer Queen", "Grenade", "You're My Baby", "Ai Meri Zohrajabeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Jesus Take the Wheel", "I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)", "Umrao Jaan", "Aap Ki Ankhon Mein"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Borderline", "I'm Still Standing", "Papers", "Allah Kare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Always on My Mind (alternate Take 2)", "When a Man Lies", "Maine to Khadi Chhat Ke Upar", "Naam Hai Tera"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Last Call", "Give It Up to Me", "\"How Deep Is Your Love (from \"\"Saturday Night Fever\"\")\"", "Love You Unconditionally"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Stan", "Aha Aha", "Teri Meri (Reprise)", "When a Man Lies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Stay (featuring Mikky Ekko)", "Damadamm", "The More I Drink", "Be Like You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["I Would", "Don't Go Breaking My Heart", "Oh Africa", "Ishq Ki Gali"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Wada Tainu", "Complicated", "It Had to Be You", "Touch Too Much"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["I Will Always Love You", "Billie Jean", "Chakna Chakna", "Coming in From the Cold"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Disturbia", "Satisfy You (feat. Puff Daddy)", "Jhalak Dikhlaja", "You Got It Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Tere Bina", "Main Jahaan Rahoon", "Trying Not to Love You", "Birthday Cake"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Mere Khwabon Mein (Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge)", "I Love You", "Superman", "Bye Bye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Kyun Chor Gaye Rastay", "Venice Queen", "Up", "Samjho Na"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["See You Again", "Moscas en la Casa", "Superstar", "Yaadan Teriyan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Rabba Ve Mera Yaar Modh De", "In Case", "Aap Ki Kashish (remix)", "Walk of Shame"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Losing My Way", "Only the Young", "Just to See You Smile", "Mujhko Yaad Sataye Teri"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["I Said Hey", "Mera Mann Kehne Laga (Reprise)", "Aashiq Banaya Aapne", "Confessions (interlude)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Brooklyn Go Hard", "Mehfooz", "Flash's Theme", "I Still"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["I've Been Everywhere", "Give It Away", "Greatest Love of All", "Sari Sari Raat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Viraaniya", "Cowboy Boots", "Michelle", "A Kind of Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Elton John", "Back To You", "It Will Rain", "I Love You O Sayyoni"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Ahista Ahista", "Sweet Caroline (Glee Cast version)", "Payphone", "Tunnel Vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Lonely", "She", "Don't Make Me", "I Don't Care Anymore"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Tera Surroor", "Quiz\u00e1s", "Give Me Love (True Tiger Remix)", "A Thousand Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Himesh Reshammiya?", "answers": ["Troublemaker", "Aaja Ve", "Someone Like You", "Dani California"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Aye Mere Watan Ke Logon", "What I've Done", "I'll Stand by You (Glee Cast version)", "Uska Hi Banana"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Papercut (remix)", "Duaa", "Return to Sender", "Hum Kis Gaali Ja (Dance Mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Jaan", "Jhoom Jhoom Ta Hun Main (Film Version)", "I'd Come For You", "Love Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Pal Pal Dil Ke Pas", "For the Love of a Daughter", "Saawali Si Raat", "Inevitable"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Never Say Never", "Raabta (Kehte Hain Khuda Ne)", "LoveGame (album version)", "Save The Last Dance For Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Tu Jaane Na", "You And I", "I Was Here", "Phir Le Aya Dil (Reprise)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Aap Ki Khatir", "Doorie", "Hometown Glory", "Dilli Wali Girlfriend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Raabta", "The Jack", "Heartbreak Hotel", "Just Want You to Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["You Don't Know", "Sweetest Goodbye", "Me and My Gang", "Raabta (Night In Motel)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["If I Can Dream", "Khalbali", "Love So Right", "I Kissed a Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["You Save Me", "Grade 8", "Raabta (Siyaah Raatein)", "The Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Black or White (album version)", "Phir Mohabbat", "Lonely", "Two Worlds (finale)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["If I Were a Boy", "Bandz a Maker Her Dance", "Wendy", "Kabira (Encore)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arijit Singh?", "answers": ["Gummy Bear Instrumental", "Ilahi", "Tequila Sunrise", "Let's Get Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Aaj Mausam Bada Beimann Hai (Today the Weather Plays Tricks on Me)", "Maine Payal Hai Chhankai", "Higher Ground", "Everything Back But You (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Escapar (Escape)", "Fuel", "Dil Jhoom Jhoom", "Angie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Helter Skelter", "Ankh Ladake", "No Worries", "Marry You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Maine to Khadi Chhat Ke Upar", "Everything I Can't Have", "2012", "Don't Take Your Guns To Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Sure Be Cool If You Did", "Mar Jani Jhanjar", "Hollywood Tonight", "Islands in the Stream"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Aha Aha", "Spotlight", "Higher Ground", "Finally Found You (Papercha$er's Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Pal Pal Teri Yaad", "All My Love", "Could You Be Loved", "We Will Rock You (Digital Remastered)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Gimme More", "Sajna Tu Mat Jai Re", "Slipping Through My Fingers - Me and I", "The Saints Are Coming"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Get Up Jawani (feat. Shah)", "Mane Chudi Piravan Lagyo", "Like You'll Never See Me Again", "One"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falguni Pathak?", "answers": ["Ek Pagla Meri Gali Ka", "Last Night on Earth", "Christmas Tree", "Come Fly With Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Nobody But Me", "Lonely", "My Best Friend", "Birthday Cake"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Everything Back But You (live)", "Give It 2 Me", "Highway Don't Care", "Who's That Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Just to See You Smile", "My Friends", "Too Damn Young", "No Worries"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Waiting on the World to Change", "Something Like That", "The Everlasting Now", "Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Temporary Home", "Don\u2019t Let Me Down", "Back When", "One Moment In Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Thrift Shop", "She's My Kind of Rain", "1+1", "Skin (Sarabeth)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["It's Your Love", "Koi Hota Jisko Apna", "Phir Le Aya Dil (Reprise)", "Yellow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Live Like You Were Dying", "Complicated (Tom Lord-Alge mix)", "I Wanna Grow Old With You", "Paradise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Last Dollar (Fly Away)", "You Had Me From Hello", "Do You Remember", "Bohemian Rhapsody"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["I Told You So", "Mama Africa", "Bakhuda Tumhi Ho", "Like We Never Loved at All"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Open Arms", "Jesus Take the Wheel", "Whenever You Remember", "Truck Yeah"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["She Loves You", "Where the Green Grass Grows", "I Can't Quit You Baby", "Fancy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["My Next Thirty Years", "Am a Gummy Bear (The Gummy Bear Song)", "Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele", "Barbara Ann"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["My Old Friend", "Somewhere I Belong", "Obsessed", "Deuces"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Southern Girl", "A Thousand Years", "Ain't No Grave", "Michelle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["The Cowboy in Me", "Who's Crying Now", "Just the Way You Are (Glee Cast version)", "You'll Never Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Jhoom Jhoom Ta Hun Main (Film Version)", "Back to Your Heart", "Me and You", "Felt Good on My Lips"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Take My Drunk Ass Home", "Southern Voice", "Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)", "Stand Inside Your Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Please Remember Me", "O Sahiba O Sahiba", "First of the Year", "American Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Like I Love You", "You and Tequila", "Bring On the Rain", "We Made You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Waka Waka (Esto es \u00c1frica) (K-mix)", "Un-Thinkable (I'm Ready)", "Ten Times Crazier", "Real Good Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Jag Jeondeyan de Mele", "Ennoda Laila", "Tu Jaane Na", "Red Ragtop"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Abhi Na Jaao Chhod Kar", "Don't Take the Girl", "Lo Hecho Est\u00e1 Hecho", "Kisi Roz Milo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Over", "Cover Girl", "I Would", "Let's Make Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["So Much Trouble In The World", "I Just Wanna Love U (Give It to Me)", "You Don't Know My Name", "Better Than I Used to Be"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Guide: Gaata Rahe Mera Dil", "Stop & Erase", "Inconsolable", "Indian Outlaw"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["One of Those Nights", "When I Close My Eyes", "We Own the Night", "Emotions"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Don't Stop 'Til You Get Enough (album version)", "Aap Ki Kashish (remix)", "Can't Be Tamed", "If You're Reading This"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Close Your Eyes", "My Little Girl (From the Motion Picture 'Flicka')", "Catch a Grenade (The Hooligans remix)", "Another Round (explicit version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Give in to Me", "Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "Angry All the Time", "Billionaire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Tim McGraw?", "answers": ["Yellow Submarine", "Highway To Hell", "When the Stars Go Blue", "They Don't Care About Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["X.Y.U.", "Fucking Die 2 (\u20ac\u20ac Cooper mix)", "Street Fightin' Man", "City of Hope"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Wild for the Night", "Help!", "A Kind of Magic", "Me and My Gang"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Summit", "Give in to Me", "Cheek to Cheek", "You Can't Always Get What You Want"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Ahista Ahista", "Losing My Way", "Viraaniya", "Rock n\u2019 Roll (Will Take You to the Mountain)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Kabira (Encore)", "Lemme See", "Syndicate (Skrillex remix)", "Love in This Club"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Daddy's Little Girl", "Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites (Zedd remix)", "That's More Like It", "Dil Jhoom Jhoom"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Ruffneck (Full Flex) (Munchi Anonymous Revolution remix)", "Como Yo Nadie Te Ha Amado", "3", "Help!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Scary Bolly Dub", "The Most Beautiful Girl in the World", "Hero", "Body Count"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["The One That Got Away", "This Ain't a Love Song", "Drive My Car", "Dreamin' (Bare Noize Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["I'm Movin' On", "Smell This Money (original mix)", "Soledad", "What It Takes to Win"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Sorry Seems To Be The Hardest Word", "First of the Year", "Love on Top", "Rote Hue Aate Hain Sab"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Numb", "WEEKENDS!!!", "Americano", "Honey Bee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Sk8er Boi", "No Such Thing", "Breakn' a Sweat", "Material Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Je Veux Savoir", "Show Me", "Come", "Lick It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele", "It's All Up to You", "Right In", "The Four Horsemen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["You Know It's Christmas", "Southern Girl", "Sussudio", "Reptile\u2019s Theme"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Honey Bee", "Under My Thumb", "All I Ask of You", "Anything But Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Count on Me", "The Devil\u2019s Den", "There's a Place for Us", "Sway"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Bicycle Race", "Bug Hunt (Noisia remix)", "Omnipresence", "St. Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Famous", "I Go Back", "The Most Beautiful Girl in the World", "Make It Bun Dem (Electro Body trance remix by Sthilmann)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Complicated", "Nothing Even Matters", "Ride Home", "Like Toy Soldiers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Kyoto", "They Don't Care About Us", "Last Night on Earth", "Take Me With U"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Kill EVERYBODY", "Free", "No More Sorrow", "We Weren't Born to Follow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Bangarang", "I Won't Let Go", "I Would", "Is This the World We Created...?"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Mermaid", "Sparks Fly", "My Name Is Skrillex", "Fight Fire With Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["The Way You Look Tonight:", "Warrior", "Easy Lover (duet with Phill Collins)", "Still Getting It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Free", "One Love / People Get Ready", "Voulez-vous", "Leaving"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Doorie", "Needed Change", "When You Believe (From the Prince of Egypt)", "Dressin\u2019 Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["After All These Years", "The Reason", "Across the Universe", "Enchanted"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Skrillex?", "answers": ["Kiss Kiss", "Another Round (explicit version)", "Right on Time", "First of May"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Slut Like You", "What Hurts the Most", "A Milli", "I Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Melt My Heart to Stone", "Outlaw", "East Jesus Nowhere", "All the Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Easy Lover (duet with Phill Collins)", "First of May", "Fireman", "Never Learn Not to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Makes Me Wonder", "Faded", "Dear Mr. President (From I'm Not Dead Live - Wembley Arena)", "Escapar (Escape)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The A Team", "My Life", "Just a Dream", "Jaoon Kahan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["John", "Never Gonna Be Alone", "Americano", "Back When"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["I Wanna Be Your Lover", "Lonely", "I Love the Lord", "Welcome to My Hood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Somewhere in Brooklyn", "Sometimes (radio edit)", "6 Foot 7 Foot", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Dance for You", "If We Were a Movie", "Straight Through My Heart", "She Will"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The Motto", "Kiss You", "Raise Your Glass", "Don't Wake Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Jab Jab Phool Khile: Pardesiyon Se Na Ankhiyan Milana", "Right Above It", "Intro", "Burn It to the Ground"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Can't Buy Me Love", "Now and Then", "Back That Azz Up", "The Way I Loved You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Tommie Sunshine\u2019s Megasix Smash-Up", "The Reason", "From the Bottom of My Broken Heart", "Drop the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Sometimes It Snows in April", "No New Friends (SFTB Remix)", "Boyfriend", "You Really Got Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Pour It Up", "Lollipop", "Ek Pagla Meri Gali Ka", "Chup Kar Ke"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Stairway to Heaven", "Just Want You to Know", "Forever", "Do it Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Follow You Home", "Take It to the Head", "Disappear", "I Guess That's Why They Call It the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Gunwalk (Feat. Gudda Gudda)", "No Love", "Summerboy", "I Will Always Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Eh Eh (Nothing Else I Can Say)", "Superstar", "4 Minutes", "Strange Clouds"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Baby One More Time", "Va Va Voom", "I Can Transform Ya", "Get to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Yara Seeli Seeli", "Too Much Love Will Kill You", "No Worries", "Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Schoolin' Life", "American Trilogy", "Have a Drink on Me", "I Can Only Imagine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["That's More Like It", "Why Don't You Love Me (MK Ultra club)", "A Dedication", "Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["God Bless Amerika", "Happy People", "Is This the World We Created...?", "Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "Bitches Love Me", "Sing for the Moment", "Take It Easy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Make It Rain", "Amplifier", "If Today Was Your Last Day", "Party in the U.S.A."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Firefly", "When I Come Around (album version)", "I Knew You Were Trouble", "Rich As Fuck (Feat. 2 Chainz)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Shakin' It 4 Daddy (feat. Nicki Minaj)", "Queen of the Night", "Pop That", "Give a Little More"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Hey Jude", "Ojos As\u00ed", "Should\u2019ve Kissed You", "Give It Up to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Confessions (interlude)", "Got Money", "Soul Survivor", "The Power of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Stupid Hoe", "Rabba", "Mirror", "Turn Me On"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Dressin\u2019 Up", "Teeth", "Promise", "Bandz a Maker Her Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Les Mis\u00e9rables: Stars", "You Are", "Into the Groove", "Let's Get Away From It All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Russian Roulette", "Do You Hear What I Hear", "What the Hell", "The Last Night of the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Chaudhvin Ka Chand Ho", "No Church in the Wild", "The American Dream", "Yara Seeli Seeli"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Our Song", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Bring Him Home", "Green", "Dreamin' (Bare Noize Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["S'il suffisait d'aimer", "Suite from Miss Saigon", "Muqaddar Ka Sikandar: O Saathi Re", "Bicycle Race"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Drops of Jupiter", "Jab Jab Phool Khile: Pardesiyon Se Na Ankhiyan Milana", "The Way", "Thuy's Death / You Will Not Touch Him"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Stars", "City Is Ours", "Whole Lotta Love", "Kootthu Onnu"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Don't", "Home", "The Best Damn Thing", "Black Ice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["The Way I Loved You", "Raabta", "What Have I Done?", "Wherever I May Roam"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["First Love", "The Movie in My Mind", "Bad Romance", "Back in Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Heart Attack", "Figure.09", "Empty Chairs at Empty Tables", "Piya (remixed by DJ Suketu)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Back to December (acoustic)", "Under The Bridge", "Across the Universe", "Who Am I?"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Lucky (Glee Cast version)", "Google Google", "Titanic", "Why God Why?"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Javert's Suicide", "Moment 4 Life (feat. Drake)", "All I Have to Give", "Can You Hear Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Best Thing I Never Had", "Confrontation", "Paint It Black", "Hello"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Fantine's Death", "Monster", "Till the World Ends", "For Whom the Bell Tolls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Martin Guerre", "Mermaid", "Cry Me a River", "Heartbreak Warfare"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Total Eclipse of the Heart", "Immortality", "Les Mis\u00e9rables", "When All Is Said and Done"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["The Scientist", "Home Sweet Home", "Le Premier Pas", "Part Of Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Now That I've Seen Her", "Hush Little Baby", "Brown Sugar", "This Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Free", "Don't Worry Baby", "Aadat (Deep Blue version)", "I'd Give My Life for You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Ponmeri", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma", "Robot", "A Little Fall of Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Run To Me", "Journey of the Sorcerer", "On My Own", "A Boy Named Sue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Claude-Michel Sch\u00f6nberg?", "answers": ["Bruises", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "The Ocean", "Written in the Stars"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Hole in My Head", "Vole", "Take It From Here", "Call Me Maybe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Not Even the King", "Fly Me to the Moon", "American Trilogy", "Smooth Criminal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Longview", "Twist and Shout", "Without You", "Rani Tu Mein Raja"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["If You're Reading This", "Cold Coffee", "Young", "Lucky (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Sing", "The Age of Worry", "Raabta (Night In Motel)", "Under My Thumb"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["My Prerogative", "Speedin'", "Raabta (Kehte Hain Khuda Ne)", "Marry You (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Defying Gravity", "Wasted Time", "Mera Mann Kehne Laga (Reprise)", "The Celestials"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["U.N.I.", "We Are Young", "Over", "Jingle Bells"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Starships", "Uska Hi Banana", "Inhale Deep", "Saturday Night's Alright (for Fighting)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Orange Blossom Special", "Coming in From the Cold", "Just the Way You Are (Glee Cast version)", "Something in Your Mouth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["To Be Loved", "Give Your Heart a Break", "Someday", "Music Sounds Better With U"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Fly on the Wall", "I'll Always Remember You", "Let Me Love You", "Breakn' a Sweat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["New Kid in Town", "Glad You Came", "Heartbreaker", "Chhod De Sari Duniya"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["It's Time", "Blue", "Ring Of Fire", "Holly Jolly Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Truck", "Bloody Mary", "Nagada Nagada", "I'll Stand by You (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Beer in Mexico", "Colours", "Don't Stop Believin' (Glee Cast version)", "Mood Kharaab"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Hoedown Throwdown", "Dressin\u2019 Up", "Doomsday Clock", "True Colors"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Pehli Nazar Mein", "For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "Hate That I Love You", "Don't Rain on My Parade"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Folsom Prison Blues (mono)", "Lovin' It", "Lean on Me (Glee Cast version)", "Fix You (edit)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Les Mis\u00e9rables", "Guide: Gaata Rahe Mera Dil", "Sweet Caroline (Glee Cast version)", "The Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Catch Me", "Stir It Up", "Get It Right", "Do Somethin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Run the World (Girls)", "Felt Good on My Lips", "Faithfully", "Miss You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Radio (Sir Spyro remix)", "Kiss", "Us Against the World", "Someday When I Stop Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Who's Lovin' You", "Cough Syrup", "Bubble Butt", "Crazy for You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Bush Song", "D\u2019yer Mak\u2019er", "Total Eclipse of the Heart", "Big Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Longview", "Be Good to Yourself", "A Thousand Years", "Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Celebration Day", "When Doves Cry", "Follow You Home", "The Scientist"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Raise Your Glass", "Cleaning Out My Closet", "Somebody to Love", "When You're Looking Like That"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Bodies", "Mehndi Laga Ke Rakhna", "Birthday", "Teenage Dream (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Glee Cast?", "answers": ["Imagine", "Come Together", "Ahista Ahista", "Hold On"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Starstruck", "Round & Round", "Charkha", "Mere Mehboob Qayamat Hogi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Just Dance", "Knockin' on Heaven's Door", "Girl From the North Country (feat. Bob Dylan)", "Escapar (Escape)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Old & Crazy", "Schei\u00dfe (DJ White Shadow Mugler)", "New Day", "Jumpin' Jack Flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Piya O Re Piya", "Buffalo Soldier", "Jaan", "Paparazzi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Girlfriend", "Hum Kis Gaali Ja (Dance Mix)", "Big Night", "Bloody Mary"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["My Way", "Wada Na Tod", "I Want It That Way (single version)", "Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Massive Attack", "Miss You", "Speechless", "Ishq Ki Gali"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Bullet With Butterfly Wings", "Dance in the Dark", "Hotel California", "Talking To The Moon (Acoustic)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Seasons in the Sun", "No Leaf Clover", "Government Hooker", "I Was Born to Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Shattered", "Boys Boys Boys", "Tera Surroor", "Summer Wind (feat. Julio Iglesias)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Stone in Love", "Perfect", "Feels Good at First", "Alejandro"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Summerboy", "Please Come Home for Christmas", "Right Thru Me", "Beam Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Cough Syrup", "The Edge of Glory", "Superstar", "Complicated"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["I Have Nothing", "Someday I'll Be Saturday Night", "Superstar", "Heavy Metal Lover"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["When You Believe (From the Prince of Egypt)", "LoveGame (album version)", "Qott Ghusian Da", "Won't Go Home Without You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Ye Ishq Hai", "We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together", "Broken-Hearted Girl", "Yo\u00fc and I"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Fool That I Am", "Music Sounds Better With U", "Fa La La", "Christmas Tree"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Be Like You", "Wheel in the Sky", "Chillin", "See You Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Rubberneckin'", "Poker Face", "Time of Our Life", "Don't Wake Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["More Than That", "The Fame", "Drive My Car", "Lego House"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Good Vibrations", "The Scientist", "Superman", "Hair"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["No Church in the Wild", "Telephone", "Starships", "High Hopes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Ronan", "Bad Kids", "Anybody Seen My Baby", "You Shook Me All Night Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Melt My Heart to Stone", "Hurt", "Bad Girl", "Teeth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Locked Out of Heaven", "Touch Too Much", "Mere naseeb mein ae dost", "Bad Romance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Born This Way", "Doolin-Dalton", "Sambhle (feat. Manak Ali)", "God Bless Amerika"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Americano", "Irresistible", "Allah Hoo", "Be True to Your School"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Fashion", "Jailhouse Rock", "LoveStoned/I Think She Knows (interlude)", "Radio GaGa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["One Drop", "Moondance", "Eh Eh (Nothing Else I Can Say)", "Straight Through My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["So Happy I Could Die", "Next to You", "Beast of Burden", "Moon River"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["I've Been Everywhere", "Yellow Submarine", "Celebration Day", "Electric Feel"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Hot 'n' Cold", "Sweetest Goodbye", "21 Guns", "My Name Is"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Part Of Me", "Almost Is Never Enough", "Get It Right", "We've Got It Goin' On"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Mirror", "Lovin' It", "Love After War", "Who Am I Living For?"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019", "\"Rascacielo (\"\"Skyscraper\"\" Spanish Version)\"", "Firework", "Chori Chori"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["I Like It", "Be Alright", "Home", "Wide Awake"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Fast Cars and Freedom", "Last Call", "Love So Right", "First of the Year"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["My Eyes (feat. Gwen Sebastian)", "Teenage Dream", "Bad Romance", "The Jack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Simple", "Dil aisa kisi ne mera toda", "All About Lovin' You", "Islands in the Stream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Faith Won't Fall", "Satisfy You (feat. Puff Daddy)", "Out of My Mind", "Mahi Ve"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["E.T.", "When a Man Lies", "Love Takes Time", "Misery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Mera Dil Bhi Kitna Pagal Hai", "Right In", "The One That Got Away", "Raabta (Siyaah Raatein)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Use Your Love", "Numb", "Paris", "Wing$"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["I'm Still Breathing", "Battery", "Let's Do This", "Live to Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["If You Can Afford Me", "New Power Generation", "Quiz\u00e1s", "Is Kadar Pyar Hai Tumse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["California Gurls", "Mera Mann Kehne Laga (Reprise)", "Just to See You Smile", "Patteya Geya"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Not Like the Movies", "Get Over It", "Redemption Song (Band Version) Very Rare", "Vaanaviley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Ur So Gay", "Je l'aime \u00e0 Mourir", "Breakfast Can Wait", "Doomsday Clock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Maine Payal Hai Chhankai", "Ek Ladki Ko Dekha", "Count on You (feat. Jordin Sparks)", "Fingerprints"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Tere Mast Mast Do Nain", "Lost", "All-American Girl", "I Got U"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Waking Up In Vegas", "Try It on My Own", "In Case", "Moby Dick"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Lonely", "Criminal", "Hummingbird Heartbeat", "You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Hey Hey What Can I Do", "I Want to Break Free", "Single Ladies (Put a Ring on It)", "If We Ever Meet Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Radio GaGa", "Check It Out", "Dressin\u2019 Up", "Imagine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Never Gone", "Thinking of You", "Never Let You Go", "Gummi From Bom Bom Bay"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["The Beginning Is the End Is the Beginning", "Clarity", "Raabta (Siyaah Raatein)", "Mannequin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Mere Mitwa Mere Meet Re", "You're My Baby", "I Kissed a Girl", "Letting Go (Dutty Love)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Maula", "Major Minus", "You Should Be Dancing", "Tommie Sunshine\u2019s Megasix Smash-Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Niggas in Paris", "Circle the Drain", "The Truth About Love", "It's Your Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Beam Me Up", "There Goes My Baby", "A Little Less Conversation (JXL radio edit remix)", "Pearl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["One of the Boys", "Pretty Lil Heart (feat. Lil Wayne)", "Easy", "Pretty Lil Heart (feat. Lil Wayne)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Desensitized", "Dil To Bachcha Hai", "1999 (LP version)", "Last Friday Night (T.G.I.F.)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Yeh Zindagi Usi Ki Hai", "Calling All Angels", "Gimme That", "Vaadi Vaadi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Smile", "Wasted Time", "My Wish", "Aye Mere Watan Ke Logon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Tera Mera Pyar Amar", "Sexy Ladies/Let Me Talk to You (prelude)", "Keep Holding On", "Someday When I Stop Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Lag Ja Gale Se Phir", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "Clocks", "Lady Lynda"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Parallel Universe", "Bindiya Chamkegi (Do Raaste)", "Who Made Who", "Love You Inside Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Man Dole Mera Tan Dole", "Woh Lamhe", "Gal Sun Ja", "Red Camaro"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Flash", "Started from the Bottom", "Vaishnav Jan To Tene Kahiye", "Ride Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Chelsea Rodgers", "I Melt", "Mehndi Laga Ke Rakhna", "Pretty Lil Heart (feat. Lil Wayne)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Tumbling Dice", "Love the Way You Lie", "Lag Ja Gale", "Tired"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Tujhe Dekha To", "Heaven for Everyone", "When It's Time", "Hung Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Nobody Knows", "Chhod De Sari Duniya", "Waiting on a Friend", "Lay Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Live to Tell", "What Hurts the Most", "My Love", "Yara Seeli Seeli"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Sorry", "Starstruck", "So Much Trouble In The World", "Satyam Shivam Sundaram"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Sweet Dreams", "Castle", "Mere Khwabon Mein (Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge)", "Goodbye's (The Saddest Word)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Pyar Kiya to Darna Kya", "My Love (feat. T.I.)", "Osito Gummy Bear (Mexican)", "These Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)", "It Will Rain", "A Woman's Worth", "Spaceship Coupe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["La Tortura (alternate Spanglish version)", "Tere Husn Ki Kya", "Are You Lonesome Tonight", "Nights on Broadway"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Aye-Dil-E-Nadan", "My Way", "Ramble On", "Don't Stop Believin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Inhale Deep", "Kahin Deep Jale Kahin Dil", "Chandaniya (Lori Lori)", "The Most Beautiful Girl in the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["We've Got It Goin' On", "Who Says You Can't Go Home", "Yeh Dil Aur Unki Nigahon Ke Saaye", "Rock With You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["We Belong Together", "Aise Na Mujhe Tum Dekho", "Kiss", "Aaj Jagraata Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Winner at a Losing Game", "Pairon Mein Bandhan Hai", "Make U Love Me", "The Thing About Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Ram Teri Ganga Maili: Sun Sahiba Sun", "Listen", "No One Else Comes Close", "Jive Talkin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Music", "Dil To Hai Dil", "Journey of the Sorcerer", "Warrior"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Somewhere I Belong", "The Saints Are Coming", "Man in the Mirror", "Wada Na Tod"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Lata Mangeshkar?", "answers": ["Mere Naseeb Mein (Naseeb)", "As I Am (intro)", "On My Own", "Drop the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["When I Need You", "Ghost of You", "Trading Places", "Halo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["The Name of the Game", "Papercut (remix)", "Moscas en la Casa", "End of Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["She's My Kind of Rain", "Around The World", "Victim of Love", "Get Me Bodied"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Ishq Ki Gali", "Taarif Karun Kya Uski (From Kashmir Ki Kali)", "Gravity", "Broken-Hearted Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["I Was Here", "\"Almost Home (Music from the Motion Picture \"\"Oz the Great and Powerful\"\")\"", "Where Have You Been", "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["At Last", "Phoolan Ka Taron Ka", "Allah Kare", "Chup Kar Ke - Remix"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Head Banger (feat. Escape)", "Listen", "Breakn' a Sweat", "After All These Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Til Kingdom Come", "Never Say Goodbye", "Schoolin' Life", "Wasted"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["When You're Looking Like That", "Video Phone", "What About Now", "Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Ave Maria", "Cruella De Vil", "Hello", "Burning Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["All at Once", "Countdown", "Today Was a Fairytale", "Phir Mohabbat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Pirate Flag", "Party (feat. Andr\u00e9 3000)", "Red Ragtop", "A Place for My Head"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Southern Girl", "If I Were a Boy", "Good in Goodbye", "Garaari (feat. Meet Malkit)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "Start Me Up", "What Now", "Diva"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Hello", "Ready", "New York Mining Disaster 1941", "High School (feat. Lil Wayne)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Kill the DJ", "Pehli Nazar Mein", "You Should Be Dancing", "Why Don't You Love Me (MK Ultra club)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["How You Remind Me", "Cabron", "In Repair", "1+1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Right on Time", "Hold My Hand", "Irreplaceable (album version)", "Falling Into You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Cocaine Blues", "Going to California", "Naughty Girl", "Thank You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["The Ocean", "Run the World (Girls)", "Who Owns My Heart", "Stuck in the Moment"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Like We Never Loved at All", "Lighters", "The Rose", "Best Thing I Never Had"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Zion Train", "Lemme See", "Sweet Dreams", "First Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Born to Make You Happy", "Saibo", "Love on Top", "Major Minus"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["My Boo", "Blown Away", "I'd Rather Go Blind", "Heartbreaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Runaway", "Sing for the Moment", "Young Forever", "Gotham City"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Single Ladies (Put a Ring on It)", "Over", "Muzzle", "Piya O Re Piya (Sad)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Ego", "When I Come Around (album version)", "Are We All We Are", "We Can Work It Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Hold On", "Upgrade U", "Gotta Be Somebody", "Heavy Metal Lover"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Beautiful Liar (Freemasons remix)", "Come Fly With Me", "Peli Waar", "Osito Gummy Bear (Mexican)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Live to Tell", "Back Where I Come From", "Mood Kharaab", "Dance for You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Lovin' It", "Do Pal Ka (Veer Zara)", "I Miss You", "Gunwalk (Feat. Gudda Gudda)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Gasoline", "Song Cry", "Jesus Loves Me", "1999 (LP version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Begin Again", "Beer in Mexico", "Heavy Metal Lover", "That\u2019s My Bitch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Better Than I Used to Be", "Public Service Announcement (interlude)", "Together", "If I Can Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Quit Playin' Games", "Larger Than Life", "Stay (featuring Mikky Ekko)", "Heart of the City (Ain't No Love)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Rude Boy", "Charkha", "Otis", "New Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Whataya Want From Me", "Jag Jeondeyan de Mele", "Monster", "Nights on Broadway"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Run This Town", "Uska Hi Banana", "Girl Can't Help It", "Papercut (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Young Forever", "Trouble", "Welcome to the Farm", "Zindagi Ye"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["I Don't Care Anymore", "Izzo (H.O.V.A.)", "Tere Bina", "Tere Bina (Indian)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["I Just Wanna Love U (Give It to Me)", "Controversy", "If Everyone Cared", "I Can\u2019t Tell You Why"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["No Church in the Wild", "Poetic Justice", "Anytime", "Martin Guerre"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Tujhe Dekha To", "You Are Not Alone", "D'Evils", "Brown Sugar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["I Know You Know (feat. Cymphonique)", "Lost One", "I Didn't Know My Own Strength", "Baby I"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Pyar Kiya to Darna Kya", "Journey of the Sorcerer", "On to the Next One", "Hurt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Encore", "Primordial Music", "In the End", "To Love Somebody"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Sometimes (radio edit)", "Wait Til You See My Smile", "Show Me What You Got", "Fade to Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Big Pimpin'", "Who Says", "The Day That Never Comes", "Tujhe Dekha To"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Crazy for You", "Half of My Heart", "99 Problems", "Chup Kar Ke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Big Gun", "Magic", "D.O.A. (Death of Auto-Tune)", "She's a Rainbow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Faded", "I Miss You", "I Love You", "Paris"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Drop the World", "The Rain Song", "Renegade", "Umrao Jaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)", "Dirt Off Your Shoulder", "Step by Step", "The Perfect Fan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Lovin' Touchin' Squeezin'", "Marry You", "Mine", "Niggas in Paris"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Baby I\u2019m a Star", "Remember When", "Roc Boys (And the Winner Is)...", "Coca Cola Braunu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Politik", "Beam Me Up", "Confessions (interlude)", "The Ruler's Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["I'm Every Woman", "The Day That Never Comes", "Moment of Clarity", "Up All Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Hard Knock Life (Ghetto Anthem)", "When I'm Gone", "Rock Star", "Take You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Emotions", "Me and My Gang", "My Friends", "Brooklyn Go Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["A Hard Day\u2019s Night", "Pour It Up", "Chanda Ki Doli Mai (Chanda Ki Doli)", "Off That"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Can I Get A...", "Iridescent", "Norwegian Wood", "Uptown Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["100$ Bill", "Right Above It", "Like I Love You", "Yeh Zindagi Usi Ki Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Funhouse", "Empire State of Mind", "Under The Bridge", "Kaya"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Ponmeri", "When I Come Around (album version)", "Changed", "Goodbye Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["I'd Rather Go Blind", "Bangarang", "Thaazhampoo", "Never Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Primordial Music", "When the Sun Goes Down", "Pyar Kiya to Darna Kya", "Koi Hota Jisko Apna"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Achha Lagta Hai", "Nari Kathai", "What Goes Around.../...Comes Around (interlude)", "I'm Not a Girl Not Yet a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Get Off My Cloud", "Whataya Want From Me", "Far Away", "Adada Vaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Baby I", "Shapath", "Pure Imagination", "If It Hadn't Been for Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Farewell and Goodnight", "Quiz\u00e1s", "Dirty Dancer", "Thanimayil"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Vaanaviley", "Don't Forget", "Yakeen", "Cheers (Drink to That)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["D'amour ou d'amiti\u00e9", "Halfway There", "Kaatu Vazhi", "Can U Believe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Omnipresence", "Take It to the Limit", "Up All Night", "Love Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Schoolin' Life", "Gypsy", "My Boo", "Oru Vaandu Koottame"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["The American Dream", "Be Good to Yourself", "Likhe Jo Khat Tujhe", "Paradise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Tere Mast Mast Do Nain", "Prem Bann", "Of a Lifetime", "This Is Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Don't Blink", "Tunnel Vision", "Blue", "Curse of Indra"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Breaking the Habit", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma", "Long Distance", "Escape"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Broken-Hearted Girl", "Oorukkoru", "I Wish", "Blackened"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Whoa Oh!", "The Way I Loved You", "Don't Make Me", "Sacrement"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["All I Want for Christmas", "Gundello Godari", "Old & Crazy", "What Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Isaiyarasi (feat. S. Rajeswari & S. Janaki)", "Heavy", "Temporary Home", "Escape"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Unakkum Enakkum", "Million Dolla Baby", "Rock With You", "Burn It Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Amplifier", "Kootthu Onnu", "Figure.09", "Fashion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Thalaattu Ketka Nanum", "Tony Montana", "Down Low (Noboby Has to Know)", "I Have a Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ilaiyaraaja?", "answers": ["Amma Endralle", "Can U Help Me", "Otherside", "Eye"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["A Wake", "Together", "Dear John", "The Adventures of Rain Dance Maggie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Mood Kharaab", "Picture to Burn", "Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "Talking To The Moon (Acoustic)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["When I Get You Alone", "I'm Gonna Live Till I Die", "Incomplete", "Our Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["I'll Just Hold On", "Stay Stay Stay", "Massachusetts", "Intuition (feat. Eric Bellinger)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Fearless", "Purple Rain", "Wasted", "Heavy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["You Remind Me of Something", "Mockingbird", "Begin Again", "Farewell and Goodnight"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Highway Don't Care", "Summertime", "You Belong With Me", "Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Likhe Jo Khat Tujhe", "Until It Sleeps", "Long Live", "Feeling Good"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Intro", "Pyar Aaya", "Surfin' Safari", "Red"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together", "We Are Young", "Bleed It Out", "Nobody Knows"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["When All Is Said and Done", "Amplifier", "I Love You", "Teardrops on My Guitar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Baby I", "I Believe in You and Me", "Slipped Away", "Fifteen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)", "White Horse", "Aanewala Pal Janewala Hai", "Mama's Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["What Now", "Why God Why?", "What About Now", "Half of My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Rock and Roll", "Eyes Open", "Jumpin' Jack Flash", "Back That Azz Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Boulevard of Broken Dreams", "Road Trippin'", "Everything Has Changed (feat. Ed Sheeran)", "Little Honda"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "Sparks Fly", "Saathiya", "Oorukkoru"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Today Was a Fairytale", "Summer Love", "Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Sathiyon", "It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Speak Now", "Knockin' on Heaven's Door", "Zindagi", "Banjo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Both of Us", "Jackson", "Mississippi", "A Woman's Worth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Jal Pari", "Up", "Haunted", "Time Is on My Side"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Reptile\u2019s Theme", "Miraksam", "Ennoda Laila", "Love Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Feeling Good", "Brand New Me", "Big Balls", "You're Not Sorry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Paint It Black", "Dilli Wali Girlfriend", "I Knew You Were Trouble", "The Perfect Fan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["22", "Run This Town", "Ben", "Give Me Love (True Tiger Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["All About Lovin' You", "Leader of Men (acoustic)", "Enchanted", "A Milli"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Every Day", "Ours", "Crash My Party", "Yakeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Lag Ja Gale Se Phir", "Too Bad (Diggla mix)", "Ronan", "Jhoom Jhoom Ta Hun Main (Film Version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Forget Forever", "A Kind of Magic", "No", "Mean"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Back to December (acoustic)", "I'll See You Again", "Sweet and Simple", "Strawberry Bubblegum"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Phoolan Ka Taron Ka", "Kyun Chor Gaye Rastay", "Mine", "Maine Puchha Chand Se (Abdullah)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Bangarang", "Smell This Money (original mix)", "Suit & Tie", "All Too Well"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Ask the Lonely", "Why Not Me?", "Vipassana", "Zindagi Ka Safar Hai Yeh Kaisa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Break The Ice", "I Love You", "Escape", "Seasons in the Sun"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Put Your Hearts Up", "Marry Me", "After All These Years", "Tailgate Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["It's Not Right but It's Okay", "Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain", "Girl Can't Help It", "I Like It"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Stop This Train", "City of Hope", "Disappear", "Until It Sleeps"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["I Want You (She's So Heavy)", "Sous le vent (feat. Garou)", "Run To Me", "Only the Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Anytime", "Begani Naar", "In These Arms", "Truck"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Kiss My Country Ass", "Feeling That Way", "Kuch Is Tarah", "Sick of You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["My Love (radio edit)", "Don't Stop Believin'", "A Day in the Life", "Locked Out of Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Black Ice", "I'll Be Alright Without You", "I Like How It Feels", "Marilyn Monroe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Wheel in the Sky", "Dance in the Dark", "When I See This Bar", "Falling Into You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Lovin' Touchin' Squeezin'", "A Boy Named Sue", "She will be loved", "F**kin' Perfect"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["As Your Friend", "Beautiful", "Words", "What It Takes to Win"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Kuch Is Tarah", "Man in the Mirror", "Of a Lifetime", "Autumn Leaves"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["The Party's Over (Hopelessly in Love)", "Ballad of a Teenage Queen", "A Groovy Kind Of Love", "Politik"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Faithfully", "God's Gonna Cut You Down", "Gravity", "Heavy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Tell Him", "Send Her My Love", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Bring Him Home", "We Will Rock You (Digital Remastered)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Fashion", "Over", "Open Arms", "the Heart of Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Hips Don't Lie (feat. Wyclef Jean)", "Sweet and Simple", "I'm Alive (Humberto Gatica mix)", "Kush"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["You Belong With Me", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma", "Violet Hill", "Still They Ride"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Windows Down", "Who's Crying Now", "Ullathai Killathe", "You Remind Me of Something"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Thuy's Death / You Will Not Touch Him", "I Need Love", "In My Place", "I Would Find You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Wish You Were Here", "Be Good to Yourself", "So Happy I Could Die", "Panjaban Theme"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["I Will Be", "Mockingbird", "Stone in Love", "Feels Like Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Lost One", "Feeling That Way / Anytime", "Misery", "San Quentin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Be True to Your School", "Encore", "Cruella De Vil", "Any Way You Want It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Figured You Out", "Grenade", "Otis", "Stay Awhile"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Free Fallin'", "Lights", "New Divide", "Show Me What You Got"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Little Girl", "Over", "California Girls (stereo)", "Last Call"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)", "Doesn't Mean Anything", "Look At Me", "Phoolan Ka Taron Ka"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Arnel Pineda?", "answers": ["Never Say Never", "Too Bad (Diggla mix)", "Whip It", "When You Love a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Summertime", "Jiya Dhadak Dhadak Jaye", "Round & Round", "Hard as a Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Lose Yourself", "You Had Me From Hello", "Shut Down", "Dosed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Hillbilly Bone", "Born and Raised", "Out Last Night (Previously Unreleased)", "Count on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Give It 2 Me", "Me and You", "Take It From Here", "Drops of Jupiter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["How Forever Feels", "Jam", "Bump n' Grind", "Come & Get It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Somewhere With You", "Tommie Sunshine\u2019s Megasix Smash-Up", "The Call", "Happy People"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Tie My Hands", "Lag Ja Gale", "Who's That Girl", "I Lost It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Umrao Jaan", "Triumphant (The New Iberican League Radio)", "My Wish", "You Save Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["The Call", "Good in Goodbye", "Feel Like a Rock Star", "Tell Me A Lie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Get Rhythm (feat. The Tennessee Two)", "That's Why I'm Here", "Smooth Criminal", "Ride On"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Aye-Dil-E-Nadan", "Lay Your Hands on Me", "Don't Blink", "Hotel California"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Chakna Chakna", "Old Blue Chair", "I Would", "Free"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Snitch", "Tonight (I'm Lovin' You)", "Anything But Mine", "The Power of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Hips Don't Lie (feat. Wyclef Jean)", "What Hurts the Most", "When I See This Bar", "I'll Be Alright Without You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Jiya Dhadak Dhadak Jaye", "I Go Back", "Warrior", "The Real Slim Shady"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Nobody's Perfect", "When I Close My Eyes", "Duaa", "Shouldn't Come Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Lucky (Glee Cast version)", "Because You Loved Me", "We Made You", "Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Beer in Mexico", "Ek Ladki Bheegi Bhaagi Si", "Love in Vain", "Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Back Where I Come From", "Lights", "Witchy Woman", "Good Times Bad Times"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Titanic", "Trying Not to Love You", "The Good Stuff", "Life Is Cinema"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Can\u2019t You Hear Me Knocking", "Baby I\u2019m a Star", "Dear Mr. President (From I'm Not Dead Live - Wembley Arena)", "She Thinks My Tractor's Sexy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Vole", "Pirate Flag", "True Colors", "Do You Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["There Goes My Life", "Elton John", "Crash My Party", "I'll Be Waiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Whoa Oh!", "Girl Gone Wild", "Come Over", "Lost One"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)", "When You Love a Woman", "Viva Las Vegas", "Mama's Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Won't Go Home Without You", "Charkha", "The Boys of Fall", "I Started a Joke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Fool Again (2000 remix)", "Be With You", "Bindiya Chamkegi (Do Raaste)", "Better as a Memory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Never Say Never", "Falling Down", "More Than a Woman", "Who You'd Be Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Nikita", "Nikita", "She's Got It All", "She Loves You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["Wooden Heart", "You and Tequila", "You're Not Sorry", "Can I Get A..."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kenny Chesney?", "answers": ["El Guardaespaldas", "Lost in the Echo", "Kuch Is Tarah", "My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Mahiya Ve", "Quit Playin' Games", "Se\u00f1orita", "Only the Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["When You're Gone", "Pehli Nazar Mein", "Hummingbird Heartbeat", "Little Saint Nick"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Cover Girl", "Kaun Hoon Main", "Cry Me a River", "Last Dollar (Fly Away)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Exodus", "Aadat (Deep Blue version)", "No More Sorrow", "American Idiot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Hum Kiss Galli", "Rude Boy", "Nobody Does It Like You", "Lovin' Touchin' Squeezin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Beautiful", "Tere Liye", "Chak Glass", "Mera Mann Kehne Laga (Reprise)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Piya O Re Piya", "Lost in the Echo", "Mohabbat Dil Ka Sakoon", "Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Take It Easy", "Duaa", "Homecoming: I. The Death of St. Jimmy / II. East 12th St. / III. Nobody Likes You / IV. Rock and Roll Girlfriend / V. We\u2019re Coming Home Again", "O Re Piya"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Road Trippin'", "Kyun Chor Gaye Rastay", "Who Says", "Home Sweet Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Stupid Hoe", "Bye Bye", "Piya O Re Piya (Sad)", "L.A. Boyz (feat. Victoria Justice and Ariana Grande)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Move On", "Hometown Glory", "Zindagi", "S & M"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Nothing Like Us", "Gal Sun Ja", "Sure Be Cool If You Did", "Somewhere With You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["(Drop Dead) Beautiful", "Piya (remixed by DJ Suketu)", "Ruby Tuesday", "Achha Lagta Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Faithfully", "Likhe Jo Khat Tujhe", "Be Intehaan", "Love So Right"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Belief", "Agar Tum Na Hote", "Rock n\u2019 Roll (Will Take You to the Mountain)", "Le Ja Tu Mujhe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Voulez-vous", "I Could Have Lied", "Doorie", "Kiss & Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Warning Sign", "Maula", "Gummybear Song", "Heart Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Love the Way You Lie", "Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain", "Wish You Were Here", "He Ain't the Leavin' Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Wake Me Up", "The Age of Worry", "Mar Jani Jhanjar", "Tu Mohabbat Hai (remixed by DJ Suketu)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Love Somebody", "Tera Hone Laga Hoon", "When You're Looking Like That", "The Way You Look Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Firework", "Music", "Hum Kis Gaali Ja (Dance Mix)", "Nari Kathai"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Saajna (unplugged)", "Chori Chori", "Woh Lamhe", "La La Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Crush", "Tere Bin", "Count On Me", "Tum Mujhe Yun Bhula Na Paoge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Mahi Ve", "Just Walk Away", "My Way (live)", "Ten Thousand Hours"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Stranger in Moscow", "Love Me Do", "Ehsaas", "Payphone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Don't Let Me Get Me", "Bangarang", "Mahiya Ve Soniya", "Chiquitita"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["\"How Deep Is Your Love (from \"\"Saturday Night Fever\"\")\"", "Without You", "Last Night on Earth", "Tu Jaane Na"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["The Reason", "Walking Contradiction", "Kuch Is Tarah", "Let It Be"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Renegade", "Give Me Love (True Tiger Remix)", "Cowboy Casanova", "Jal Pari"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Bakhuda Tumhi Ho", "Until It Sleeps", "It's a Beautiful Day", "Gimme That"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["O Mere Khuda", "You Win Again", "One Less Lonely Girl", "The Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Yakeen", "Kiss", "Kanday Utay", "Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Sathiyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Real Talk", "I Will Be", "Batdance", "She Will"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["For the Love of a Daughter", "Speedin'", "Emotions", "Nightingale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Night Fever", "The World's Greatest", "Naughty Girl", "Don't Forget To Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["You Remind Me of Something", "If I Knew", "Dreamin' (Bare Noize Remix)", "The Name of the Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Just a Dream", "Bump n' Grind", "Shakin Hands", "Cocaine Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Promise", "Keep You Much Longer", "So Happy I Could Die", "It Seems Like You're Ready"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["I Wish It Would Rain Down", "One And Only", "Satisfy You (feat. Puff Daddy)", "You're My Best Friend"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Let It Be", "Si tu te vas", "If I Could Turn Back the Hands of Time", "It's All Up to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["I Can't Sleep Baby (If I)", "Calling All Angels", "Part Of Me", "Phoolon Ke Rang Se"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["If You Ain't Here to Party", "Step in the Name of Love", "Thirty Three", "Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Uptown Girl", "Sex Therapy", "Doorie", "When a Woman's Fed Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Happy People", "I'd Come For You", "Rolling In The Deep", "I Need a Doctor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Gotham City", "Mine Would Be You", "Cama De Rosas", "Politik"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Ignition", "Kiss and Tell (Bonus Track)", "Dum", "Come Wake Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Burn It Down", "Lights", "The Storm Is Over Now", "The Four Horsemen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Feelin' on Yo Booty", "San Quentin", "I Just Had Sex", "When the Stars Go Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Down Low (Noboby Has to Know)", "I'd Come For You", "Ram Teri Ganga Maili: Sun Sahiba Sun", "Blackened"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["The Power of the Dream", "Fiesta", "Glitter in the Air", "Kyoto"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["I Like How It Feels", "I Believe", "Saans", "Be With You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Thoia Thoing", "Soul Rebel", "Love in This Club", "I Get Around"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Worldwide", "Immortality", "Speed of Sound", "Slow Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["WEEKENDS!!!", "Nobody's Home", "Hold Your Head Up", "12 Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Space Bound", "Hometown Glory", "I'm a Flirt", "My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Kiss Tomorrow Goodbye", "That's All Right", "Lying From You", "When a Man Lies"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["It's Me Bitches (remix)", "El Guardaespaldas", "Addicted", "Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Prem Bann", "Your Body's Callin'", "I Want You (She's So Heavy)", "Intro"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Both of Us", "Parler \u00e0 mon p\u00e8re", "You Make Me Want To", "I Wish"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Ave Maria", "New Day", "Invisible", "U Saved Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Hello", "Dive", "I'm Your Angel", "You're My Best Friend"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Trapped in the Closet Chapter 1", "Love Song", "Get The Party Started", "Takin' Back My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Hold My Hand", "Lay Your Hands on Me", "Wanna Love You Girl", "When a Woman Loves"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["I've Got You Under My Skin", "Hard as a Rock", "Kiss Tomorrow Goodbye", "Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Sacrifice", "Nobody Does It Like You", "Alguien soy yo", "Moment of Clarity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["I'm Gonna Live Till I Die", "Loba", "Experiencia religiosa", "Mirrors"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["No Me Digas Que No", "Still They Ride", "Better Than I Used to Be", "1+1"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Something in Your Mouth", "I'm with You", "Por amarte", "Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Cry Me a River", "Could I Have This Kiss Forever", "Whataya Want From Me", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Be With You", "Ankhon Se", "Borderline", "Sofa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Tonight (I'm Lovin' You)", "Whenever Wherever", "Kaise Mujhe", "Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["I Love You", "Ronan", "Hero (MetroMix)", "Ben"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Master of Puppets", "Uptown Girl", "Maula", "Bailamos"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Esperanza", "Harvest Time", "Wayfaring Stranger", "You'll Never Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Don't Let Me Be the Last to Know", "Good Riddance (Time of Your Life)", "Takin' Back My Love", "Touch My Body"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Hummingbird Heartbeat", "One Drop", "Turn Your Lights Down Low", "Si tu te vas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Don't Be Cruel", "Grenade", "Addicted", "Thoia Thoing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Unbroken", "Quiz\u00e1s", "Die in Your Arms", "Dreamworld"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Escape", "Closer Than Close", "Emotions (Mariah Carey cover)", "Don't Stop Believin' (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["California Dreaming", "I Tried", "Tu Jaane Na", "Heartbeat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["You Don't Know Me", "Is This the World We Created...?", "Escapar (Escape)", "One in a Million"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Always on My Mind (alternate Take 2)", "Right on Time", "Ring My Bells", "Family Portrait"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Perfectly Lonely", "Why Not Me?", "Kootthu Onnu", "Stray Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Chasing Cars", "My Name Is Skrillex", "Goliyan", "Somebody's Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Rumour Has It", "Can You Hear Me", "First Love Song", "I'm Still Breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Hold On", "I Like How It Feels", "Vole", "Hurts Like Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Dirty Dancer", "Kiss Me", "Country Man", "Love Will Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Smooth Criminal", "Ayer", "When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)", "Aadat (Deep Blue version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Irreplaceable (album version)", "Pyar Aaya", "Do You Know? (The Ping Pong Song)", "Good Vibrations"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["One in a Million", "Nunca Te Olvidar\u00e9", "My Name Is Skrillex", "Sun Rabba"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["You Remind Me of Something", "Firework", "Lego House", "Finally Found You (Papercha$er's Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Painting Pictures", "Heart of the City (Ain't No Love)", "Tired of Being Sorry", "We Don't Care"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Mentiroso", "Va Va Voom", "Inhale Deep", "Right Above It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Last Night on Earth", "Funeral for a Friend / Love Lies Bleeding", "Cry Me a River", "I Like It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Enrique Iglesias?", "answers": ["Madhuban Mein Radhika Nache", "Naked", "Turn the Page", "Mane Chudi Piravan Lagyo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Long Distance", "Touch My Body", "Put Your Hearts Up", "Grade 8"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Let the Groove Get In", "Ooh La La", "Autumn Leaves", "Dance in the Dark"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Stir It Up", "Always Be My Baby", "Stay (featuring Mikky Ekko)", "Chasing Cars"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Lego House", "You're the Devil in Disguise", "Ordinary Girl", "Rubberneckin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["I Love You", "Out Last Night (Previously Unreleased)", "I Know You're Gonna Be There", "Butterfly"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Chakna Chakna", "Take Care", "Honeymoon Avenue", "Fall (Live At the Bedford)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Love the Way You Lie", "Tujh Mein Rab Dikhta Hai", "Homeless (Live At the Bedford)", "Give It Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Gold Rush", "Hero", "Forever", "Dive"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["I Don't Miss You at All", "You Know It's Christmas", "Lonely", "Hush Little Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Wake Me Up When September Ends", "I Drove All Night", "Firefly", "Magical"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Pour It Up", "Smile", "Mann Ki Lagan", "Let it Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Never Gonna Be Alone", "God Is a DJ", "Sunburn", "Smell This Money (original mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Drunk", "Moondance", "Love and Marriage", "Off the Chain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Little Lady", "Life Is a Highway", "Why God Why?", "Iron Lion Zion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Stray Heart", "The Cowboy in Me", "Meri Zindagi Mein Ajnabee", "U.N.I."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Ek Ladki Bheegi Bhaagi Si", "Wake Me Up", "Don't Matter", "You And I"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["She", "Remind Me", "Are You Ready", "Sing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Farewell and Goodnight", "You Belong With Me", "Pearl", "Radio (Sir Spyro remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Where We Land", "Redemption Song (Band Version) Very Rare", "Hole in the World", "They Don't Know About Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["The A Team", "I'll Just Hold On", "We Don't Care", "Lose Yourself"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Thrift Shop", "Firework", "Come Fly With Me", "Small Bump"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Nothing Even Matters", "Your Body's Callin'", "Wake Up Call", "Cold Coffee"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Zindagi Ka Safar Hai Yeh Kaisa", "Human Nature", "I Have a Dream", "Little Bird"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Do You Remember", "Baby One More Time", "Sofa", "After All"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Funny DJ", "Kiss Me", "Na Na Na", "My Name Is"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Kaya", "One Night", "I Want to Break Free", "Goliyan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Stay at Home Dad", "Hit the Lights", "Be Like You", "Simple"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Heart Attack", "The City", "All Nightmare Long", "Lady Lynda"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["If I Never See Your Face Again", "This", "Sing for the Moment", "As Tears Go By"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Shot for Me", "Thrift Shop", "Who Owns My Heart", "Give Me Love (True Tiger Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Roop Tera Mastana", "I'm Your Angel", "Shattered", "You Don't Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Take You", "Just Lose It", "Gummy Bear Instrumental", "Papercut (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["A Little Less Conversation (JXL radio edit remix)", "Yara Seeli Seeli", "I'll Be Waiting", "Ass Like That"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Without Me", "All Tied Up", "Erotic City", "Thank You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Sing for the Moment", "Can U Help Me", "Son of Man", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Satisfy My Soul", "Higher Ground", "Blown Away", "Space Bound"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Daydreamer", "Lose Yourself", "Tell Me Baby", "Tommy Chong"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Surfin' Safari", "Don't Do That", "Celebration Day", "Like Toy Soldiers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["7 Things", "More Than a Woman", "Girl Gone Wild", "Hello"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Business", "Umbrella (feat. Jay-Z)", "Green Eyes", "Don\u2019t Hold the Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Don't Let Me Get Me", "Haven't Met You Yet", "No Love", "If I Ain't Got You (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Wipe Your Eyes", "Elton John", "Blow Me (One Last Kiss)", "That's All She Wrote"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Love the Way You Lie", "Beautiful People", "Doesn't Mean Anything", "Alice (extended version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Stuck", "We Made You", "My All", "Intro"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Not Afraid", "If I Can Dream", "The Devil\u2019s Den", "You Are"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Funny DJ", "Mockingbird", "One Thing", "Maine to Khadi Chhat Ke Upar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["I Walk The Line", "Turn Up the Music", "My Name Is", "No One"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Superman", "The Rain Song", "Crash My Party", "Falling Into You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap", "I Need a Doctor", "By the Way", "Love and Marriage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Real Slim Shady", "Dear John", "Ghosts", "Million Dolla Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Music", "Dil aisa kisi ne mera toda", "Someone Else Calling You Baby", "Miraksam"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["I Got U", "Reptile\u2019s Theme", "W.T.P.", "Yellow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Wheel in the Sky", "Wish You Were Here", "Forgot About Dre", "Start All Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Lag Ja Gale Se Phir", "Stan", "Sk8er Boi", "Google Google"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["'Till I Collapse", "Overprotected", "When I Come Around (album version)", "First Love Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["The One", "Beautiful", "A Day in the Life", "Teri Meri"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Help", "Drop the World", "Irresistible", "Lovin' Touchin' Squeezin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Day Before You Came", "Cleaning Out My Closet", "Count on Me", "En Ti Dej\u00e9 Mi Amor"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["When I'm Gone", "Won't Go Home Without You", "Two Black Cadillacs", "Truck Yeah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Elton John", "Goodbye Yellow Brick Road", "The Way I Am", "Anything But Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["Total Eclipse of the Heart", "Hair", "Pon de Replay", "Shake That"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eminem?", "answers": ["You Don't Fool Me", "Trouble", "8 Mile", "Somebody to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Rock With You", "Forgotten", "Husn Di Botel", "Uptown Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["The Song Remains the Same", "Papercut (remix)", "Give Me All Your Luvin' (Party Rock remix)", "I Wanna Be Your Lover"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Boyfriend", "Freedom", "My Way (live)", "In the End"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Breaking the Habit", "I Need Love", "Have a Nice Day (album version)", "Don't Make Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Feelin' on Yo Booty", "Bleed It Out", "It's Me Bitches (remix)", "Give Your Heart a Break"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["When You Believe (From the Prince of Egypt)", "Numb", "Muskura", "Warning Sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Gimme Shelter", "Lying From You", "I Just Had Sex", "Last of the American Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["I Still", "Blue Ocean Floor", "Break The Ice", "A Thousand Suns: The Full Experience"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["St. Patrick's Day", "Man in the Mirror", "Leave Out All the Rest", "Neon Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["St. Patrick's Day", "D'Evils", "No More Sorrow", "Neele Neele Ambar Par"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Castle of Glass", "Fuel", "Life in Technicolor", "Dirty Dancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Moments", "Shadow Of The Day", "I'm Movin' On", "Wake Me Up When September Ends"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Creeping Death", "Trust Issues", "Las de la Intuici\u00f3n", "A Place for My Head"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Bang a Drum", "Something in Your Mouth", "Come Fly With Me", "Faint"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Kaun Hoon Main", "One Step Closer", "Tommie Sunshine\u2019s Megasix Smash-Up", "Tera Ishq Bada Teekha"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Bad Kids", "The Catalyst", "Shiver", "Runaway"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["I'm Not a Girl Not Yet a Woman", "Zero", "Don\u2019t Stay", "Ass Like That"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["What I've Done", "Kill the DJ", "Never Gone", "Wasted"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Te amo", "Just Dance", "Longview", "Burn It Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Ur So Gay", "Who Am I?", "Fingerprints", "Pushing Me Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Feels Like Today", "My Name Is", "By Myself", "Remember When"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["From the Inside", "The Ruler's Back", "This Ain't Goodbye", "Ankhon Se"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Points of Authority", "Hummer", "Heartbreaker", "Michelle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Given Up", "Keep You Much Longer", "Gotham City", "Bleed"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Forever", "Iridescent", "Radha", "Lil' Freak"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Ab Mujhe Raat Din", "One More Night", "Nights on Broadway", "Crawling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Muzzle", "Give It Away", "Lost in the Echo", "Hold On"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Give Me Love (True Tiger Remix)", "Session", "Last of the American Girls", "Ray of Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["What Country Is", "Jaane Ya Ali Ali Ali", "Pata Chalgea", "Waiting for the End"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["New Divide", "Kush", "Speak Now", "Heartbeat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["That's All Right", "Figure.09", "All the Man That I Need", "Imagine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Deuces", "Bounce", "I'm Your Funny Bear (Gelatine club mix)", "Somewhere I Belong"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Don't Stop Believin'", "I Could Have Lied", "Use Your Love", "Take You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Give It 2 Me", "Into the Groove", "Something in Your Mouth", "Still They Ride"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Badan Pe Sitare (Prince)", "That's All She Wrote", "Hard to Concentrate", "Open Arms"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["A Place for My Head", "Garaari (feat. Meet Malkit)", "Bandz a Maker Her Dance", "I Would Find You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["As I Am (intro)", "One of Those Nights", "Sweet and Simple", "Ehsaas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Entre Deux Mondes", "Faithfully", "Since I've Been Loving You", "Under The Bridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "I Can't Make You Love Me", "Superman", "Send Her My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Escape", "Karma", "Summerboy", "Batdance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Bounce", "Of a Lifetime", "All at Once", "As Your Friend"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["I'll Be Alright Without You", "D.O.A. (Death of Auto-Tune)", "Aap Ki Ankhon Mein", "Remember High School"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Mere Dil Ki Duniya Mein", "Angel (feat. David Guetta)", "Lovin' Touchin' Squeezin'", "Slow Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Celebration Day", "Pehli Nazar Mein", "If I Were a Boy", "Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Burn It to the Ground", "When You Love a Woman", "To Be Loved", "The Way I Loved You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Bump n' Grind", "Lights", "Easy", "Gimme! Gimme! Gimme! (A Man After Midnight)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Savin' Me", "On and On and On", "Wide Awake", "Ask the Lonely"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Anytime", "Koi Humdum Na Raha", "Moon River", "Ankhon Se"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Beez in the Trap", "Little Girl", "Last First Kiss", "D\u2019yer Mak\u2019er"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["One Love", "Satisfy My Soul", "Lost in the Echo", "Who's Crying Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Mahiya Ve Soniya", "Last Friday Night (T.G.I.F.)", "No Love", "After All These Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Red", "To Be Loved", "Be Good to Yourself", "Funny DJ"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Beautiful", "Vaishnav Jan To Tene Kahiye", "Only the Young", "Famous"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Lighters", "Wheel in the Sky", "The Unforgiven", "Me and Mrs. Jones"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Feeling That Way", "Heart of the City (Ain't No Love)", "California Dreaming", "Pairon Mein Bandhan Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["To Love Somebody", "Hummer", "Feeling That Way / Anytime", "Don\u2019t Hold the Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Stay Awhile", "Asphalt Cowboy", "Do I", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["If We Ever Meet Again", "Mera Jeevan Kora Kagaz", "Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites (Zedd remix)", "Stone in Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["No Leaf Clover", "Girl Gone Wild", "Come & Get It", "The Party's Over (Hopelessly in Love)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["When All Is Said and Done", "Shut Up and Drive", "Best of My Love", "Girl Can't Help It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Honky Tonk Women", "Kyun Chor Gaye Rastay", "City of Hope", "Garaari (feat. Meet Malkit)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["Any Way You Want It", "Sweet Love", "Hummer", "Teri Meri (Reprise)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Journey?", "answers": ["What It Takes to Win", "Neon Lights", "It's Not Right but It's Okay", "A Groovy Kind Of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["O Duniya Ke Rakhwale", "Playboys of the Southwestern World", "The Reason", "Drop the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["All About Tonight", "Christmas Tree", "Come Wake Me Up", "Pearl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Does Your Mother Know", "Doin' What She Likes", "Song for You", "Separate Ways"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["The Lazy Song", "Sober", "Run", "Boys 'Round Here (feat. Pistol Annies)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Dil Ka Rishta", "The Wonder of You", "If You Can Afford Me", "The More I Drink"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["You'll Never Know", "Computer Blue", "Nobody But Me", "Pon de Replay"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["I Found Someone", "I Like It That Way", "Lucy in the Sky With Diamonds", "Hakuna Matata"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["True Love", "Two Pieces", "God Gave Me You", "Trouble Nobody"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Chura Ke Dil Mera", "There You Go", "Do You Remember", "What Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Goodbye Time", "Doesn't Mean Anything", "Ghost of You", "Holly Jolly Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Ten Times Crazier", "I Got You", "Folsom Prison Blues (mono)", "Take It All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Please Remember Me", "Faith Won't Fall", "If I Ain't Got You", "Some Beach"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Teardrops on My Guitar", "Honey Bee", "Pearl", "Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["I Won't Let Go", "Pyar Ke Baatein", "Granddaddy's Gun", "If It's Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["When All Is Said and Done", "Little Bird", "Million Dolla Baby", "You Are"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Love Story", "Hillbilly Bone", "Where Them Girls At", "Tum Mujhe Yun Bhula Na Paoge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Who Am I Living For?", "The Last Night of the World", "Fake ID", "Austin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Inevitable", "Warrior", "You Shook Me All Night Long", "Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Who Are You When I'm Not Looking", "Dream", "Don't Stop 'Til You Get Enough (album version)", "Hammer to Fall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Bottoms Up", "Smile", "Drink on It", "They Don't Know About Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["My Eyes (feat. Gwen Sebastian)", "Dreamworld", "Again", "Believe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Take Me With U", "All Too Well", "Ol' Red", "(Drop Dead) Beautiful"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Aaja Ve", "No", "Angels Cry", "She Wouldn't Be Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["The Way You Look Tonight:", "Who You'd Be Today", "Chak Glass", "Sure Be Cool If You Did"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Itt Van A Gumimaci (Hungarian)", "I'll Just Hold On", "Two Pieces", "Feels Good at First"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Green", "Guide: Gaata Rahe Mera Dil", "Ring Of Fire", "Who's Lovin' You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Angry All the Time", "Under The Bridge", "Does Your Mother Know", "Kiss My Country Ass"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Home", "Young Forever", "Mama Africa", "Deuces"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Man Down", "Aap Ki Khatir", "The Baby", "This Is Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["Sun Rabba", "To Love You More", "Larger Than Life", "Mine Would Be You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Blake Shelton?", "answers": ["First Time Ever I Saw Your Face", "Mere Sapnon Ki Rani", "Don't Make Me", "Mann Ki Lagan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["So Emotional", "Begani Naar", "Get Over It", "Heartbreaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["I'm Your Funny Bear (Gelatine club mix)", "Pretty Maids All In A Row", "Down Low (Noboby Has to Know)", "Beautiful"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Best of My Love", "Magic", "When We Stand Together", "Lego House"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Already Gone", "Tum Dil Ki Dhadkan Mein", "From the Inside", "Head Banger (feat. Escape)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Your Body Is a Wonderland", "See You Again", "Ordinary Girl", "Heartache Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Last Name", "Remember December", "Try and Love Again", "Baazigar O Baazigar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Age of Worry", "Love Will Keep Us Alive", "Inhale Deep", "Trust Issues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Could You Be Loved", "Those Shoes", "Stayin' Alive", "The Edge of Glory"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Burning Love", "Take It Easy", "the Heart of Life", "Stuck in the Moment"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["In the City", "It's In The Mornin (feat. Snoop Dogg)", "Beer in Mexico", "Better Left Unsaid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Hotel California", "Where We Land", "Stranger in Moscow", "Panjaban Theme"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Don\u2019t Let Me Down", "Tommy Chong", "Don't Take Your Guns To Town", "Saturday Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Moments", "Lyin' Eyes", "Shot for Me", "E.T."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Numb", "James Dean", "Bang a Drum", "The Wonder of You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Just a Dream", "Take It to the Limit", "DJ Got Us Fallin' in Love", "Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Victim of Love", "Charlie Brown", "Nobody Knows", "Papa Don't Preach"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["My Eyes (feat. Gwen Sebastian)", "The Way", "Liberian Girl", "Tequila Sunrise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["New Kid in Town", "Baby I\u2019m a Star", "I Found a Boy", "Photograph"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Last Resort", "Feels Good at First", "Surfin' Safari", "Popular Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Seven Bridges Road", "Rabiosa", "Just Dance", "Lying From You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Life in the Fast Lane", "Lightweight", "Tiny Dancer", "Give It Up to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Forever", "Sex Therapy", "Doolin-Dalton", "How Will I Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Yesterday", "Walk of Shame", "Intro", "Teri Meri (Reprise)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Journey of the Sorcerer", "Man Dole Mera Tan Dole", "My Wish", "Birthday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Lo Que Soy (This Is Me Spanish version)", "I Won't Apologize", "Start All Over", "I Can\u2019t Tell You Why"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Please Come Home for Christmas", "Me and You", "Make You Feel My Love", "Girls Got Rhythm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Undo It", "Peaceful Easy Feeling", "Where Do Broken Hearts Go", "You Make Me Feel So Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["You the Boss (album version) (Explicit)", "Major Minus", "Best Thing I Never Had", "Wasted Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Girl From Yesterday", "Bichdann", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "Escapar (Escape)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["You Don't Know My Name", "How Long", "No One Else Comes Close", "B-Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["\"Can You Feel the Love Tonight (from \"\"The Lion King\"\")\"", "Witchy Woman", "You and Tequila", "Fire We Make"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Eagles?", "answers": ["Mera Mann Kehne Laga (Reprise)", "Hole in the World", "Keep You Much Longer", "Tunnel Vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["It's a Beautiful Day", "Promise", "LoveStoned/I Think She Knows (interlude)", "Austin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Kanday Utay", "Like Money", "U Remind Me", "Run to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Is Kadar Pyar Hai Tumse", "I Believe in You and Me", "Numb", "Satisfya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Mera Rang De Basanti", "I Have a Dream", "You Make Me Wanna...", "Tattooed Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Chamak Challo Chel Chabeli", "Come", "You Got It Bad", "Greatest Love of All"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["I Wish", "Lil' Freak", "Can't Hold Us", "Back Where I Come From"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me", "Dive", "One Night", "I Wanna Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Rest of My Life (Extended)", "Sunburn", "Hole in the World", "Heartbreaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Can't Stop Loving You", "Tees Maar Khan", "Jhalak Dikhlaja", "Superstar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Mere Sapnon Ki Rani", "I've Been Everywhere", "Circle of Life", "Climax"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Can U Help Me", "Te amo", "Chandaniya (Lori Lori)", "Free"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Something That We're Not", "Heart of the City (Ain't No Love)", "Ek Pagla Meri Gali Ka", "That's What It's Made For"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Love in This Club", "She will be loved", "Waking Up In Vegas", "Misery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["The Show Must Go On", "The Climb", "You the Boss (album version) (Explicit)", "Bad Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Kuch Is Tarah", "Everytime (album version)", "DJ Got Us Fallin' in Love", "Stan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Good Times Bad Times", "Cheers (Drink to That)", "Have a Nice Day (album version)", "Lemme See"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Dreamin' (Bare Noize Remix)", "Warrior", "Electric Feel", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["What I've Done", "John", "Dil Kya Kare", "Nice & Slow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Trading Places", "Super Trouper", "Holiday", "Castle of Glass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Always on My Mind (alternate Take 2)", "Kiss Tomorrow Goodbye", "OMG", "Dark"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Stole My Heart", "In Your Atmosphere", "My Boo", "Black Dog"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Summer Wind (feat. Julio Iglesias)", "Ehsaas", "Run", "There Goes My Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Everybody (Backstreet's Back)", "Run", "4 Minutes", "Hey Daddy (Daddy's Home)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Thank You for the Music", "Confessions (interlude)", "Run It!", "Curse of Indra"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["SexyBack", "No Worries", "Never Again", "Moving Mountains"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Hero (MetroMix)", "Lego House", "Freedom", "His Mistakes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Jailhouse Rock", "Too Much Heaven", "Soul To Squeeze", "Without U (interlude)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Get Me Bodied", "Scream", "Secret", "Kaya"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Little Things", "Pendu Jatt", "Up", "Papers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["There's a Place for Us", "Back to December (acoustic)", "Come Over", "More"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Usher?", "answers": ["Beat It", "I Surrender", "Caught Up", "Dil Jhoom Jhoom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Better Than I Used to Be", "The Lady Is a Tramp", "When the Stars Go Blue", "Born to Be My Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Someday I'll Be Saturday Night", "For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "Here Comes the Sun", "Take It From Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Tere Bina (Indian)", "Michelle", "Papa Don't Preach", "Shot Through the Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Hey Hey What Can I Do", "Satisfy You (feat. Puff Daddy)", "Tragedy", "Never Say Goodbye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["'Till I Collapse", "Eyes Open", "Runaway", "Take Me With U"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Abhi Mujh Main Kahin", "Girlfriend", "Neon", "It's My Life (2003)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Is This Love", "Doin' Dirt", "Help!", "What About Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Dressin\u2019 Up", "Bed of Roses", "Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)", "Lost in the Echo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Put It in a Love Song", "Bad Medicine", "How Long", "Lay All Your Love on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Fly to Your Heart", "Pyar Aaya", "Hook Me Up", "Leader of Men (acoustic)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["This Ain't a Love Song", "You Can't Hurry Love", "Party on My Mind", "I Guess That's Why They Call It the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Thank You for Loving Me", "Who You'd Be Today", "One of Those Nights", "Letting Go (Dutty Love)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Everything Has Changed (feat. Ed Sheeran)", "I'll Just Hold On", "Cover Girl", "You Give Love a Bad Name"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Stupid Hoe", "Austin", "Bless the Broken Road", "Cama De Rosas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["In These Arms", "Leader of Men (acoustic)", "Supergirl", "Scar Tissue"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["I Need You Tonight", "The Party's Over (Hopelessly in Love)", "(You Want To) Make a Memory", "The Last Night of the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["More Than Words", "The Way", "Touch Me (Gummib\u00e3*R)", "These Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Whiskey in the Jar", "Sick of You", "The One", "We Weren't Born to Follow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Kiss", "If I Were a Boy", "Santa Fe", "Don't Stop 'Til You Get Enough (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Chiquitita", "Lay Your Hands on Me", "I've Been Everywhere", "Gotta Be You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Are You Ready", "Aadat (Deep Blue version)", "All About Lovin' You", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Aaj Mausam Bada Beimann Hai (Today the Weather Plays Tricks on Me)", "Pretty Little Ditty", "Misunderstood", "Birthday Cake"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Stranger in Moscow", "Thalaattu Ketka Nanum", "I'll Be There for You", "When We Stand Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Leaving", "Kaatu Vazhi", "We Will Rock You (with Beyonce & Pink)", "What Do You Got?"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Have a Nice Day (album version)", "Schoolin' Life", "Rolling In The Deep", "Kiss Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Because We Can", "Everything", "D\u2019yer Mak\u2019er", "Now That I've Seen Her"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Always", "Crazy for You", "You're Gonna Make Me Lonesome When You Go", "The Edge of Glory"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Let It Snow! Let It Snow! Let It Snow!", "Old Blue Chair", "Slow Down", "Who Says You Can't Go Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Wanted Dead or Alive", "Yeah 3X", "Moment 4 Life (feat. Drake)", "Rock 'n' Roll Train"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Gasoline", "Mere Naseeb Mein (Naseeb)", "Change My Mind", "Livin' on a Prayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Keep the Faith", "Cocaine Blues", "Sad but True", "American Idiot"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Love You Like a Love Song", "Ten Years Gone", "Como Yo Nadie Te Ha Amado", "Is Kadar Pyar Hai Tumse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Dreamin' (Bare Noize Remix)", "Always Be My Baby", "Mermaid", "I Want"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["I Guess That's Why They Call It the Blues", "Stand Up", "Countdown", "Make You Feel My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Get Me Bodied", "Change My Mind", "Born to Be My Baby", "California Gurls"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Smile", "Another World", "Cherish", "Starships"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Irresistible", "Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "If It's Love", "I'm Lovin' It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Last First Kiss", "The Celestials", "Country Man", "Piece Of Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Same Love", "Live While We're Young", "Make You Feel My Love", "Suit & Tie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Schei\u00dfe (DJ White Shadow Mugler)", "Gotta Be You", "I Won't Apologize", "Yo\u00fc and I"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Funhouse", "Javert's Suicide", "A Milli", "One Way or Another (Teenage Kicks)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Up All Night", "Peli Waar", "Doom And Gloom", "Panjaban Theme"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Magical", "Fool That I Am", "Rude Boy", "I Would"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Believe in Me", "Rock Me", "Mahiya Ve Soniya", "Sorority Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["I Learned From You", "4 Minutes", "Glad You Came", "What Makes You Beautiful"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["50 Ways to Say Goodbye", "I Wish", "Calling All Angels", "Count On Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Try It on My Own", "One Thing", "Best of My Love", "Windows Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Ring Of Fire", "Same Love", "Keep You Much Longer", "They Don't Know About Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Don't Do That", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)", "Save You Tonight", "Dive"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Ain't No Grave", "Fool in the Rain", "Everything About You", "Anywhere For You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["The Reason", "Business", "Hollywood", "Over Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Blow Me (One Last Kiss)", "One And Only", "I Can Transform Ya", "Taken"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Stole My Heart", "My Happy Ending", "I Just Can't Stop Loving You", "Get Me Bodied"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Harvest Time", "Pop That", "Little Things", "Shakin' It 4 Daddy (feat. Nicki Minaj)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Summer Nights", "Don't Be Cruel", "Venice Queen", "Summer Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Stay at Home Dad", "More Than This", "High Hopes", "What Have I Done?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Na Na Na", "Karma", "Don't Go Breaking My Heart", "I Still Believe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["The Zephyr Song", "Snow (Hey Oh)", "Forever", "Heart Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Mirrors", "Right Now (featuring David Guetta)", "Feel Like a Rock Star", "Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Please Don't Leave Me", "When I See This Bar", "Tera Mera Pyar Amar", "Kiss You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Moments", "In Love With the Girl", "Tommy Chong", "Frozen (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by One Direction?", "answers": ["Dangerous", "Innuendo", "Tell Me A Lie", "This Is Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["The Best Is Yet to Come", "Trenchtown Rock", "Talking To The Moon (Acoustic)", "You Can't Always Get What You Want"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Chup Kar Ke - Remix", "Flying Without Wings", "Count On Me", "You and Tequila"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Stray Heart", "Feeling Good", "Runaway Baby", "Mehfooz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Nothing Compares 2 U", "Stiff Upper Lip", "Love of My Life", "Moonshine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Mockingbird", "Somebody's Me", "Hometown Glory", "Treasure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Locked Out of Heaven", "Hey Jude", "Still Getting It", "I Go Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Love in Vain", "For Whom the Bell Tolls", "Fever", "Just the Way You Are"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Billionaire", "Enter Sandman", "I'll Just Hold On", "The Best Damn Thing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["If I Was Your Girlfriend", "Move On", "Crocodile Rock", "Kasam Khake Kaho"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Bandz a Maker Her Dance", "I Wanna Grow Old With You", "Die in Your Arms", "Grenade"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Long Distance", "Vogue", "Figure.09", "Tere Bin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Marry You", "Mandy (live at the O2)", "Warning Sign", "Anything But Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["If I Knew", "Fa La La", "The Party's Over (Hopelessly in Love)", "Shot for Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["The End", "Natalie", "At Last", "Easy Skanking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Girlfriend", "Nothing Lasts Forever", "Bubble Butt", "Countdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Play Hard", "Thanimayil", "It Will Rain", "Beast of Burden"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["I Found a Boy", "Could You Be Loved", "Love and Marriage", "Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["For Those About To Rock (We Salute You)", "Seven Bridges Road", "The Other Side (Feat. Cee Lo Green And B.o.B)", "One"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["One More Night", "Gorilla", "If I Was Your Girlfriend", "Our Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Martin Guerre", "Tera Surroor", "When I'm Gone", "Our First Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Soledad", "Show Me", "The Way You Look Tonight:", "Tera Mera Pyar Amar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["It's All Up to You", "Right Now (featuring David Guetta)", "Figured You Out", "Catch a Grenade (The Hooligans remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Chori Chori", "The Lazy Song", "Firefly", "Hero"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Run To Me", "Starstruck", "Ronan", "Liquor Store Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["What Goes Around.../...Comes Around (interlude)", "Old & Crazy", "Sorority Girl", "Me and My Gang"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Somewhere in Brooklyn", "Nazar Se Nazar Tum", "Everything I Can't Have", "Daydreamer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Always on My Mind (alternate Take 2)", "Lighters", "First Time Ever I Saw Your Face", "Wish You Were Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Take It to the Head", "Young Girls", "Can't Buy Me Love", "Headlines"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Like We Never Loved at All", "Keep Holding On", "Hollywood", "Money Make Her Smile"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["So What", "When I Was Your Man", "Shot Through the Heart", "Cherish"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Overboard", "Time of Our Life", "Stairway to Heaven", "Yeh Dil Aur Unki Nigahon Ke Saaye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["California Gurls", "Mandy (live at the O2)", "I Know You Know (feat. Cymphonique)", "Haven't Met You Yet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["America", "Help", "Tum Mujhe Yun Bhula Na Paoge", "More Than a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["No Love", "We Can Work It Out", "Emotions (Mariah Carey cover)", "When I Look to the Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["I Don't Trust Myself (With Loving You)", "Stay Schemin'", "O Sahiba O Sahiba", "Famous"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Somewhere With You", "Lovin' Touchin' Squeezin'", "Emotions", "Nothing Even Matters"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Takin' Back My Love", "Oh Yeah", "Pendu Jatt", "Chup Kar Ke - Remix"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Do You Remember", "Night Fever", "Can't Buy Me Love", "Calling All Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["I Love You", "Invisible", "My All", "Now That I've Seen Her"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Til I Forget About You", "Moving Mountains", "Future Lovers", "These Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Boyfriend", "Birthday", "Run", "Deewana Tera"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Belief", "Tere Bina", "Pearl", "Count on You (feat. Jordin Sparks)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Sorry Seems To Be The Hardest Word", "All I Want for Christmas", "409", "Give Me All Your Luvin' (Party Rock remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Felt Good on My Lips", "Love Me Love Me", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Stars", "When a Woman Loves"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["O Mere Khuda", "How Forever Feels", "My All", "City Is Ours"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["American Idiot", "Big Time Rush (Theme)", "Wouldn't It Be Nice", "Two Pieces"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Let There Be Rock", "If I Ruled the World", "Free", "Nai Reina"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Worldwide", "Girl Can't Help It", "All Too Well", "Love in This Club"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Pairon Mein Bandhan Hai", "Cover Girl", "Soledad", "Waiting for the End"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Zindagi Ek Safar Hai Suhana", "Winner at a Losing Game", "When I Come Around (album version)", "Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Believe", "Stuck", "Whiskey in the Jar", "I Won't Apologize"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["This Is It", "Maine to Khadi Chhat Ke Upar", "Big Night", "To Live Is to Die"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Bodies", "Zero", "You Give Love a Bad Name", "You're Not Alone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Ignition", "Windows Down", "Teri Meri", "Stay Awhile"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Voulez-vous", "Fake ID", "Climax", "Halfway There"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["I Melt", "White Privilege", "Music Sounds Better With U", "Soma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Make It Bun Dem (Electro Body trance remix by Sthilmann)", "Drops of Jupiter", "Rapture", "All Over Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Eleanor Rigby", "Dreaming With a Broken Heart", "No Idea", "I Still Believe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)", "Funhouse", "Always on My Mind", "Show Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Big Time Rush?", "answers": ["Angie", "Keep the Faith", "Fix a Heart", "Any Kind of Guy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Desensitized", "Too Bad (Diggla mix)", "Moby Dick", "The Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Seven Bridges Road", "Wake Up Call", "If I Ruled the World", "Right There"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Chalte Chalte", "Put Your Hearts Up", "Eagle", "Raabta (Night In Motel)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Baby I", "Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain", "Always on My Mind", "Crazy Little Thing Called Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Almost Is Never Enough", "Run", "I Have a Dream", "The Name of the Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["L.A. Boyz (feat. Victoria Justice and Ariana Grande)", "I'd Give My Life for You", "Superwoman", "Hero (MetroMix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Catch Me", "You'll Never Know", "Is This the World We Created...?", "Little Bit Later On"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Like Money", "Is Kadar Pyar Hai Tumse", "Popular Song", "Wave"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Piano", "Pal Pal Dil Ke Pas", "Goodbye's (The Saddest Word)", "Billie Jean"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Pyar Ke Baatein", "War Machine", "Lovin' It", "Take It From Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Give It Up", "The Rose", "Confrontation", "Do You Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Honeymoon Avenue", "Midnight Rambler", "Lady Lynda", "Aaj Mausam Bada Beimann Hai (Today the Weather Plays Tricks on Me)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Ab Mujhe Raat Din", "Uptown Girl", "It Will Rain", "Tattooed Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Do You Hear What I Hear", "Better Left Unsaid", "It's Time", "Bye Bye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Lonely", "Emotions (Mariah Carey cover)", "Californication", "What It Takes to Win"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["O Sahiba O Sahiba", "Daydreamin'", "Jive Talkin'", "Crazy for You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Breaking the Girl", "Across the Universe", "Everything Has Changed (feat. Ed Sheeran)", "Simple"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Promise", "Drive My Car", "Take It to the Head", "Isaiyarasi (feat. S. Rajeswari & S. Janaki)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Yellow Submarine", "I'll See You Again", "Irreplaceable (album version)", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Ego", "Tere Mast Mast Do Nain", "Letting Go (Dutty Love)", "Oh! Darling"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["In My Life", "Love After War", "Pyar Kiya to Darna Kya", "For Whom the Bell Tolls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["The Prayer", "Love Me Do", "My Name Is Skrillex", "Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Feeling That Way / Anytime", "She Loves You", "Flash", "Ring My Bells"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["If I Could Turn Back the Hands of Time", "Help!", "Thunderstruck", "Don't Be Cruel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Middle of Nowhere", "Save You Tonight", "Cold Shoulder", "A Hard Day\u2019s Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Tu Mohabbat Hai (remixed by DJ Suketu)", "Eleanor Rigby", "Music", "You Drive Me Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Burn It to the Ground", "Yesterday", "Remember December", "The First Noel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Iridescent", "Kokomo", "Come Together", "Shakin' It 4 Daddy (feat. Nicki Minaj)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Lighters", "Moment 4 Life (feat. Drake)", "Here Comes the Sun", "Your Body Is a Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Eagle", "Ghost of You", "All You Need Is Love", "Did It Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Look At Me", "Give Your Heart a Break", "Lucy in the Sky With Diamonds", "Someday"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Be Alright", "Let It Be", "Achilles Last Stand", "Mentiroso"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Hey Jude", "Born to Be My Baby", "Feeling That Way / Anytime", "Sure Be Cool If You Did"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Forever", "Mere Mitwa Mere Meet Re", "Helter Skelter", "Give It Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["If I Were a Carpenter", "Don\u2019t Let Me Down", "Doorie", "When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Jackson", "Cocaine Blues", "Michelle", "Dilli Wali Girlfriend"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Blackbird", "Ever Ever After (record version)", "I Go Back", "Daydreamer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Just Walk Away", "I Want You (She's So Heavy)", "U Saved Me", "Shapath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Man Down", "I Am the Walrus", "Never Let You Go", "Brand New Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["I Want to Hold Your Hand", "Count on You (feat. Jordin Sparks)", "Supergirl", "Popular Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Are You Ready", "El Guardaespaldas", "Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "Norwegian Wood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["I Walk The Line", "How Did I Fall in Love With You", "Revolution", "You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Twist and Shout", "Hate That I Love You", "Tequila Sunrise", "Love and Marriage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Autumn Leaves", "Begin Again", "Strawberry Fields Forever", "Be Intehaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Drown", "A Day in the Life", "Aadat (Deep Blue version)", "As I Am (intro)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Song for You", "You Really Got Me", "Something", "Antologia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Cabron", "The Last Resort", "Birthday", "Everything Back But You (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Dolna", "Tunnel Vision", "Don't Blink", "Rubberneckin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Don't Be Cruel", "Bodies", "What About Now", "When I See This Bar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["2012", "Tragedy", "Snow (Hey Oh)", "Jailhouse Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["What Country Is", "Aye-Dil-E-Nadan", "Picture to Burn", "Hound Dog"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Skyline Pigeon", "Wooden Heart", "Perfect", "Believe It or Not"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Heartbreak Hotel", "She Wouldn't Be Gone", "Addicted", "Just Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Stand Up", "I Want to Break Free", "Paparazzi", "A Little Less Conversation (JXL radio edit remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Gundello Godari", "Prem Bann", "It's Now or Never", "Drown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Time Is on My Side", "Hard as a Rock", "In The Ghetto", "Gorilla"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Piya O Re Piya (Sad)", "Quiz\u00e1s", "One Night", "Sometimes It Snows in April"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)", "If I Ain't Got You", "Birthday", "Burning Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["That's All Right", "Jaoon Kahan", "No Love", "Run This Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Yeh Zindagi Usi Ki Hai", "I'm Counting on You", "I Got You", "Remind Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Boys 'Round Here (feat. Pistol Annies)", "Viva Las Vegas", "Runaway Baby", "He Ain't the Leavin' Kind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)", "Return to Sender", "I Love You", "A Little Fall of Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Use Your Love", "You the Boss (album version) (Explicit)", "Love Me Tender", "Intro"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Viraaniya", "Smell This Money (original mix)", "The First Noel", "If I Can Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["If I Ain't Got You (live)", "Piece Of Me", "You're the Devil in Disguise", "Saturday Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Amazing Grace", "Somebody's Me", "The Power of Good-Bye (album version)", "Fireman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Rest of My Life (Extended)", "La La Land", "America", "Never Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Are You Lonesome Tonight", "Adore", "One of Us", "Enfant de L'homme"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Perfect", "You Can Finally Meet My Mom", "My Way", "The Song Remains the Same"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Never Learn Not to Love", "Sacrifice", "Can't Help Falling in Love", "Dreamlover"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Try Sleeping With a Broken Heart", "Funny DJ", "Unchained Melody", "Diamonds"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["I Have Nothing", "Save Me", "Experiencia religiosa", "Blue Suede Shoes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Don't Judge Me", "Bug Hunt (Noisia remix)", "Le Ja Tu Mujhe", "Suspicious Minds"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Butterflyz", "Feels Good at First", "Blurred Lines", "Love Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Monster", "In My Room", "Separate Ways", "Last Dollar (Fly Away)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["The Wonder of You", "Song for You", "My Name Is", "Kanday Utay"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["We've Got It Goin' On", "American Trilogy", "Ride Home", "One"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Slut Like You", "Don't Stop 'Til You Get Enough (album version)", "When the Levee Breaks", "Always on My Mind (alternate Take 2)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Family Portrait", "Listen", "Did It on\u2019em", "Anyplace Is Paradise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["I Wish", "Open Arms", "Inevitable", "Landslide"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Moscas en la Casa", "Have a Nice Day (album version)", "Sparks", "Let's Get Away From It All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Piya (remixed by DJ Suketu)", "Heartbeat", "I Want to Hold Your Hand", "Ojos As\u00ed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Las de la Intuici\u00f3n", "I Look to You", "Something Happened on the Way to Heaven", "Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Jaoon Kahan", "Si Te Vas", "Aamde Mustafa Marhaba", "Body Count"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Ava Adore", "The One", "Hum Kis Gaali Ja (Dance Mix)", "Underneath Your Clothes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Made In the USA", "Give Your Heart a Break", "I Love You O Sayyoni", "Gypsy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Mohabbat Dil Ka Sakoon", "Girlfriend", "I Don't Miss You at All", "Addicted to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Aaj Mausam Bada Beimann Hai (Today the Weather Plays Tricks on Me)", "Mann Ki Lagan", "No", "Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["I Will Always Love You", "Nobody's Home", "I Love You", "Give It Up to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Who Am I Living For?", "Drops of Jupiter", "What the Hell", "D\u00eda de Enero"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Love the Way You Lie", "Grade 8", "Hey Daddy (Daddy's Home)", "Hay Amores"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Now That I've Seen Her", "Hello", "Thrift Shop", "Whenever Wherever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["I Love the Lord", "You", "Tu", "Pehli Nazar Mein"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Raabta (Night In Motel)", "Take Me There", "Make You Feel My Love", "She Wolf"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Young Forever", "As I Am (intro)", "Je l'aime \u00e0 Mourir", "Send It On"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["The Movie in My Mind", "Confrontation", "Waka Waka (Esto es \u00c1frica) (K-mix)", "Guzarish"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["La Tortura (alternate Spanglish version)", "Last First Kiss", "Hate That I Love You", "Country Girl (Shake It for Me)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["My Dilemma", "Mere Naseeb Mein (Naseeb)", "Show Me", "Antes de las seis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["\"Can You Feel the Love Tonight (from \"\"The Lion King\"\")\"", "Tu Mohabbat Hai (remixed by DJ Suketu)", "Billie Jean", "Rabiosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Hips Don't Lie (feat. Wyclef Jean)", "I Can't Sleep Baby (If I)", "Goodnight Goodnight", "Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Tailgate Blues", "Live Like You Were Dying", "Heavy Metal Lover", "Lo Hecho Est\u00e1 Hecho"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Superstar", "Loba", "Anywhere For You", "Fireman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Old & Crazy", "Did It Again", "U Remind Me", "Lay All Your Love on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Do You Remember", "Sale el sol", "Where We Land", "Who Says"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Fuel", "Eye", "Antologia", "Feels Good at First"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shakira?", "answers": ["Who Am I Living For?", "Prayin' for Daylight", "Loca", "As Long as You Love Me (radio version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Tees Maar Khan", "Keep Holding On", "Hummingbird Heartbeat", "Gorilla"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Innocence", "All I Want for Christmas", "Too Much Love Will Kill You", "I Feel for You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Red Camaro", "Bounce", "Kahin Deep Jale Kahin Dil", "Complicated (Tom Lord-Alge mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Slipped Away", "Duaa", "I'm Your Baby Tonight", "Chhod De Sari Duniya"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Climax", "I Need Love", "The Man in Black", "My Happy Ending"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Someday (I Will Understand)", "Girl on Fire (Inferno version)", "Roman\u2019s Revenge", "Remember When"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Runaway", "Unbroken", "Hate That I Love You", "He Won't Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Heartbreak Hotel", "Strawberry Swing", "Smile", "Drowning"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Coca Cola Braunu", "Bangarang", "The Best Damn Thing", "Satisfy My Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Secret", "I'm with You", "Thinking of You", "Russian Roulette"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Ennoda Laila", "How Can You Mend A Broken Heart", "Here Is to Never Growing Up", "Mellon Collie and the Infinite Sadness"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Thank You for Loving Me", "What the Hell", "Crazy Love", "Bad Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Brooklyn Go Hard", "The Way You Look Tonight:", "Goodbye", "Teach U A Lesson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Alice (extended version)", "Unbroken", "She Ain\u2019t You", "I Surrender"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Nobody's Home", "Smack That", "Because You Loved Me", "St. Patrick's Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Viva La Vida", "I Will Be", "You Are", "Show Me What You Got"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Twist and Shout", "Things I'll Never Say", "California Gurls", "Panjaban Theme"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Beautiful Goodbye", "My Life", "Black Star", "Love in Vain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Stars Dance", "Trust Issues", "Ride Home", "Bad Reputation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Lucky Strike", "Gimme That", "Hakuna Matata", "Tomorrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["You Drive Me Crazy", "Everybody Hurts", "Hiding My Heart", "Boys 'Round Here (feat. Pistol Annies)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Don't Tell Me", "Remember the Time", "Fifteen", "Wake Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Orange Blossom Special", "Mama's Song", "Black Ice", "I Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Do You Know? (The Ping Pong Song)", "Wish You Were Here", "Kasam Khake Kaho", "Strawberry Swing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Knockin' on Heaven's Door", "Nothing Even Matters", "Ten Times Crazier", "Butterflyz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Time Is on My Side", "God Only Knows (live)", "Bottoms Up", "Everything Back But You (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Be Good to Yourself", "Sk8er Boi", "Jackson", "Could You Be Loved"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Girlfriend", "Saanson Ne", "Last of the American Girls", "Why Georgia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["End of Time", "Jump", "Hung Up", "When You're Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Windows Down", "She's a Rainbow", "Cowboy Casanova", "Hot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Losing Grip", "She Don't Like the Lights", "Why Don't You Love Me (MK Ultra club)", "Made In the USA"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["I've Got You Under My Skin", "Better Left Unsaid", "All-American Girl", "Ankh Ladake"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["I Can't Sleep Baby (If I)", "Tere Bin", "The First Noel", "Ava Adore"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Beer in Mexico", "True Colours", "Starts With Goodbye", "Moscas en la Casa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Southern Voice", "There's a Place for Us", "Stray Heart", "Satisfy You (feat. Puff Daddy)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Got 2 Be Down (feat. Faith Evans)", "Wide Awake", "Tere Bina", "Whenever You Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Before He Cheats", "Whataya Want From Me", "Remember December", "Underneath Your Clothes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Maine Payal Hai Chhankai", "Inside Your Heaven", "Sun Rabba", "Fashion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Diamonds", "Unbroken", "You da One", "Just a Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Moneytalks", "Never Gonna Leave This Bed", "Just Want You to Know", "So Small"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Give It Up to Me", "Shoot to Thrill", "Temporary Home", "Mere Mehboob Qayamat Hogi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Beauty and a Beat", "You Don't Know My Name", "Bullet With Butterfly Wings", "Two Black Cadillacs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Home Sweet Home", "Don't", "Don't Stop Me Now", "White Privilege"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Pendu Jatt", "Wherever I May Roam", "Blown Away", "Begin Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["She Thinks My Tractor's Sexy", "The Way You Make Me Feel", "My Way (live)", "Do You Hear What I Hear"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Yeh Jo Halki Halki Khumariya", "Wasted", "Hard as a Rock", "Wish You Were Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Tere Bin", "She", "Someday When I Stop Loving You", "Aaja We Mahiya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Good Girl", "You Can't Always Get What You Want", "My Happy Ending", "Warning Sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Don't Forget to Remember Me", "Birthday", "Up All Night", "I Won't Apologize"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Cowboy Casanova", "I'd Give My Life for You", "Gypsy", "Your Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Words", "Last Name", "Renegade", "Superstar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Bad Girls", "In Repair", "Roc Boys (And the Winner Is)...", "Remind Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["I Told You So", "A Place for My Head", "Stand Up", "Mood Kharaab"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["See You Again", "Rabba Ve Mera Yaar Modh De", "Forgotten", "The Thing About Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Por amarte", "Nights on Broadway", "Ever Ever After (record version)", "Luna"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Can You Hear Me", "Mama's Song", "Gummi From Bom Bom Bay", "Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Already Gone", "Jesus Take the Wheel", "Hero", "Still They Ride"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Suspicious Minds", "I'll Stand by You", "Imagine", "Le Premier Pas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Ehsaan Tera Hoga Mujh Par", "Good in Goodbye", "The Everlasting Now", "Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Move On", "Do You Think About Me", "Fool That I Am", "She's My Kind of Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Ordinary Girl", "One Piece at a Time", "When You're Gone", "Look At Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Carrie Underwood?", "answers": ["Falling Into You", "Bounce", "Deewana Hoke Hum (Jan)", "Undo It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Space Bound", "Nai Reina", "You Really Got Me", "Phoolan Ka Taron Ka"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["The Catalyst", "Ol' Red", "I Found Someone", "Amplifier"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Ring My Bells", "Play Hard", "You're the Devil in Disguise", "Aaja We Mahiya"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Pata Chalgea", "Inconsolable", "The Real Slim Shady", "Be Like You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Nazar", "Bless the Broken Road", "This'll Be My Year", "I Want to Know What Love Is"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["40 Pra", "Moving Mountains", "Jaoon Kahan", "Love Somebody"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["International Love", "Chaar Dina Ki", "Kokomo", "The American Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Kal Ho Na Ho (Kal Ho Na Ho)", "Tired of Being Sorry", "Cab", "Superstar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Home", "Show Me", "Satisfya", "Picture to Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["What Have I Done?", "Here", "Saving All My Love For You", "Chak Glass"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Express Yourself", "Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "Feeling Good", "My Way (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Strawberry Bubblegum", "Saathiya", "Change My Mind", "Peli Waar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["400 Years", "Ghetto", "True Colors", "Hey Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Unbroken", "Bewafa", "Never Again", "Deewana Tera"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["It's Not Right but It's Okay", "Girl on Fire (Inferno version)", "Only Girl (in the World)", "Qott Ghusian Da"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Soul To Squeeze", "Feeling That Way", "Schei\u00dfe (DJ White Shadow Mugler)", "Bounce Billo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Imran Khan?", "answers": ["Feeling Good", "Gummy Bear Instrumental", "Lying From You", "Gora Gora Rang (feat. Mr Probz)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["When I Need You", "Intuition (feat. Eric Bellinger)", "Rabba", "Last Night on Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Yeh Jo Halki Halki Khumariya", "Believe in Me", "Stop This Train", "Sk8er Boi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["You're My Only Shorty", "Always Be My Baby", "Jaane Ya Ali Ali Ali", "Against All Odds (Take A Look At Me Now)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Koi Humdum Na Raha", "Rabba Main Toh Mar Gaya Oye (Rahat)", "I Can\u2019t Tell You Why", "Batdance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Me and My Gang", "Free", "Yaar Da Makaan", "Starships"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["How Long", "Free Fallin'", "Jag Jeondeyan de Mele", "B-Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Sanu Ik Pal Chain Na Aave", "Bridge of Light", "Never Say Goodbye", "Christmas Tree"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Bichdann", "Iridescent", "Redemption Song (Band Version) Very Rare", "Dark"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Battery", "Losing My Way", "All the Time", "Main Jahaan Rahoon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Angels Cry", "Don't Rain on My Parade", "Set Fire To The Rain", "Kanday Utay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["My Old Friend", "See You Again", "Mere Dil Ki Duniya Mein", "12 Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Dil To Bachcha Hai", "Witchcraft", "Radio (Sir Spyro remix)", "Chasing Pavements"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Tere Mast Mast Do Nain", "Thanimayil", "Girls Just Wanna Have Fun", "Chaska"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["I Miss You", "Home", "Rabba Ve Mera Yaar Modh De", "Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Everything", "Mera Rang De Basanti", "Shouldn't Come Back", "Nazar Se Nazar Tum"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Say", "What Makes You Beautiful", "Love You Unconditionally", "Jiya Dhadak Dhadak Jaye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Charkha", "Never Been Hurt", "Mohabbat Dil Ka Sakoon", "Pon de Replay"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Back Where I Come From", "Stir It Up", "4 Minutes", "Teri Ore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Kill the DJ", "Jaoon Kahan", "I Wanna Be Your Lover", "Mar Jani Jhanjar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["I Love You", "That's Why God Made the Radio", "Daydreamin'", "Zindagi Ye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Tere Bina (Indian)", "Going to California", "You're the Devil in Disguise", "Michelle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Chillin", "Aamde Mustafa Marhaba", "Vaishnav Jan To Tene Kahiye", "Abhi Mujh Main Kahin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Bewafa", "Allah Hoo", "One", "The Day Before You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["If Today Was Your Last Day", "Main Tenu", "Elton John", "Til Kingdom Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["Cry Me a River", "Remember December", "Funhouse", "Kisi Roz Milo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rahat Fateh Ali Khan?", "answers": ["These are the Days of Our Lives", "Kiss and Tell (Bonus Track)", "Mann Ki Lagan", "Arrival"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Whataya Want From Me", "This Ain't a Love Song", "Say Goodbye", "Back in Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Yeh Jo Halki Halki Khumariya", "Bridge of Light", "Daylight", "Sunday Morning Coming Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Blue", "Beam Me Up", "Butterfly", "21 Guns"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["What I've Done", "Anytime", "Ponmeri", "I Don't Believe You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Burn It to the Ground", "Starfish and Coffee", "Raise Your Glass", "No Leaf Clover"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["True Love", "Bye Bye", "Alone", "Back That Azz Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Shadow Days", "Like Money", "Nobody Knows", "You'll Never Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["A Kind of Magic", "One of the Boys", "There Goes My Baby", "F**kin' Perfect"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Diamonds", "Try", "Heart Attack", "Safe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["After All These Years", "Dear Mr. President (From I'm Not Dead Live - Wembley Arena)", "The City", "The Rain Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Run", "Creeping Death", "Again", "Disappear"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Rumour Has It", "U + Ur Hand", "Osito Gummy Bear (Mexican)", "Livin' on a Prayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Stupid Girls", "Kaatu Vazhi", "Funky Monks", "Yakeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Scary Bolly Dub", "I Just Wanna Love U (Give It to Me)", "Funhouse", "Enfant de L'homme"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Just Like a Pill", "Make U Love Me", "A Thousand Years", "Lemme See"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Be True to Your School", "Please Don't Leave Me", "Saturday Night", "Are You Ready"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Hot 'n' Cold", "Blow Me (One Last Kiss)", "Angreji Beat", "Apologize"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)", "Outlaw", "Encore", "Family Portrait"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Invisible", "Never Say Never", "Are We All We Are", "Mayberry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Pehli Nazar Mein", "Love", "There You Go", "Yaad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Beauty and a Beat", "Before He Cheats", "How Will I Know", "Trouble"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["She's a Rainbow", "Easy Lover (duet with Phill Collins)", "Kyun Chor Gaye Rastay", "Walk of Shame"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["The Truth About Love", "Strangers in the Night", "Teach U A Lesson", "(Ghost) Riders in the Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Enfant de L'homme", "Just Give Me a Reason", "Wait Til You See My Smile", "Alone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Sober", "Shine", "Little Red Corvette", "The World's Greatest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Get The Party Started", "Naturally", "Believe It or Not", "Get Over It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["In the Closet", "God Is a DJ", "Good Vibrations", "Yaad"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Little Girl", "Glitter in the Air", "Break The Ice", "Honky Tonk Women"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["I'm Every Woman", "Bewafa", "Slut Like You", "Piano"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Who Knew", "I Like It That Way", "Dolna", "Through the Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["All at Once", "Million Dolla Baby", "So What", "Tere Liye"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Pink?", "answers": ["Uska Hi Banana", "Basket Case", "Don't Let Me Get Me", "Tu Mohabbat Hai (remixed by DJ Suketu)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Sathiyon", "Together", "Pretty Maids All In A Row", "Highway Don't Care"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Ek Ladki Bheegi Bhaagi Si", "Madhuban Mein Radhika Nache", "Scar Tissue", "Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Mere Mitwa Mere Meet Re", "Sure Be Cool If You Did", "The Beginning Is the End Is the Beginning", "Mean"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["O Duniya Ke Rakhwale", "Cherub Rock", "If I Let You Go", "Dreaming With a Broken Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["A Beautiful World", "Tum Mujhe Yun Bhula Na Paoge", "If It's Love", "Love in This Club"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Dono Ne Kiya Tha", "Payphone", "S.O.S.", "I Love You O Sayyoni"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Ehsaan Tera Hoga Mujh Par", "Saajna (unplugged)", "Peli Waar", "Defying Gravity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Flying Without Wings", "Dancing Queen", "Maula", "Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Just the Way You Are", "Suhani Raat Dhal Chuki", "Lollipop", "When You Love a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Born to Make You Happy", "Girl From Ipanema", "Seasons in the Sun", "Abhi Na Jaao Chhod Kar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Pal Pal Teri Yaad", "Do You Think About Me", "Badan Pe Sitare (Prince)", "Somebody to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["\"Rascacielo (\"\"Skyscraper\"\" Spanish Version)\"", "Stupid Girls", "Chal Ud Jaa Re Panchi", "Papa Don't Preach"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Jamming", "Yakeen", "La Isla Bonita", "Maine Puchha Chand Se (Abdullah)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Superman", "Birthday", "Aaj Mausam Bada Beimann Hai (Today the Weather Plays Tricks on Me)", "Halo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Circle the Drain", "Come Wake Me Up", "Likhe Jo Khat Tujhe", "Chillin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Yara Seeli Seeli", "I Told You So", "Ordinary Girl", "Chahonga Mein Tujhe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Dil Ka Bhanwar Kare Pukar", "Aanewala Pal Janewala Hai", "Everything's Not Lost", "Dangerous"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["O Bekhabar", "Touch Too Much", "Tere Husn Ki Kya", "Autumn Leaves"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Do You Think I'm Sexy", "Yeh Duniya Agar Mil Bhi Jaye To", "That's What It's Made For", "Who Made Who"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Superstar", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)", "Jab Jab Phool Khile: Pardesiyon Se Na Ankhiyan Milana", "Gravity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Lyin' Eyes", "Yeh Duniya Yeh Mehfil", "Total Eclipse of the Heart", "Viva La Vida"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Taarif Karun Kya Uski (From Kashmir Ki Kali)", "Kootthu Onnu", "In the End", "Do You Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mohammed Rafi?", "answers": ["Winner at a Losing Game", "She Thinks My Tractor's Sexy", "We Rode in Trucks", "Chaudhvin Ka Chand Ho"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["You Can't Hurry Love", "Shakin Hands", "Baby I\u2019m a Star", "When I Look at You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Meet Virginia", "Start All Over", "LoveStoned/I Think She Knows (interlude)", "Separate Ways"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Unbroken", "Pop That", "Open Arms", "The Climb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["The Scientist", "Robot", "Take It All", "Lucky (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Nobody's Perfect", "Don't Rain on My Parade", "Phir Mohabbat", "Le Premier Pas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Who Owns My Heart", "Off That", "Jam", "Better Than I Used to Be"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Fly on the Wall", "Old & Crazy", "The Call of Ktulu", "Sexy Ladies/Let Me Talk to You (prelude)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Amazing Grace", "A Woman's Worth", "Let's Get Crazy", "Aeroplane"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Here Is to Never Growing Up", "Hot", "I Hope You Find It", "Muzzle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Party in the U.S.A.", "My Life", "Intuition (feat. Eric Bellinger)", "Ramble On"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["We Don't Care", "Can't Be Tamed", "Small Bump", "Mann Ka Radio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["I Miss You", "Aadat (Deep Blue version)", "Aha Aha", "Innocence"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Big Night", "Wada Na Tod", "Hoedown Throwdown", "I'll Be Alright Without You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["7 Things", "Southern Girl", "How Can You Mend A Broken Heart", "Smooth Criminal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Telephone", "Brain Stew", "Moment of Clarity", "Stay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Dream", "Arrival", "Quiz\u00e1s", "Wing$"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["See You Again", "Gravity", "Miss You", "Beast of Burden"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["This Is Us", "Right Here", "All Around The World (featuring Ludacris)", "Something Happened on the Way to Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["I'll Always Remember You", "If I Could Turn Back the Hands of Time", "Can't Help Falling in Love", "Rabiosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["I Like It", "Roop Tera Mastana", "Girls Just Wanna Have Fun", "It's Me Bitches (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Skin (Sarabeth)", "I'm with You", "True Friend", "American Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["If We Were a Movie", "Man in the Mirror", "O Duniya Ke Rakhwale", "The World's Greatest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Manzilen Apni Jagah Hain", "If Everyone Cared", "Broken-Hearted Girl", "Supergirl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["You're Gonna Make Me Lonesome When You Go", "One Love / People Get Ready", "Stupid Hoe", "Thank You for Loving Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Ordinary Girl", "Trouble", "Magic", "Ahista Ahista"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Kikli Kalerdi", "Numb", "Send It On", "Look At Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Nothing Like Us", "DJ Got Us Fallin' in Love", "Don't Make Me", "You'll Always Find Your Way Back Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Show Me The Meaning of Being Lonely", "I Learned From You", "Doing It Wrong", "Next to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Let's Do This", "High Hills", "Start Me Up", "Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["The Best of Both Worlds (2009 Movie mix)", "In Your Atmosphere", "Don't Rain on My Parade", "Ashley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Jesus of Suburbia", "Close Your Eyes", "One in a Million", "American Idiot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["You Don't Know", "Not Even the King", "Bad Reputation", "Mere Khwabon Mein (Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Piya O Re Piya", "Massachusetts", "Like You'll Never See Me Again", "Clarity"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["I'll See You Again", "What I've Done", "Girl on Fire (Inferno version)", "22"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Teenage Love Affair", "Welcome to the Farm", "Write Your Name", "Numb"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Ruby Tuesday", "Tere Chehre Pe", "Butterflyz", "Guide: Gaata Rahe Mera Dil"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Karma", "Cherish", "Jive Talkin'", "Aye Mere Watan Ke Logon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Young Girls", "Turn Your Lights Down Low", "A Woman's Worth", "Mannequin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["I Started a Joke", "Un-Thinkable (I'm Ready)", "Try and Love Again", "I Would"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["All at Once", "Vipassana", "Fire We Make", "Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["You Don't Know My Name", "White Walls", "Smile", "Complicated"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Mann Ki Lagan", "Doesn't Mean Anything", "Speedin'", "Abhi Mujh Main Kahin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Run", "Do You Think I'm Sexy", "Fallin'", "Last Name"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Dirty Diana", "Runaway", "When It's Time", "Girlfriend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Diary", "Norwegian Wood", "Who's That Girl", "Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Tears Always Win", "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me", "Like a Champion", "Faint"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Wouldn't It Be Nice", "Fix You (edit)", "Try Sleeping With a Broken Heart", "Tum Dil Ki Dhadkan Mein"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Magical", "The Lemon Song", "Wait Til You See My Smile", "The Cowboy in Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Who's Lovin' You", "Gora Gora Rang (feat. Mr Probz)", "Tees Maar Khan", "The Thing About Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["That's Why I'm Here", "Drive By", "Superwoman", "Forgot About Dre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Be Intehaan", "Brand New Me", "Come Together", "You're Gonna Make Me Lonesome When You Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["You Know It's Christmas", "You Remind Me", "For Those About To Rock (We Salute You)", "Streets of New York (City Life)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Pretty Little Ditty", "Rapture", "Let There Be Rock", "That's Why I'm Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Lay Your Hands on Me", "As I Am (intro)", "Bush Song", "Funny Bear (Good Night mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)", "I Will Make the Darkness Light", "Cowboy Boots", "These Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["New Day", "Defying Gravity", "City Is Ours", "Do You Know? (The Ping Pong Song)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Wouldn't It Be Nice", "Right by My Side", "When It's All Over", "B.E.A.T."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Renegade", "Chandaniya (Lori Lori)", "No One", "Kyoto"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Hey Girl", "Soledad", "Put It in a Love Song", "Piya O Re Piya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["That's How Strong My Love Is", "There You Go", "Black Star", "Irresistible"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Come Together", "Eleanor Rigby", "Freestyle", "If I Ain't Got You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Alicia Keys?", "answers": ["Quit Playin' Games", "Old Blue Chair", "Across the Universe", "Distance and Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele", "The One", "Beautiful People", "Umrao Jaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Through the Rain", "Christmas (Baby Please Come Home)", "Another Round (explicit version)", "Aamde Mustafa Marhaba"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["The Ruler's Back", "Please Come Home for Christmas", "Easy", "Ready"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["A Hard Day\u2019s Night", "When All Is Said and Done", "As Your Friend", "I Will Be"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Melt My Heart to Stone", "Papercut (remix)", "Government Hooker", "Celebration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Should\u2019ve Kissed You", "One Time", "Orange Blossom Special", "Nazar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Sweet Love", "All the Man That I Need", "All Over Again", "Inevitable"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Battery", "Deuces", "Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites (Zedd remix)", "Easy Skanking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Promise", "Wall to Wall", "Candle in the Wind", "When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Freakshow", "Say Goodbye", "Stay Stay Stay", "I Need You Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Fool That I Am", "Dani California", "Kiss Kiss", "Scary Bolly Dub"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Right by My Side", "More Than This", "Mere Dil Ki Duniya Mein", "See You Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Tragedy", "Save You Tonight", "Take It to the Head", "Ek Ajanabee Haseena Se"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Dosed", "Picture to Burn", "Take You Down", "The Lady Is a Tramp"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Sometimes It Snows in April", "Under The Bridge", "Run It!", "Schoolin' Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Words", "You", "Shattered", "Woh Lamhe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Painting Pictures", "Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)", "Otis", "2012"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Don't Wake Me Up", "The Boys", "Can U Believe", "Bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Last of the American Girls", "Sunday Morning", "Fine China", "If I Were a Carpenter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Firework", "Aamde Mustafa Marhaba", "Honeymoon Avenue", "Turn Up the Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Someday When I Stop Loving You", "Mera Jeevan Kora Kagaz", "Knockout", "Don't Judge Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Keep You Much Longer", "You Can Finally Meet My Mom", "I Can Only Imagine", "I Started a Joke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["In Repair", "Something Like That", "I Can Transform Ya", "New Divide"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Run to You", "Fire We Make", "Gimme That", "Send It On"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["The Way I Am", "She Ain\u2019t You", "Wake Me Up When September Ends", "Who Owns My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Wasted Time", "Talk", "Next to You", "Chhod De Sari Duniya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Cabron", "Delirious", "Poppin'", "Strangers Like Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["First Love Song", "Talking To The Moon (Acoustic)", "Funeral for a Friend / Love Lies Bleeding", "Yeah 3X"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["All Back", "Jesus of Suburbia", "Suhani Raat Dhal Chuki", "We Don't Care"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Bullet With Butterfly Wings", "Function (remix)", "Big Night", "One Less Lonely Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Title Song", "Fall (Live At the Bedford)", "Forever", "A New Day Has Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Umrao Jaan", "International Love", "Here Is to Never Growing Up", "All I Have to Give"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["The Song Remains the Same", "We Will Rock You (Digital Remastered)", "\"Can You Feel the Love Tonight (from \"\"The Lion King\"\")\"", "Bring On the Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Goodbye Yellow Brick Road", "One Thing", "Hero (MetroMix)", "My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Girls Just Wanna Have Fun", "Cough Syrup", "Viva La Vida", "Nikita"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Drown", "Slow Wind", "Elton John", "Lucky (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Like Toy Soldiers", "Going to California", "All I Want for Christmas", "Philadelphia Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Summerboy", "Beautiful Goodbye", "Heartbreaker", "Hello Hello (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["I Would", "Candle in the Wind", "Maine to Khadi Chhat Ke Upar", "Nice & Slow"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Satan", "The One", "It Seems Like You're Ready", "L O V E"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Don't", "Animals", "The Ocean", "Sorry Seems To Be The Hardest Word"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Mere Naseeb Mein (Naseeb)", "Goodbye", "Funeral for a Friend / Love Lies Bleeding", "What Do You Got?"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["La La Land", "Circle of Life (The Lion King)", "Suhani Raat Dhal Chuki", "When a Woman's Fed Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Miss Me", "Phir Mohabbat", "Bounce Billo", "Your Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Curse of Indra", "Next to You", "Your Body Is a Wonderland", "Blessed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["I Feel for You", "Hakuna Matata", "Heaven for Everyone", "Head Banger (feat. Escape)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["The Other Side (Feat. Cee Lo Green And B.o.B)", "Here Comes the Sun", "Tiny Dancer", "U Saved Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Les Mis\u00e9rables", "Candle in the Wind 1997", "Beautiful Liar (Freemasons remix)", "Chandaniya (Lori Lori)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Saturday Night's Alright (for Fighting)", "Don't Stop Believin' (Glee Cast version)", "Blown Away", "Farewell and Goodnight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Faithfully", "Pal Pal Teri Yaad", "Kaatu Vazhi", "Don't Go Breaking My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Your Body's Callin'", "It's All Up to You", "Money Make Her Smile", "Bennie and the Jets"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Something About the Way You Look Tonight", "Hero (MetroMix)", "Beer in Mexico", "New York Mining Disaster 1941"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Crocodile Rock", "Forever", "Na Na Na", "Smooth Criminal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Big Gun", "I Want It That Way (single version)", "Patteya Geya", "Circle of Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["The More I Drink", "Spicks and Specks", "Kaatu Vazhi", "Sacrifice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me", "Americano", "Trouble", "Where Them Girls At"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Don't Be Cruel", "The Edge of Glory", "I Want Love", "409"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Hole in My Head", "Skyline Pigeon", "Those Shoes", "Mere Khwabon Mein (Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["No Idea", "Again", "Million Dolla Baby", "I Just Can't Wait to Be King"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Don't Make Me", "Words", "If U Seek Amy", "I Guess That's Why They Call It the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Holiday", "Ignition", "The Last Song", "I Wish"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["A Hard Day\u2019s Night", "Daniel", "Forever", "I Still"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Elton John?", "answers": ["Summer Love", "Obsessed", "Massive Attack", "I'm Still Standing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Saving All My Love For You", "I Have a Dream", "Norwegian Wood", "Hard to Say I'm Sorry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["All the Man That I Need", "Started from the Bottom", "End of Time", "The Last Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Show Me", "Do You Think I'm Sexy", "Forever", "I Love the Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["All at Once", "The Catalyst", "St. Patrick's Day", "Criminal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["White Walls", "I Was Here", "When You Believe (From the Prince of Egypt)", "Fernando"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Greatest Love of All", "Sun Is Shinning", "Little Lady", "Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain", "When Doves Cry", "Treasure", "El Guardaespaldas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Cry Me a River", "Surfin' Safari", "So Emotional", "Drinkin' Beer and Wastin' Bullets"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Crawling", "Crush", "'Till I Collapse", "I'm Every Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Never Say Goodbye", "Stay", "It's Not Right but It's Okay", "I Want to Hold Your Hand"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Natalie", "Abhi Mujh Main Kahin", "I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)", "Thaazhampoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Shot for Me", "Fireman", "Run to You", "Wasted"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["I Look to You", "To Love Somebody", "Breakfast in Bed", "I Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Try It on My Own", "Bottoms Up", "Could I Have This Kiss Forever", "Yeh Kya Hua"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Sweet Love", "See You Again", "Live to Tell", "I'm Your Baby Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Let\u2019s Go Crazy", "Didn't We Almost Have It All", "Tera Surroor", "Cold Coffee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Jesus Loves Me", "Home", "Soldiers", "Ab Mujhe Raat Din"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["I Have Nothing", "Just Want You to Know", "Mere Naseeb Mein (Naseeb)", "Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["International Love", "I Believe in You and Me", "Batdance", "Two Black Cadillacs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Duaa", "Queen of the Night", "Twist and Shout", "Right on Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Million Dollar Bill", "Stuck in the Moment", "Ordinary Girl", "Runaway"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Thinking About You", "Off That", "Fashion", "Don't Forget To Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["He Ain't the Leavin' Kind", "Shut Up and Drive", "I Will Always Love You", "Sad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["His Eye Is On The Sparrow", "Off the Chain", "Lag Ja Gale Se Phir", "Spotlight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Parler \u00e0 mon p\u00e8re", "Something About the Way You Look Tonight", "I Didn't Know My Own Strength", "Te amo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Playboys of the Southwestern World", "How Will I Know", "Don't You Remember", "Savin' Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Thinking of You", "Lost One", "Off the Chain", "One Moment In Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Aanewala Pal Janewala Hai", "Resurrection (Axwell's Recut Club Version) / Paradise", "Step by Step", "Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Close Your Eyes", "My Love Is Your Love", "I Miss You", "Por amarte"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Where Do Broken Hearts Go", "One Night", "Bicycle Race", "Tum Dil Ki Dhadkan Mein"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Count on Me", "Summer Love", "Sweet Love", "Count on You (feat. Jordin Sparks)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Whitney Houston?", "answers": ["Miracle", "Forever", "Say", "Experiencia religiosa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falak Shabir?", "answers": ["Born and Raised", "Saajna (unplugged)", "Hips Don't Lie (feat. Wyclef Jean)", "God's Gonna Cut You Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Falak Shabir?", "answers": ["Trenchtown Rock", "Mera Mann Kehne Laga (Reprise)", "Here Is to Never Growing Up", "Lego House"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Mentiroso", "Adore", "Slipping Through My Fingers - Me and I", "Turn Up the Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["I Won't Apologize", "Sun Is Shinning", "Kyun", "Take a Chance on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Roc Boys (And the Winner Is)...", "Our Last Summer", "Last First Kiss", "Thaazhampoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["A Thousand Years", "Never Gonna Be Alone", "The Winner Takes It All", "My Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Fuel", "Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "Does Your Mother Know", "Show Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Incomplete", "Believe", "Something", "Super Trouper"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Otherside", "It Seems Like You're Ready", "Voulez-vous", "Down to Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Numb", "Through the Never", "Love You Like a Love Song", "Waterloo (French)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Hasta ma\u00f1ana", "Livin' on a Prayer", "Have a Drink on Me", "Girls Just Wanna Have Fun"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Make It Rain", "Muskura", "Move On", "SOS"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["O Duniya Ke Rakhwale", "Speedin'", "One of Us", "Billie Jean"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Sometimes (radio edit)", "Alejandro", "Thoia Thoing", "Lay All Your Love on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Without You", "What About Now", "Jaadu Hai Nasha Hai (female)", "On and On and On"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Dive", "Sunday Morning", "I'd Rather Go Blind", "Honey Honey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Inconsolable", "Don't Stop Believin'", "Piya (remixed by DJ Suketu)", "Fernando"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Get Rhythm (feat. The Tennessee Two)", "Personal Jesus", "This Is It", "Move On"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["It's Your Love", "I Can Transform Ya", "Total Eclipse of the Heart", "Thank You for the Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Kuch Is Tarah", "Happy New Year", "Animals", "If I Could Turn Back the Hands of Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Mera Dil Bhi Kitna Pagal Hai", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Stars", "I Have a Dream", "Aap Ki Ankhon Mein"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Electric Feel", "The Name of the Game", "Brown Sugar", "Immigrant Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Chiquitita", "I Learned From You", "She Ain\u2019t You", "Everytime (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Stars", "Dil To Bachcha Hai", "Mamma Mia", "Everything Has Changed (feat. Ed Sheeran)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Get Down", "I'll Always Remember You", "Thinking About You", "The Day Before You Came"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Someday (I Will Understand)", "Eagle", "The World's Greatest", "It's Now or Never"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Computer Blue", "Arrival", "1979", "White Privilege"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Dancing Queen", "We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together", "The Truth About Love", "Bounce Billo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Billie Jean", "The Ocean", "When All Is Said and Done", "Last Call"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by ABBA?", "answers": ["Crocodile Rock", "Gimme! Gimme! Gimme! (A Man After Midnight)", "Locked Up", "Warning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Mirrors", "Bangarang", "Unbroken", "Otherside"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["It", "Snow (Hey Oh)", "Sorority Girl", "Candle in the Wind 1997"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Tiny Dancer", "Dani California", "Heartbeat", "We Can Work It Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Road Trippin'", "Hold My Hand", "You Raise Me Up", "Thank You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["My Friends", "Come Wake Me Up", "I Want You (She's So Heavy)", "Naturally"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Just the Way You Are", "Funky Monks", "Ooh La La", "O Duniya Ke Rakhwale"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Chaudhvin Ka Chand Ho", "I Could Die For You", "Iridescent", "Those Shoes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Thank You for Loving Me", "Californication", "Until It Sleeps", "Incomplete"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Parallel Universe", "Best of My Love", "That\u2019s My Bitch", "Where We Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Can\u2019t You Hear Me Knocking", "Wing$", "Stay Schemin'", "Cabron"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Mama's Song", "Walk of Shame", "Tell Me Baby", "Freestyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Don\u2019t Let Me Down", "Can't Stop", "Show Me", "Yaar Da Makaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Beautiful People", "Any Way You Want It", "Piya (remixed by DJ Suketu)", "Suck My Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Higher Ground", "Who's Crying Now", "Distance and Time", "Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites (Zedd remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Set Fire To The Rain", "Welcome to the Farm", "Around The World", "The Other Side (Feat. Cee Lo Green And B.o.B)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Sweet and Simple", "James Dean", "Dil Jhoom Jhoom", "I Could Have Lied"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Everybody Hurts", "Dosed", "Gora Gora Rang (feat. Mr Probz)", "Yeh Duniya Agar Mil Bhi Jaye To"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Try and Love Again", "The City", "The Zephyr Song", "Are You Ready"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Rain Dance Maggie", "Hair", "Lovers in Japan (acoustic version)", "Better Left Unsaid"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Don't Forget Me", "Troublemaker", "Granddaddy's Gun", "Teenage Dream (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Love Rollercoaster", "Muqaddar Ka Sikandar: O Saathi Re", "This Love", "Lying From You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Bailamos", "Venice Queen", "Both Sides of the Story", "Ehsaan Tera Hoga Mujh Par"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Aaja Ve", "Jesus Take the Wheel", "Hard to Concentrate", "Thinking About You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Eagle", "Daughters", "Scar Tissue", "O Mere Khuda"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Take You Down", "Si Te Vas", "Aeroplane", "Only Girl (in the World)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["By the Way", "Like You'll Never See Me Again", "High School (feat. Lil Wayne)", "Walk of Shame"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["When the Stars Go Blue", "Born and Raised", "This'll Be My Year", "Look Around"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019", "Breaking the Girl", "Surfin USA", "She's My Kind of Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Colours", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "Soul To Squeeze", "I Was Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["En Ti Dej\u00e9 Mi Amor", "Syndicate (Skrillex remix)", "Won't Go Home Without You", "Pretty Little Ditty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Chanda Ki Doli Mai (Chanda Ki Doli)", "Shape of My Heart", "Under The Bridge", "Omnipresence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["A Milli", "She will be loved", "Without Me", "Give It Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Jingle Bells", "A Hard Day\u2019s Night", "Who Says", "Last Night on Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["It's All Up to You", "You're the Devil in Disguise", "Mayberry", "Vision of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["No Love", "Oh Love", "Achha Lagta Hai", "Witchcraft"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Don't", "Last Dollar (Fly Away)", "Rich As Fuck (Feat. 2 Chainz)", "Fly Me to the Moon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["As Tears Go By", "Loca", "Jag Jeondeyan de Mele", "Girl From Ipanema"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Ben", "Let It Snow! Let It Snow! Let It Snow!", "Runaway", "You Know It's Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["The Way You Look Tonight", "Lego House", "Take a Chance on Me", "Say"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["You Don't Know Jack", "Nunca Te Olvidar\u00e9", "White Horse", "High Hopes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Strangers in the Night", "Heal The World", "Eenie Meenie", "I Shot the Sheriff"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Is Kadar Pyar Hai Tumse", "Hollywood Tonight", "Luck Be a Lady"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Something Happened on the Way to Heaven", "The Simpsons Theme", "The Best Is Yet to Come", "Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Moon River", "Tere Chehre Pe", "Count on Me", "Little Things"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)", "Shine", "Do You Think I'm Sexy", "The First Noel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Falling Into You", "It Was a Very Good Year", "Girlfriend", "Hello Hello (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Love and Marriage", "Moments", "Calling All Angels", "Open Arms"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["When I Was Your Man", "Penis Song", "Red Ragtop", "I'm Gonna Live Till I Die"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Bridge of Light", "Sussudio", "I've Got You Under My Skin", "Vision of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Let's Get Away From It All", "Back Where I Come From", "Stranger in Moscow", "I Can't Sleep Baby (If I)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["That's Life", "Open Arms", "Where Them Girls At", "Tera Ishq Bada Teekha"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["To Love Somebody", "Who Made Who", "Kaatu Vazhi", "Come Fly With Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["You're Nobody 'Til Somebody Love You", "Yeh Zindagi Usi Ki Hai", "Shot Through the Heart", "From the Inside"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Jab Se Tumko Dekha Hai Sanam", "You Make Me Feel So Young", "Overboard", "Heart Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Tonight (I'm Lovin' You)", "Next to You", "Wave", "We Made You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Like a Prayer", "Dosed", "For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "I Love Rock'n Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Can U Believe", "Knockout", "It Had to Be You", "I Like It That Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Innuendo", "Take It All", "I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)", "My Way (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Up", "Papers", "Alone", "Blue Moon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Magic", "Take It to the Head", "Kuch Is Tarah", "Cheek to Cheek"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Baby One More Time", "I Love You", "Como Yo Nadie Te Ha Amado", "How Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Lay All Your Love on Me", "Summer Wind (feat. Julio Iglesias)", "Zero", "Still Getting It"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Frank Sinatra?", "answers": ["Kiss Me", "The Lady Is a Tramp", "Naughty Girl", "The Song Remains the Same"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Raabta", "Stop & Erase", "One Time", "Ray of Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Into the Groove", "Bailamos", "Best Thing I Never Had", "Don\u2019t Stay"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Kill EVERYBODY", "Allah Hoo", "Like a Prayer", "A Year Without Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Always", "Who's That Girl", "O Bekhabar", "Naam Hai Tera"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Talk", "Teenage Dream", "Frozen (album version)", "Liquor Store Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Badan Pe Sitare (Prince)", "Melody Fair", "These Days", "Hung Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Nobody Knows", "Piya (remixed by DJ Suketu)", "Girl Gone Wild", "Clocks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Everything's Not Lost", "Unakkum Enakkum", "Please Come Home for Christmas", "American Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Take You", "4 Minutes", "She", "Isaiyarasi (feat. S. Rajeswari & S. Janaki)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Run It!", "LoveGame (album version)", "Future Lovers", "Starfish and Coffee"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Not Even the King", "Give Me All Your Luvin' (Party Rock remix)", "Made In the USA", "Princess of China"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Borderline", "Hole in My Head", "La La Land", "Got Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Moment 4 Life (feat. Drake)", "Vogue", "Dazed and Confused", "Backwards"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["You Should Be Dancing", "Larger Than Life", "Holiday", "Got Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["You da One", "True Blue", "True Colors", "Moonshine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Right In", "Justify My Love", "Natalie", "Si Te Vas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Lo Hecho Est\u00e1 Hecho", "Express Yourself", "Sympathy for the Devil (original)", "Sun Is Shinning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Better Left Unsaid", "One Piece at a Time", "Makes Me Wonder", "Cherish"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Just a Dream", "When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)", "Fuel", "Jump"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Papa Don't Preach", "Call Me Maybe", "Ooh La La", "Pound the Alarm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Larger Than Life", "Thank You for Loving Me", "We Made You", "Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["I've Got You Under My Skin", "Tailgate Blues", "The Everlasting Now", "Sorry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Give It 2 Me", "Wooden Heart", "Drown", "Give a Little More"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Power of Good-Bye (album version)", "Hawaii", "Saanson Ne", "Goodnight Goodnight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Material Girl", "Title Song", "All the Man That I Need", "Snitch"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Summerboy", "Speechless", "Banjo", "Masterpiece"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Crazy for You", "Something Happened on the Way to Heaven", "Get Over It", "Drops of Jupiter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Imagine", "Sober", "Helter Skelter", "Live to Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["Cherub Rock", "La Isla Bonita", "Tell Me Baby", "I Know You're Gonna Be There"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["She Thinks My Tractor's Sexy", "The Thing About Love", "Don't Cry for Me Argentina", "Fight Fire With Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["I Kissed a Girl", "Nights on Broadway", "Like a Virgin", "Here Comes the Sun"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Madonna?", "answers": ["I Can\u2019t Tell You Why", "Run to You", "Bennie and the Jets", "Celebration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Ajnabi Hawaayein Bekrara Bahein", "Death And All His Friends", "The Forgotten", "Erotic City"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Nothing Lasts Forever", "If I Let You Go", "Breakfast Can Wait", "Bleed It Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Schei\u00dfe (DJ White Shadow Mugler)", "Take Me With U", "Through the Never", "In the Closet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Tony Montana", "Black Ice", "Shoot to Thrill", "Delirious"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Somewhere I Belong", "Save the Day", "Vultures", "The Most Beautiful Girl in the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Show Me What You Got", "Tequila Sunrise", "El Guardaespaldas", "The Beautiful Ones"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Gummybear Song", "Can't Be Tamed", "Forever", "Little Red Corvette"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Call Me Maybe", "That's How Strong My Love Is", "Written in the Stars", "Starfish and Coffee"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Take Me There", "Until It Sleeps", "I Wanna Be Your Lover", "Hasta ma\u00f1ana"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Lucky", "If I Was Your Girlfriend", "Bleed", "Cry Me a River"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Without You", "L.A. Boyz (feat. Victoria Justice and Ariana Grande)", "Dil Ka Bhanwar Kare Pukar", "Computer Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["New Power Generation", "Mere Mitwa Mere Meet Re", "Brooklyn Go Hard", "Back To You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Holiday / Boulevard of Broken Dreams", "Slow Dancing in a Burning Room", "Addicted", "When Doves Cry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Saturday Night", "The Celestials", "End of Time", "Controversy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["You Had Me From Hello", "Come", "The Reason", "Autumn Leaves"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Guitar", "Take My Drunk Ass Home", "Naked", "All Too Well"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Rock and Roll Ain\u2019t Noise Pollution", "Part Of Me", "Baby I\u2019m a Star", "Waiting for the End"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Kiss", "On to the Next One", "The Lady Is a Tramp", "Calling All Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Marvin's Room", "Time of Our Life", "Love", "Stone Cold Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Robot", "My Old Friend", "Step in the Name of Love", "The Everlasting Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["That\u2019s My Bitch", "Chelsea Rodgers", "Ride the Lightning", "Little Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Take It to the Limit", "1999 (LP version)", "In the Closet", "It's All Up to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Adore", "Summer Love", "The Song Remains the Same", "Luck Be a Lady"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["You Can Finally Meet My Mom", "Dark", "Meet Virginia", "Bad Romance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down (Duet With Uncle Kracker)", "Encore", "It", "Young Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Batdance", "Don't Rain on My Parade", "All About Lovin' You", "Girlfriend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Nothing Compares 2 U", "The One That Got Away", "Shake That", "That's All She Wrote"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Don\u2019t Let Me Down", "Feel Like a Rock Star", "Sometimes It Snows in April", "If I Ruled the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["I Feel for You", "Alguien soy yo", "Mamma Mia", "Suck My Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Brand New Me", "Holiday", "Purple Rain", "Can't Stop Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Prince?", "answers": ["Badan Pe Sitare (Prince)", "Let\u2019s Go Crazy", "These are the Days of Our Lives", "In Repair"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Truck", "You Can Finally Meet My Mom", "Allah Kare", "Phir Mohabbat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["I Got You", "Hay Amores", "Ask the Lonely", "Anybody Seen My Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["If It's Love", "If U Seek Amy", "A Day in the Life", "Unchained Melody"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Calling All Angels", "Run to You", "Crush", "Personal Jesus"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Kaise Mujhe", "Body Count", "Mermaid", "Thanimayil"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["When I Look to the Sky", "Don't Stop The Music", "As a Blonde", "All at Once"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Marry Me", "Why", "Triumphant (The New Iberican League Radio)", "Til Kingdom Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Drops of Jupiter", "Home", "See You Again", "You Don't Know Jack"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Heavy", "La La Land", "Wake Me Up When September Ends", "Ring Of Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Itt Van A Gumimaci (Hungarian)", "Teach U A Lesson", "It Will Rain", "To Be Loved"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Hips Don't Lie (feat. Wyclef Jean)", "Funky Monks", "Your Body's Callin'", "Imagine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Taken", "Can't Help Falling in Love", "Mississippi", "Fall (Live At the Bedford)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Feels Good at First", "If I Ain't Got You (live)", "Politik", "Perfect"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Ronan", "Starts With Goodbye", "This'll Be My Year", "Pirate Flag"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Boys Boys Boys", "Cab", "Jaan", "Brooklyn Go Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Les Mis\u00e9rables: Bring Him Home", "My Happy Ending", "Meet Virginia", "Smack That"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Saawali Si Raat", "My Happy Ending", "She's on Fire", "Purple Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Runaway", "The American Dream", "Free", "Fire We Make"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Ordinary", "Hummer", "Birthday Cake", "When It's All Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["She Wolf", "50 Ways to Say Goodbye", "How Will I Know", "I'm Counting on You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["The Last Time", "Uptown Girl", "Blind", "Can\u2019t You Hear Me Knocking"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["This Ain't Goodbye", "Runaway Baby", "Make U Love Me", "Vipassana"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Drive By", "Bad Reputation", "Shape of My Heart", "Smile"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Battery", "Stronger (Pablo La Rosa's Tranceformation edit)", "I Want It That Way (single version)", "Sing Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Never Again", "Turn Me On", "Chaudhvin Ka Chand Ho", "Get to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["It Was a Very Good Year", "Pure Imagination", "I'm Still Breathing", "Breakfast in Bed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Let it Out", "Part Of Me", "Drown", "Getaway"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Train?", "answers": ["Bruises", "The Song Remains the Same", "Hey Daddy (Daddy's Home)", "Anyplace Is Paradise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Oorukkoru", "Piya O Re Piya", "You the Boss (album version) (Explicit)", "Good Riddance (Time of Your Life)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Warning Sign", "Irish Celebration", "Cheek to Cheek", "The Forgotten"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Back to Your Heart", "21st Century Breakdown", "Last First Kiss", "Kiss You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Wake Me Up When September Ends", "From the Bottom of My Broken Heart", "Livin' on a Prayer", "Kashmir"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Two Pieces", "Renegade", "Holiday", "Banjo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Heartbreaker", "Minority (album version)", "Famous", "Lonely"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["The Town", "Boulevard of Broken Dreams", "Soma", "Do You Think I'm Sexy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Ashley", "Halfway There", "Apologize", "All Tied Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Holiday", "Brain Stew", "Sing Together", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Tere Husn Ki Kya", "Warning", "The Four Horsemen", "All I Have to Give"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["The Simpsons Theme", "Soma", "One Night", "Wherever I May Roam"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Black Dog", "Holiday / Boulevard of Broken Dreams", "To Love Somebody", "Nothing Even Matters"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["When It's Time", "Naam Hai Tera", "Penis Song", "Could I Have This Kiss Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Nothing Compares 2 U", "Longview", "Hasta ma\u00f1ana", "Hot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Today Was a Fairytale", "East Jesus Nowhere", "Ray of Light", "Te amo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Emotions (Mariah Carey cover)", "The Scientist", "21 Guns", "Soul Survivor"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["What's My Name?", "Funny Bear (Good Night mix)", "Without You", "When I Come Around (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["A Thousand Years", "Is Kadar Pyar Hai Tumse", "Kill the DJ", "Papa Don't Preach"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Aaja Ve", "Green", "I Know You're Gonna Be There", "Basket Case"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Stray Heart", "This Is Us", "A Beautiful World", "Tere Bin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Walking Contradiction", "Faithfully", "Heartbreaker", "Pirate Flag"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["How Can You Mend A Broken Heart", "Be With You", "Last of the American Girls", "Felt Good on My Lips"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["I Got You", "Angry All the Time", "Don't Take the Girl", "She"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Desensitized", "Gold Rush", "Pretty Lil Heart (feat. Lil Wayne)", "Gummi From Bom Bom Bay"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Oh Love", "Bring On the Rain", "What Goes Around.../...Comes Around (interlude)", "She's on Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Tu Jaane Na", "American Idiot", "I Told You So", "I Look to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Aap Ki Ankhon Mein", "On to the Next One", "I Don't Care Anymore", "Know Your Enemy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Jesus of Suburbia", "Roc Boys (And the Winner Is)...", "The Edge of Glory", "Chak Glass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Dosed", "Homecoming: I. The Death of St. Jimmy / II. East 12th St. / III. Nobody Likes You / IV. Rock and Roll Girlfriend / V. We\u2019re Coming Home Again", "My Name Is", "Politik"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Winner at a Losing Game", "The Saints Are Coming", "Tony Montana", "Tiny Dancer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Tera Mera Pyar Amar", "Last Night on Earth", "Smooth Criminal", "Beast of Burden"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Green Day?", "answers": ["Like a Prayer", "Un-Thinkable (I'm Ready)", "Welcome to Paradise", "Livin' on a Prayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Playboys of the Southwestern World", "Right Here", "True Love", "Ten Times Crazier"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["All Around The World (featuring Ludacris)", "Titanic", "The Edge of Glory", "Aston Martin Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Beauty and a Beat", "Soma", "If I Let You Go", "Ignition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["I Would", "Rude Boy", "Victim of Love", "Bananza (Belly Dancer)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Pata Chalgea", "Drivin' Around Song", "She Don't Like the Lights", "Anything But Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Get It Right", "Another Round (explicit version)", "Faint", "Overboard"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Sure Be Cool If You Did", "That Should Be Me", "Ghosts", "Poetic Justice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["He Won't Go", "U Remind Me", "Stuck in the Moment", "Sofa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Beautiful", "Kiss and Tell (Bonus Track)", "Needed Change", "Straight Through My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Something Happened on the Way to Heaven", "Tommie Sunshine\u2019s Megasix Smash-Up", "Time Is on My Side", "Die in Your Arms"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Love on Top", "Hurts Like Heaven", "Fall", "Close Your Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["All About Lovin' You", "Get Off My Cloud", "Baby", "Just to See You Smile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Never Been Hurt", "One Less Lonely Girl", "Liberian Girl", "The Day That Never Comes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["I'm Your Funny Bear (Gelatine club mix)", "Halfway There", "Boyfriend", "Chiquitita"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Born This Way", "One Time", "Oops!...I Did It Again", "It Will Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Brain Stew", "Eenie Meenie", "Fantine's Death", "Saturday Night's Alright (for Fighting)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Now and Then", "Nothing Like Us", "Drunk on You", "Syndicate (Skrillex remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Bad Kids", "Walking Contradiction", "Be Alright", "The American Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Something Happened on the Way to Heaven", "You Save Me", "The Way", "As Long As You Love Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Dangerous", "Never Let You Go", "We've Got It Goin' On", "First of May"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["D\u00eda de Enero", "I Got U", "Love Me", "Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Wipe Your Eyes", "Next to You", "Daydreamer", "Isaiyarasi (feat. S. Rajeswari & S. Janaki)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Forever", "Up", "Marilyn Monroe", "Government Hooker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["You'll Always Find Your Way Back Home", "Tere Husn Ki Kya", "Blue Ocean Floor", "Fa La La"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Harvest Time", "Never Say Never", "Blue Suede Shoes", "Dreaming With a Broken Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Somebody to Love", "Whataya Want From Me", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "A Boy Named Sue"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Headlines", "Hush Little Baby", "A Place for My Head", "Down to Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Meet Virginia", "One Love", "D'Evils", "Faithfully"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Come Wake Me Up", "Favorite Girl (live) (acoustic)", "Radio GaGa", "Should\u2019ve Kissed You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Before He Cheats", "Who's Lovin' You", "Getaway", "Take You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Up All Night", "Moon River", "Wish You Were Here", "Believe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["It's a Beautiful Day", "LoveStoned/I Think She Knows (interlude)", "Rude Boy", "Skin (Sarabeth)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Pour It Up", "Saving All My Love For You", "You", "Didn't We Almost Have It All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Little Honda", "Wayfaring Stranger", "I Look to You", "S.O.S."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Hard", "Entre Deux Mondes", "Husn Di Botel", "Song Cry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Do I", "S & M", "Holiday", "Cough Syrup"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Hammer to Fall", "Lego House", "For Those About To Rock (We Salute You)", "Birthday Cake"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Don't Stop The Music", "Scary Bolly Dub", "Freedom", "We Never Change"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Easy", "Live", "Hawaii", "Take Care"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Yeh Jo Halki Halki Khumariya", "Take A Bow", "Practice", "Marvin's Room"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Gundello Godari", "Don't Cry for Me Argentina", "Candle in the Wind", "Where Have You Been"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Cheers (Drink to That)", "Rabba Ve Mera Yaar Modh De", "Dream", "Inside Your Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Angie", "Immigrant Song", "Words", "Fly (feat. Rihanna)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Hero (MetroMix)", "If Today Was Your Last Day", "Right Now (featuring David Guetta)", "Bye Bye"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Middle of Nowhere", "Gummi From Bom Bom Bay", "You da One", "Sparks Fly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["When You're Looking Like That", "Te amo", "Every Teardrop Is a Waterfall", "Rain Is a Good Thing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["That Should Be Me", "Shut Up and Drive", "Yaar Da Makaan", "All the Man That I Need"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Calling All Angels", "Stayin' Alive", "Love the Way You Lie (piano version)", "Khalbali"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Run This Town", "Wasted", "Dirt Off Your Shoulder", "Sing for the Moment"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Venice Queen", "Hate That I Love You", "Both of Us", "Lucy in the Sky With Diamonds"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Million Dolla Baby", "Wouldn't It Be Nice", "Tere Liye", "Pon de Replay"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Slipped Away", "Warrior", "Only Girl (in the World)", "Oh Yeah"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Charkha", "Brooklyn Go Hard", "Mentiroso", "Rehab"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Wish You Were Here", "Smile", "Diamonds", "Brahms' Lullaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Country Man", "Russian Roulette", "I Was Here", "Adada Vaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["What's My Name?", "Escape", "You Don't Know", "Blackened"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Stay (featuring Mikky Ekko)", "Let's Get Crazy", "Nobody's Home", "Numb"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Clarity", "Man Down", "Aamde Mustafa Marhaba", "Yeh Duniya Agar Mil Bhi Jaye To"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Schoolin' Life", "U.N.I.", "Chal Ud Jaa Re Panchi", "Unfaithful"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Baby I", "Vipassana", "Umbrella (feat. Jay-Z)", "Tere Bin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Baby I", "We Found Love", "Baby", "Paradise"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["What About Now", "Disturbia", "Ramble On", "Tell Me Something I Don't Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rihanna?", "answers": ["What Now", "Who Am I Living For?", "Sing Together", "More Than This"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["God Bless America", "Til Kingdom Come", "I Don't Miss You at All", "Brown Sugar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Fall for Your Type", "Red", "FutureSex/LoveSound", "The Power of the Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["I Know You Know (feat. Cymphonique)", "Live", "Somebody to Love", "Everything Has Changed (feat. Ed Sheeran)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["If I Could Turn Back the Hands of Time", "I Wish", "Immortality", "I Walk The Line"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Pretty Lil Heart (feat. Lil Wayne)", "I Surrender", "Honeymoon Avenue", "Escapar (Escape)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Who Made Who", "S'il suffisait d'aimer", "Let's Get Away From It All", "I Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Til Kingdom Come", "Son of Man", "A New Day Has Come", "Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Til I Forget About You", "Smooth Criminal", "Shine", "I Drove All Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["I Love You", "Kiss Me", "My Name Is", "Save You Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Confrontation", "Brahms' Lullaby", "Jesus Loves Me", "Winner at a Losing Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Feelin' on Yo Booty", "Only the Young", "To Love You More", "Something Like Olivia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Sous le vent (feat. Garou)", "Bed of Roses", "In the Closet", "Never Learn Not to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Gimme Shelter", "City of Hope", "Drunk on You", "Parler \u00e0 mon p\u00e8re"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Ignition", "Falling Down", "So Emotional", "Because You Loved Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["The Prayer", "It's In The Mornin (feat. Snoop Dogg)", "Burning Love", "Burn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Vole", "My Friends", "Get Rhythm (feat. The Tennessee Two)", "Jesus of Suburbia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Ave Maria", "Natalie", "Tujhe Dekha To", "Please Remember Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Sweetest Goodbye", "Kokomo", "Titanic", "Cocaine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Tiny Dancer", "Goodbye's (The Saddest Word)", "Rock n\u2019 Roll (Will Take You to the Mountain)", "Count on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["All by Myself (Spanish version)", "Tere Mast Mast Do Nain", "Sweetest Goodbye", "Apnaa Mujhe Tu Lagaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Don't Rain on My Parade", "Party (feat. Andr\u00e9 3000)", "D'amour ou d'amiti\u00e9", "I Feel for You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Jingle Bells", "Already Gone", "Parallel Universe", "Falling Into You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Miss Me", "When I Need You", "One Night", "To Be Loved"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["The Power of Love", "In the City", "Bump n' Grind", "Pure Imagination"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["When You're Looking Like That", "Jesus of Suburbia", "Na Na Na", "I'm Alive (Humberto Gatica mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Lag Ja Gale", "Si tu te vas", "My Same", "Just Walk Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Ye Ishq Hai", "Naked", "Massive Attack", "Pour que tu m'aimes encore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Beauty and the Beast", "After All", "Know Your Enemy", "The World's Greatest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Alone", "Jailbreak", "Muskura", "Rock and Roll Ain\u2019t Noise Pollution"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["All About Lovin' You", "Last Dollar (Fly Away)", "You Had Me From Hello", "It's All Coming Back to Me Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["Bruises", "Dirty Dancer", "That's The Way It Is", "Someday (I Will Understand)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Celine Dion?", "answers": ["It Was a Very Good Year", "Tell Him", "Bleed", "Kaun Hoon Main"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Crazy for You", "Tera Surroor", "Back Where I Come From", "Hurts Like Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Lovers in Japan (acoustic version)", "To Love Somebody", "Cocaine", "You Can't Hurry Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Yeah 3X", "Justify My Love", "Princess of China", "Satisfy My Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Don't Say Alvida", "Speed of Sound", "Take A Bow", "Why God Why?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["The A Team", "There Goes My Baby", "The Scientist", "Pour que tu m'aimes encore"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Mar Jani Jhanjar", "Eagle", "She Ain\u2019t You", "Sparks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Paradise", "Stupid Hoe", "Waiting in Vain (remix 84)", "Mother's Little Helper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Hook Me Up", "Clocks", "Itsy Bitsy Bikini", "Lighters"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Everything's Not Lost", "Disappear", "Come", "Homecoming: I. The Death of St. Jimmy / II. East 12th St. / III. Nobody Likes You / IV. Rock and Roll Girlfriend / V. We\u2019re Coming Home Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Hometown Glory", "Every Teardrop Is a Waterfall", "Against All Odds (Take A Look At Me Now)", "Daylight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Dolna", "Politik", "No Lie", "I Can Only Imagine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Viva La Vida", "All the Man That I Need", "Lights", "Right on Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Life in Technicolor", "Nothing Like Us", "Strange Clouds", "Numb"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Numb", "Immigrant Song", "Something Like Olivia", "Violet Hill"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["O Re Piya", "Death And All His Friends", "One Moment In Time", "Spanish Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Ur So Gay", "Summer Love/Set the Mood (prelude)", "Daddy's Little Girl", "Shiver"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["You the Boss (album version) (Explicit)", "Cama De Rosas", "Someone Else Calling You Baby", "Trouble"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Us Against the World", "Fire Your Guns", "Bottoms Up", "Tujhe Dekha To"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["My Love Is Your Love", "Charlie Brown", "Prem Bann", "Real Good Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Mirrors", "Sunday Morning", "Strawberry Swing", "You'll Never Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Orange Blossom Special", "Red", "We Never Change", "Innocence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Heartbeat", "Help!", "Kiss", "Yellow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["The Zephyr Song", "Pal Pal Teri Yaad", "Green Eyes", "Lovesong"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["See You Soon", "One Night", "Fernando", "Nobody But Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Major Minus", "Faithfully", "I Can't Sleep Baby (If I)", "I Just Wanna Love U (Give It to Me)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["I Just Can't Wait to Be King", "Why", "The Zephyr Song", "Warning Sign"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["No Worries", "I'll Stand by You (Glee Cast version)", "I'll Be There for You", "Talk"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Yaadan Teriyan", "Jag Jeondeyan de Mele", "Til Kingdom Come", "Start All Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Nari Kathai", "Fix You (edit)", "Session", "Don't Stop The Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Give a Little More", "Lost!", "Oorukkoru", "The Prayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Resurrection (Axwell's Recut Club Version) / Paradise", "Bodies", "Be True to Your School", "I Wish It Would Rain Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Kiss Me", "In My Place", "Let's Get Away From It All", "Goodbye Yellow Brick Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Bounce", "Ten Years Gone", "No Worries", "Paris"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["It's All Coming Back to Me Now", "Immigrant Song", "This Ain't a Love Song", "Chillin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Snow (Hey Oh)", "Somebody's Me", "I Want It That Way (single version)", "Since I've Been Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["My Love (feat. T.I.)", "Lightweight", "Kashmir", "We Weren't Born to Follow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["One Moment In Time", "Tangerine", "Without Me", "4 Minutes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Right Above It", "Please Don't Leave Me", "I Drove All Night", "Rock and Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Kiss My Country Ass", "Return to Sender", "Stairway to Heaven", "The Last Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Bruises", "Hey Hey What Can I Do", "Didn't We Almost Have It All", "All I Ask of You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["One of the Boys", "Over the Hills and Far Away", "1979", "Flying Without Wings"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["We Never Change", "All My Love", "Intro", "I'm Alive (Humberto Gatica mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Happy People", "The Song Remains the Same", "99 Problems", "Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Celebration Day", "Thriller", "Irish Celebration", "Still They Ride"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Fingerprints", "Saathiya", "When the Levee Breaks", "Chillin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Boys 'Round Here (feat. Pistol Annies)", "Rock 'n' Roll", "Believe in Me", "Sorry Seems To Be The Hardest Word"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Can\u2019t You Hear Me Knocking", "Escape", "Going to California", "New Power Generation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Tujhe Dekha To", "D\u2019yer Mak\u2019er", "Popular Song", "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["California Dreaming", "Ramble On", "Crush", "See You Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Samjho Na", "The Ocean", "When I See This Bar", "Love Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Achilles Last Stand", "A Dedication", "Tujh Mein Rab Dikhta Hai", "She Wouldn't Be Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Good Times Bad Times", "D'Evils", "Rehab", "You Don't Know My Name"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["If I Were a Boy", "My Prerogative", "Moneytalks", "Whole Lotta Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Spicks and Specks", "Chelsea Rodgers", "Boys 'Round Here (feat. Pistol Annies)", "Fool in the Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Dazed and Confused", "Heavy Metal Lover", "My Little Girl (From the Motion Picture 'Flicka')", "Do it Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Wipe Your Eyes", "Wild Horses (alternate)", "The Lemon Song", "The Man Comes Around"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Hard to Say I'm Sorry", "The Best Is Yet to Come", "I Can't Quit You Baby", "Promise"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Snow (Hey Oh)", "Moby Dick", "Best Thing I Never Had", "You Shook Me All Night Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Chasing Pavements", "T.N.T.", "Heartbreaker", "Solitary Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Back Where I Come From", "Too Damn Young", "Take It Easy", "Black Dog"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Lovers in Japan (acoustic version)", "You Belong With Me", "Heaven for Everyone", "The Rain Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Your Body's Callin'", "Thank You", "Run To Me", "No Lie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["New Power Generation", "What Now", "Caught Up", "Wipe Your Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Best of My Love", "Pure Imagination", "Superwoman", "Hole in the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["One Sweet Day (feat. Boyz II Men)", "It's Your Love", "Losing My Way", "Beautiful Goodbye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Inconsolable", "Our First Time", "Daylight", "Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Heartbreak Warfare", "All Nightmare Long", "Somewhere I Belong", "This Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["E.T.", "Sexy Ladies/Let Me Talk to You (prelude)", "Sweetest Goodbye", "Come Fly With Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Makes Me Wonder", "Redemption Song", "Beez in the Trap", "Qott Ghusian Da"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Locked Up", "Song for You", "Never Gonna Leave This Bed", "White Horse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Troublemaker", "Sunday Morning", "Sing Together", "Trouble Nobody"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Eye", "You Don't Know Jack", "Hotel California", "Give a Little More"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Loba", "Ek Ladki Ko Dekha", "Sad", "After All These Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Chup Kar Ke", "Come Fly With Me", "Won't Go Home Without You", "You Raise Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Lucky Strike", "Hakuna Matata", "Master of Puppets", "Achilles Last Stand"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Cruella De Vil", "Run To Me", "You Don't Know My Name", "The Way You Look Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Secret", "My Old Friend", "Love of My Life", "Firefly"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["I Won't Let Go", "Run It!", "Hands All Over", "If We Ever Meet Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Yeh Duniya Yeh Mehfil", "This Ain't Goodbye", "Nothing Lasts Forever", "Do I"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Just a Feeling", "Blue Moon", "Thank You", "Granddaddy's Gun"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Hole in the World", "Do You Remember", "She will be loved", "Every Teardrop Is a Waterfall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Bad Kids", "Long Live", "One More Night", "Daydreamer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Harder to Breathe", "No Church in the Wild", "Daniel", "T.N.T."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Sorry Seems To Be The Hardest Word", "You're Gonna Make Me Lonesome When You Go", "Snow (Hey Oh)", "If I Never See Your Face Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["The Man Who Never Lied", "Back Where I Come From", "Straight Through My Heart", "The Rain Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Trouble", "Misery", "Sweet and Simple", "Earth Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Aanewala Pal Janewala Hai", "Kiss", "Someday When I Stop Loving You", "I Need You Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Castle", "Daydreamin'", "Payphone", "The Jack"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Uska Hi Banana", "Goodnight Goodnight", "Do You Remember", "Gimme Shelter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Love Somebody", "You Had Me From Hello", "Dressin\u2019 Up", "Mockingbird"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Luck Be a Lady", "I Can't Quit You Baby", "Thank You for Loving Me", "Stutter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Doin' Dirt", "1+1", "Goodbye Yellow Brick Road", "By Myself"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Who Made Who", "Begin Again", "Moving Mountains", "Wake Up Call"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Quiz\u00e1s", "Black Star", "If I Ain't Got You (live)", "Nazar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Another One Bites The Dust", "It's Not Right but It's Okay", "Main Hoon Na", "Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Pretty Maids All In A Row", "Tees Maar Khan", "The Boys", "Lovers in Japan (acoustic version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Lying From You", "Nice & Slow", "Phir Milenge Chalte Chalte", "If I Were a Carpenter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["California Girls (stereo)", "Can't Help Falling in Love", "Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)", "Guzarish"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Dum", "Here", "One And Only", "Life in Technicolor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Do Pal Ka (Veer Zara)", "Russian Roulette", "Queen of California", "If I Ain't Got You (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Get Up Jawani (feat. Shah)", "Kal Ho Na Ho (Kal Ho Na Ho)", "Can't Hold Us", "Just Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["That's Life", "Be Intehaan", "Abhi Mujh Main Kahin", "Yeh Duniya Yeh Mehfil"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Free", "Mama's Song", "One Less Lonely Girl", "Tere Bin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Saanson Ne", "Love Story", "The Other Side (Feat. Cee Lo Green And B.o.B)", "Cabron"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Summer Nights", "Deewana Hoke Hum (Jan)", "Eu Sou O Ursinho Gummy (Brasilian)", "High School (feat. Lil Wayne)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["We Weren't Born to Follow", "Dil Ka Rishta", "Leader of Men (acoustic)", "Runaway"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Michelle", "Lick It", "Like Toy Soldiers", "Pyar Aaya"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["I'm Alive (Humberto Gatica mix)", "Ab Mujhe Raat Din", "Easy", "Fire Your Guns"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Is Kadar Pyar Hai Tumse", "Yeh Raaten Yeh Mausam", "I Can Transform Ya", "I'll Be Waiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["I Want Love", "Apnaa Mujhe Tu Lagaa", "Halo", "Kush"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Speak Now", "Back When", "It's Me Bitches (remix)", "Sun Zara"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["You Make Me Want To", "Magic", "Rapture", "Nagada Nagada"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["See You Again", "Stand", "Muskura", "Back Where I Come From"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Sparks", "Ankhon Se", "Toxic", "Mohabbat Kabhi Mai Ne (Yaad)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Balle Balle", "Feeling Good", "U Remind Me", "Lovers in Japan (acoustic version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Surfin' Safari", "You Remind Me", "That's Why God Made the Radio", "Saathiya"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["You Remind Me of Something", "Birthday", "O Sahiba O Sahiba", "Elton John"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["The Way You Make Me Feel", "Miraksam", "Naam Hai Tera", "Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["We Made You", "Step by Step", "FutureSex/LoveSound", "Chori Chori"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Ooh La La", "Aston Martin Music", "Mera Rang De Basanti", "She"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["LoveGame (album version)", "Tu", "Aston Martin Music", "Breaking the Habit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Am a Gummy Bear (The Gummy Bear Song)", "I Don't Believe You", "Deewana Tera", "Lean on Me (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Sonu Nigam?", "answers": ["Chanda Ki Doli Mai (Chanda Ki Doli)", "Since I've Been Loving You", "Quit Playin' Games", "Love You Inside Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Snitch", "Heartbreaker", "There Goes My Baby", "Bubble Butt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Troublemaker", "Brooklyn Go Hard", "Chillin", "Yesterday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Main Hoon Na", "If I Ruled the World", "Bitches Love Me", "Oh Africa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Play Hard", "One of Those Nights", "\"Can You Feel the Love Tonight (from \"\"The Lion King\"\")\"", "Eh Eh (Nothing Else I Can Say)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Sure Be Cool If You Did", "Love Me", "Locked Up", "Candle in the Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Who Knew", "Make U Love Me", "We Don't Care", "Temporary Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)", "Eagle", "Hot", "Somewhere With You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Happy People", "Boulevard of Broken Dreams", "Hold My Hand", "Best Thing I Never Had"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Sorry Seems To Be The Hardest Word", "Right now (Na Na Na)", "Otherside", "Gimme! Gimme! Gimme! (A Man After Midnight)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["The One", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Bring Him Home", "Don't Matter", "Confrontation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Now and Then", "Let's Get Away From It All", "Smack That", "Ek Pagla Meri Gali Ka"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Never Let Me Down Again", "O Saathi Re", "Girls Just Wanna Have Fun", "Like Money"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Innocence", "Freedom", "I Get Around", "Allah Hoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Windows Down", "Green", "High School (feat. Lil Wayne)", "Angel (feat. David Guetta)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Kush", "I Miss You", "Winner at a Losing Game", "Dreamworld"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Take It to the Limit", "Tangerine", "Temporary Home", "I Just Had Sex"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Shake That", "Trouble Nobody", "Trouble", "Come Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["When I Get You Alone", "X.Y.U.", "Oh! Darling", "I Wanna Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["I'm So Paid", "Drowning", "Mere Sapnon Ki Rani", "Tu Mohabbat Hai (remixed by DJ Suketu)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["I Wish It Would Rain Down", "I'll Still Kill (feat. Akon)", "Antes de las seis", "My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Magic", "Remind Me", "Ego", "Out Here Grindin\u2019"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["W.T.P.", "Rapture", "Bananza (Belly Dancer)", "Take a Chance on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["When You're Looking Like That", "I Need a Doctor", "Get Over It", "Ghetto"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Lonely", "No Love", "I Can't Make You Love Me", "All Nightmare Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["That's More Like It", "Beautiful", "Save Me", "Bullet With Butterfly Wings"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Don't Cry for Me Argentina", "Mama Africa", "Drive My Car", "Something Like Olivia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Kyun Chor Gaye Rastay", "Lullaby", "I Got U", "Be With You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["All About Tonight", "Ahista Ahista", "I Tried", "Little Lady"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Small Bump", "Tired", "Soul Survivor", "Simple"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Akon?", "answers": ["Girlfriend", "Keep You Much Longer", "Adada Vaa", "True Colors"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["No Leaf Clover", "Heart Attack", "Right Here", "Tequila Sunrise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["To Live Is to Die", "Young Forever", "Who's That Girl", "Fly to Your Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["You Really Got Me", "Got 2 Be Down (feat. Faith Evans)", "Aap Ki Khatir", "Castle of Glass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Sometimes It Snows in April", "Run", "S.E.X.", "All Nightmare Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Sad but True", "Circle of Life (The Lion King)", "I'll Always Remember You", "Violet Hill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Way I Am", "The Day That Never Comes", "WEEKENDS!!!", "Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites (Zedd remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Wendy", "Mama Said", "Always on My Mind (alternate Take 2)", "High Hills"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Sure Be Cool If You Did", "Ride the Lightning", "I'll Still Kill (feat. Akon)", "Holiday / Boulevard of Broken Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Love the Way You Lie (piano version)", "Home", "Always", "Through the Never"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Today", "Kabira (Encore)", "Put It in a Love Song", "Turn the Page"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Through the Rain", "The Call of Ktulu", "Forever", "Sun Zara"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Papercut (remix)", "Melt My Heart to Stone", "Take A Bow", "For Whom the Bell Tolls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Quiz\u00e1s", "Enter Sandman", "Castle of Glass", "Love of My Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["\u2026and Justice for All", "Summer Love/Set the Mood (prelude)", "Time Is on My Side", "Raabta (Siyaah Raatein)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Hold My Hand", "The Unforgiven", "Radio (Sir Spyro remix)", "Jaane Ya Ali Ali Ali"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Suit & Tie", "Battery", "I Want to Hold Your Hand", "If I Ruled the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Run This Town", "See You Again", "City of Hope", "Orion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Cowboy in Me", "The Four Horsemen", "Who's That Boy", "Start Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Girlfriend", "Right by My Side", "One", "Every Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Earth Song", "Shadow Days", "Until It Sleeps", "Iridescent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Hole in My Head", "Zindagi Ka Safar Hai Yeh Kaisa", "The Winner Takes It All", "Fade to Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Maine Puchha Chand Se (Abdullah)", "Do Pal Ka (Veer Zara)", "Black Ice", "The Memory Remains"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Material Girl", "Don't Blink", "Birthday", "Welcome Home (Sanitarium)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["When I Close My Eyes", "Do Pal Ka (Veer Zara)", "Creeping Death", "Whoa Oh!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Sexy Ladies/Let Me Talk to You (prelude)", "Satisfya", "The Movie in My Mind", "Seek & Destroy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Coming in From the Cold", "Maine Payal Hai Chhankai", "Fight Fire With Fire", "Never Let Me Down Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Kahin Deep Jale Kahin Dil", "Satisfy You (feat. Puff Daddy)", "Feel Like a Rock Star", "Blackened"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Shake That", "Yaar Da Makaan", "Master of Puppets", "Try Sleeping With a Broken Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Reason", "Ayer", "Dance in the Dark", "St. Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Rich As Fuck (Feat. 2 Chainz)", "Fuel", "Heavy Metal Lover", "Luck Be a Lady"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["Forgot About Dre", "Spanish Eyes", "Wherever I May Roam", "Neon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Baby", "Whiskey in the Jar", "Never Let Me Down Again", "Bed of Roses"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Leader of Men (acoustic)", "Really Don't Care", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Bring Him Home", "100$ Bill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Mannequin", "Never Gonna Be Alone", "Already Gone", "Sous le vent (feat. Garou)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Abhi Mujh Main Kahin", "Bottoms Up", "Take A Bow", "Don't Stop Believin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["If Everyone Cared", "I'll Never Break Your Heart", "Don't Go Breaking My Heart", "Saajna (unplugged)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["The Most Beautiful Girl in the World", "Because You Loved Me", "Too Bad (Diggla mix)", "Right There"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["The Prayer", "Every Teardrop Is a Waterfall", "Trying Not to Love You", "Si Te Vas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Little Saint Nick", "Boys Boys Boys", "Lullaby", "Hollywood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Our Song", "Stutter", "Savin' Me", "Bicycle Race"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Patteya Geya", "Figure.09", "Russian Roulette", "Rock Star"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Super Bass", "Are We All We Are", "Shakin Hands", "Say Something"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Never Say Never", "Winner at a Losing Game", "This Afternoon", "The Prayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Rain Dance Maggie", "Far Away", "California Girls (stereo)", "Dirty Diana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Moscas en la Casa", "Aashke (feat. Money Aujla)", "Nazar Se Nazar Tum", "S.E.X."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Vision of Love", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma", "Photograph", "More"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Fuel", "Gotta Be Somebody", "Open Arms", "I Lay My Love On You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Shattered", "I Can\u2019t Tell You Why", "Te amo", "How You Remind Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Wayfaring Stranger", "Get Off My Cloud", "Never Again", "Last Name"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Burn It to the Ground", "Esperanza", "Frozen (album version)", "Losing My Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Hero", "He Ain't the Leavin' Kind", "Pairon Mein Bandhan Hai", "I Wanna Grow Old With You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Animals", "Granddaddy's Gun", "Cover Girl", "Cheers (Drink to That)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Flat on the Floor", "Let It Be", "Mera Mann Kehne Laga (Reprise)", "When a Woman's Fed Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Hurts Like Heaven", "Likhe Jo Khat Tujhe", "If Today Was Your Last Day", "Mujhko Yaad Sataye Teri"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Duaa", "Chaska", "This Means War", "Mere Mitwa Mere Meet Re"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["I'd Come For You", "I Feel for You", "My Best Friend", "I Won't Let Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Someday", "Si tu te vas", "Stars", "Shadow Of The Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Tragedy", "Something in Your Mouth", "Panjaban Theme", "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Chandaniya (Lori Lori)", "Born This Way", "Feelin' on Yo Booty", "Figured You Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["I Still", "Amma Endralle", "When We Stand Together", "Emotion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Wait Til You See My Smile", "What About Now", "Buffalo Soldier", "You Remind Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Here Is to Never Growing Up", "Next Contestant", "One Way or Another (Teenage Kicks)", "6 Foot 7 Foot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["That Girl", "Live to Tell", "Believe It or Not", "Adada Vaa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nickelback?", "answers": ["Wild Horses (alternate)", "City Is Ours", "Follow You Home", "Beautiful"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma", "She Don't Like the Lights", "Candle in the Wind", "Touch Me (Gummib\u00e3*R)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["She Ain\u2019t You", "The Last Resort", "Jodl Jodl Dance", "Just Want You to Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Got Money", "Gummi From Bom Bom Bay", "Take You Down", "What Do You Got?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["I'm Your Funny Bear (Gelatine club mix)", "Samjho Na", "Keep Holding On", "Bounce"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Don't Blink", "Send It On", "Gummy Bear Instrumental", "Don't Cry for Me Argentina"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Eu Sou O Ursinho Gummy (Brasilian)", "Dil aisa kisi ne mera toda", "A Dedication", "Miraksam"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Girl From the North Country (feat. Bob Dylan)", "Do You Think I'm Sexy", "Enchanted", "I Got You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Something Like That", "Crocodile Rock", "Fly (feat. Rihanna)", "Itsy Bitsy Bikini"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["You Know It's Christmas", "Hush Little Baby", "The Good Stuff", "Sous le vent (feat. Garou)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Gummybear Song", "Pyar Aaya", "Sacrifice", "Radio GaGa"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["If It's Love", "Funny Bear (Good Night mix)", "Get Over It", "Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["One in a Million", "Itt Van A Gumimaci (Hungarian)", "It's Gotta Be You", "Love Me Do"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Use Your Love", "I Want It That Way (single version)", "Osito Gummy Bear (Mexican)", "Castle of Glass"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Little Deuce Coupe", "When You're Looking Like That", "Am a Gummy Bear (The Gummy Bear Song)", "Ten Thousand Hours"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Zindagi Ye", "Jag \u00e4r en gummibj\u00f6rn", "Philadelphia Freedom", "Prayin' for Daylight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["Eenie Meenie", "Thriller", "Earth Song", "Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["This Ain't a Love Song", "F**kin' Perfect", "Harder to Breathe", "Don't Do That"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Gummybear?", "answers": ["I Need a Doctor", "Funny DJ", "Mama Africa", "Drown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["I Would Find You", "Raise Your Glass", "Get Down", "The Power of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Drowning", "Forever", "Just a Feeling", "Drops of Jupiter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Fantine's Death", "In the End", "Breakfast in Bed", "Inconsolable"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Enfant de L'homme", "You Save Me", "Just Want You to Know", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Electric Feel", "We've Got It Goin' On", "Without Me", "Touch My Body"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Winner at a Losing Game", "It Seems Like You're Ready", "You Can't Hurry Love", "Incomplete"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Penis Song", "Practice", "Hay Amores", "All I Have to Give"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Girl Can't Help It", "Anywhere For You", "Music", "Jaane Ya Ali Ali Ali"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Little Things", "\"Almost Home (Music from the Motion Picture \"\"Oz the Great and Powerful\"\")\"", "Beautiful", "Show Me The Meaning of Being Lonely"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["I Look to You", "Moment of Clarity", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "No One Else Comes Close"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Have a Drink on Me", "The Call", "Khalbali", "Intro"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Country Man", "As Long as You Love Me (radio version)", "Everything's Not Lost", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Stars"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Here Is to Never Growing Up", "Rock 'n' Roll", "Ol' Red", "This Is Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["The Lemon Song", "Long Live", "The Perfect Fan", "Anybody Seen My Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Run To Me", "Lay All Your Love on Me", "I'll Never Break Your Heart", "White Privilege"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Grade 8", "Shape of My Heart", "City Is Ours", "Freakshow"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Fantasy", "Unmistakable", "Something in Your Mouth", "This Is Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Everybody (Backstreet's Back)", "Earth Song", "Closer Than Close", "Sympathy for the Devil (original)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Never Gone", "Best I Ever Had", "After All These Years", "My All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Gypsy", "Larger Than Life", "Born to Be My Baby", "Robot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Lying From You", "Unakkum Enakkum", "Ullathai Killathe", "Spanish Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Whataya Want From Me", "Shiver", "Give It Away", "I Still"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Back to Your Heart", "Dil To Hai Dil", "Far Away", "Hush Little Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["No More Sorrow", "Quit Playin' Games", "Heaven for Everyone", "White Privilege"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Americano", "Suck My Kiss", "I Need You Tonight", "Be Intehaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Practice", "How Did I Fall in Love With You", "Inside Out", "Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Anyplace Is Paradise", "Goodbye's (The Saddest Word)", "Poppin'", "Straight Through My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["The Day Before You", "The One", "Bleed It Out", "Shiver"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Best for Last", "I Want It That Way (single version)", "Love Will Remember", "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Little Deuce Coupe", "Love Story", "More Than That", "More Than Words"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["It's Gotta Be You", "Over Again", "Break The Ice", "Diva"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Rusty Cage", "Nunca te har\u00e9 llorar", "Sari Sari Raat", "If I Ain't Got You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Landslide", "Heartbreaker", "Yeh Duniya Yeh Mehfil", "Adore"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Escapar (Escape)", "Perfect", "Tired", "Love on Top"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Lucy in the Sky With Diamonds", "Never Let Me Down Again", "Follow You Home", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Fantine's Death", "Antes de las seis", "Zero", "Mockingbird"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["X.Y.U.", "Another Round (explicit version)", "The Perfect Fan", "Hey Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Always on My Mind (alternate Take 2)", "Skyfall", "Have a Drink on Me", "Doomsday Clock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Are We All We Are", "The Celestials", "Otherside", "I Kissed a Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Today", "Hate That I Love You", "Edge of Desire", "Ain't No Grave"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Stand Inside Your Love", "Fix You (edit)", "The Reason", "Sway"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["My Friends", "Against All Odds (Take A Look At Me Now)", "Whenever You Remember", "The Beginning Is the End Is the Beginning"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Feelin' on Yo Booty", "Vision of Love", "Take You Down", "Drown"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["You da One", "Things I'll Never Say", "Cherub Rock", "Changed"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["You'll Always Find Your Way Back Home", "Pour que tu m'aimes encore", "Muzzle", "I Started a Joke"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Thirty Three", "When a Woman's Fed Up", "Kiss You", "Tere Bin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Farewell and Goodnight", "If I Never See Your Face Again", "Pyar Kiya to Darna Kya", "If You Ain't Here to Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Money Make Her Smile", "Rocket", "I Wish", "D\u2019yer Mak\u2019er"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Stop & Erase", "(Ghost) Riders in the Sky", "I Don't Miss You at All", "Bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Somewhere I Belong", "Greatest Love of All", "Party on My Mind", "Bullet With Butterfly Wings"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Buffalo Soldier", "Mellon Collie and the Infinite Sadness", "Make It Rain", "Anything But Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["1979", "Aanewala Pal Janewala Hai", "Material Girl", "Welcome Home (Sanitarium)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Thank You for Loving Me", "Bleed", "Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)", "Suck My Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Man Down", "Soma", "Suit & Tie", "Gummy Bear Instrumental"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Love Song", "Drive My Car", "Ava Adore", "Pour It Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Punjabane", "The Best of Both Worlds (2009 Movie mix)", "Michelle", "Disarm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Eye", "Right as Rain", "Coming in From the Cold", "Red Camaro"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Bottoms Up", "Rhinoceros", "Mandy (live at the O2)", "I'm Your Baby Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Moondance", "The Other Side (Feat. Cee Lo Green And B.o.B)", "Mayonaise", "Space Bound"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["I'll Stand by You", "Inside Your Heaven", "Make It Bun Dem (Electro Body trance remix by Sthilmann)", "The Everlasting Gaze"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["I'll Stand by You (Glee Cast version)", "Luna", "Make It Rain", "Kiss Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Smashing Pumpkins?", "answers": ["Hummer", "Blow Me (One Last Kiss)", "I'm Every Woman", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Vijay?", "answers": ["Don't Make Me", "Vaadi Vaadi", "Don't Let Me Be the Last to Know", "Skin (Sarabeth)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Vijay?", "answers": ["I Miss You", "I'll Be Waiting", "Hold On", "Ullathai Killathe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Vijay?", "answers": ["Little Lady", "Rani Tu Mein Raja", "Muskura", "Ennoda Laila"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Vijay?", "answers": ["Change My Mind", "From the Inside", "Coca Cola Braunu", "You Raise Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Vijay?", "answers": ["Defying Gravity", "Google Google", "Gold", "Funhouse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Waiting on a Friend", "Alone", "Angel", "Don't Stop 'Til You Get Enough (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["The Perfect Fan", "Smile", "Mother's Little Helper", "Gimme That"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Thank You", "She's a Rainbow", "Sing Together", "Disarm"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Adore", "The Call of Ktulu", "Dead Flowers", "Charlie Brown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Jump", "Gravity", "Deewana Tera", "You Can't Always Get What You Want"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Chalte Chalte", "That's All Right", "Brown Sugar", "Something Like That"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Rabiosa", "Thuy's Death / You Will Not Touch Him", "Slow Dancing in a Burning Room", "Beast of Burden"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Barbara Ann", "Get Over It", "Winner at a Losing Game", "Ruby Tuesday"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Gal Sun Ja", "Lovesong", "All Too Well", "Tumbling Dice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Ullathai Killathe", "Crazy for You", "Raabta", "Under My Thumb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["I Love Rock'n Roll", "Let's Spend the Night Together", "Every Day", "It's In The Mornin (feat. Snoop Dogg)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Young", "O Bekhabar", "Sympathy for the Devil (original)", "Mere Dil Ki Duniya Mein"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Stars Dance", "Gimme Shelter", "Saawali Si Raat", "That\u2019s My Bitch"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Life Is Cinema", "Paint It Black", "Crush", "Letting Go (Dutty Love)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["As Tears Go By", "Aise Na Mujhe Tum Dekho", "The Best Is Yet to Come", "My Boo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Angie", "Scream", "Dil Kya Kare", "Satisfya"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Painting Pictures", "Time Is on My Side", "What About Now", "Give It Up to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["At Last", "Pretty Little Ditty", "Distance and Time", "Honky Tonk Women"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Drops of Jupiter", "Blue Suede Shoes", "Doom And Gloom", "Strawberry Fields Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Orion", "Street Fightin' Man", "Summertime", "She's on Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["I Started a Joke", "Smooth Criminal", "Anybody Seen My Baby", "Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["You Don't Fool Me", "Angel", "Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019", "Get Off My Cloud"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Hard to Say I'm Sorry", "Back in Black", "Shattered", "Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Crash My Party", "A Boy Named Sue", "Start Me Up", "Feeling That Way / Anytime"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Wild Horses (alternate)", "I Started a Joke", "You're My Only Shorty", "American Idiot"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Show Me", "Midnight Rambler", "Beautiful People", "Osito Gummy Bear (Mexican)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["(I Can't Get No) Satisfaction", "You're Not Alone", "Bottoms Up", "All by Myself (Spanish version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Can\u2019t You Hear Me Knocking", "Piya O Re Piya", "The World's Greatest", "I Want"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Waiting for the End", "Intro", "Feelin' on Yo Booty", "Jumpin' Jack Flash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Prem Bann", "I'll Stand by You", "The Last Time", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Bless the Broken Road", "Miss You", "Disappear", "Wish You Were Here"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Pour It Up", "Love in Vain", "Every Teardrop Is a Waterfall", "Do You Think About Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Irreplaceable (album version)", "Jaoon Kahan", "Like a Prayer", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Death And All His Friends", "Magic", "Something", "I Need Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Can't Stop Loving You", "Going to California", "Your Song", "Shakin' It 4 Daddy (feat. Nicki Minaj)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["These are the Days of Our Lives", "Make U Love Me", "Castle of Glass", "\"Rascacielo (\"\"Skyscraper\"\" Spanish Version)\""], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Las de la Intuici\u00f3n", "Sex Therapy", "Doin' Dirt", "Haunted"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Magical", "Last First Kiss", "Pretty Lil Heart (feat. Lil Wayne)", "Somebody to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Bad Girls", "Confrontation", "World of Your Own", "Va Va Voom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["The Last Night of the World", "A Beautiful World", "Controversy", "One Drop"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Lost Without U", "One Way or Another (Teenage Kicks)", "Use Your Love", "City of Hope"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Hard to Say I'm Sorry", "The Jack", "Wanna Love You Girl", "Tunnel Vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Step by Step", "Oh Africa", "The Sweetest Love", "Soul Rebel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["The Baby", "Blurred Lines", "Sk8er Boi", "High School (feat. Lil Wayne)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Walking Contradiction", "Who Wants to Live Forever", "Yeh Raaten Yeh Mausam", "Cocaine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Qott Ghusian Da", "Complicated", "Jab Se Tumko Dekha Hai Sanam", "Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Please Remember Me", "Didn't We Almost Have It All", "This Is Me", "Million Dolla Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Born to Make You Happy", "Real Good Man", "See You Again", "Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Beat It", "Let's Spend the Night Together", "O Bekhabar", "Dreamworld"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Got 2 Be Down (feat. Faith Evans)", "Picture to Burn", "Dil Ka Rishta", "Ennoda Laila"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Miss You", "Do You Think About Me", "Love After War", "Bohemian Rhapsody"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Woh Lamhe", "Green", "Back to Your Heart", "Tie My Hands"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Mama Said", "Dear Mr. President (From I'm Not Dead Live - Wembley Arena)", "Everything I Can't Have", "Everything Has Changed (feat. Ed Sheeran)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["You're My Baby", "Next Contestant", "Forever", "Cab"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Hello", "Road Trippin'", "Superman", "Circle of Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["All Tied Up", "This Afternoon", "Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites (Zedd remix)", "Right Thru Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Teach U A Lesson", "Super Bass", "One Piece at a Time", "Catch a Grenade (The Hooligans remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Too Much Love Will Kill You", "Mera Jeevan Kora Kagaz", "When I Get You Alone", "Saturday Night's Alright (for Fighting)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["My Life", "Dear Mr. President (From I'm Not Dead Live - Wembley Arena)", "Michelle", "Rock 'n' Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Magic", "She", "Another World", "Immortality"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["How Forever Feels", "Strawberry Bubblegum", "Can U Believe", "Stone Cold Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Doomsday Clock", "Save the Day", "It's In The Mornin (feat. Snoop Dogg)", "Tragedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["It's My Life (2003)", "For Whom the Bell Tolls", "I'll Be There for You", "Lay Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Freakshow", "Phoolan Ka Taron Ka", "I Have Nothing", "Cry Me a River"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Right In", "Same Love", "Google Google", "Mera Jeevan Kora Kagaz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Mehfooz", "Kiss You", "A New Day Has Come", "Haal Kya Hai Dilon Ka"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Love in This Club", "Die in Your Arms", "Aap Ki Ankhon Mein", "Why Not Me?"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Highway To Hell", "Livin' on a Prayer", "Ek Ajanabee Haseena Se", "One Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Thank You for the Music", "Firefly", "Guide: Gaata Rahe Mera Dil", "Tera Ishq Bada Teekha"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Stayin' Alive", "Big Time Rush (Theme)", "Dil Kya Kare", "Numb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Zindagi Ka Safar Hai Yeh Kaisa", "Innocence", "In My Room", "Banjo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["I Found a Boy", "Manzilen Apni Jagah Hain", "No New Friends (SFTB Remix)", "Sorry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Getaway", "Phoolon Ke Rang Se", "Teardrops on My Guitar", "Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Buffalo Soldier", "Rote Hue Aate Hain Sab", "Do You Remember", "Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["I'm with You", "Pal Pal Dil Ke Pas", "Kal Ho Na Ho (Kal Ho Na Ho)", "Jaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Encore", "Desensitized", "O Saathi Re", "Koi Hota Jisko Apna"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Could You Be Loved", "Dreamlover", "Off That", "Ek Ladki Bheegi Bhaagi Si"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Any Way You Want It", "Wall to Wall", "Mere Mehboob Qayamat Hogi", "Give It Up to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Dilbar Mere Kab Tak Mujhe", "Ave Maria", "Rolling In The Deep", "Give Me All Your Luvin' (Party Rock remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Never Say Goodbye", "If It's Love", "Agar Tum Na Hote", "When the Stars Go Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Life in Technicolor", "Words", "Aanewala Pal Janewala Hai", "No Such Thing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Sloop John B", "Aise Na Mujhe Tum Dekho", "Borderline", "I Just Wanna Love U (Give It to Me)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Chalte Chalte", "Count On Me", "Daydreamer", "Are You Ready"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["The Prayer", "Ave Maria", "Masterpiece", "Yeh Raaten Yeh Mausam"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Everything", "Roop Tera Mastana", "I Would", "Overprotected"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Jesus Take the Wheel", "Mere Sapnon Ki Rani", "Kabira (Encore)", "Kaun Hoon Main"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Chasing Pavements", "Neele Neele Ambar Par", "By Myself", "Satyam Shivam Sundaram"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Addicted", "Now and Then", "Everybody (Backstreet's Back)", "Zindagi Ek Safar Hai Suhana"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Rain Dance Maggie", "I Can Only Imagine", "Muqaddar Ka Sikandar: O Saathi Re", "Hummer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Tragedy", "Chhu Kar Mere Manko", "50 Ways to Say Goodbye", "Viraaniya"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kishore Kumar?", "answers": ["Koi Humdum Na Raha", "You'll Be in My Heart", "High Hopes", "I Wanna Love You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["(Ghost) Riders in the Sky", "Headlines", "True Colours", "What Hurts the Most"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["How Did I Fall in Love With You", "Colours", "Crew Love (featuring The Weeknd)", "Hero"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Queen of California", "Best I Ever Had", "Nobody Knows", "Dono Ne Kiya Tha"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Yeh Duniya Yeh Mehfil", "Amen", "Strawberry Swing", "Blessed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["The Motto", "DJ Got Us Fallin' in Love", "Sweet Dreams", "This Is Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["My Same", "You Can't Always Get What You Want", "Take Care", "Slipped Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Round of Applause", "Rain Is a Good Thing", "Keep You Much Longer", "Lost Without U"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Summer Wind (feat. Julio Iglesias)", "Us Against The World", "Banjo", "Right Above It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Fool Again (2000 remix)", "Aston Martin Music", "Everything Back But You (live)", "Bakhuda Tumhi Ho"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Right Here", "Because You Loved Me", "When I Look to the Sky", "Asphalt Cowboy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Boys 'Round Here (feat. Pistol Annies)", "My Best Friend", "International Love", "Cameras / Good Ones Go Interlude"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Be With You", "Rest of My Life (Extended)", "Pop That", "6 Foot 7 Foot"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Practice", "Dilbar Mere Kab Tak Mujhe", "Trading Places", "Ballad of a Teenage Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Experiencia religiosa", "Trouble Nobody", "Trust Issues", "Jab Jab Phool Khile: Pardesiyon Se Na Ankhiyan Milana"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Parler \u00e0 mon p\u00e8re", "Rubberneckin'", "Say Something", "The Way You Look Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Nobody's Perfect", "Marvin's Room", "Izzo (H.O.V.A.)", "Goliyan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Stay Schemin'", "3", "Angel", "Orion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Fancy", "Angie", "Something Like That", "If I Ain't Got You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Ahista Ahista", "Run", "Poetic Justice", "Caught Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Forever", "I Was Here", "I'm Gonna Live Till I Die", "Tonight (I'm Lovin' You)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Here Is to Never Growing Up", "Heartbreak Warfare", "Punjabane", "5AM In Toronto"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["I Can't Sleep Baby (If I)", "Numb", "Jesus of Suburbia", "She Will"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["She Loves You", "Banjo", "Over", "Love Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["You Win Again", "Some Beach", "Fall for Your Type", "Whenever Wherever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Doing It Wrong", "Gummybear Song", "Tera Mera Pyar Amar", "Slow Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Letting Go (Dutty Love)", "Shot for Me", "U.N.I.", "We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["I'm Every Woman", "Tees Maar Khan", "The Town", "HYFR (Hell Ya F*****g Right)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Your Love", "You're My Baby", "I'll Be Waiting", "Miss Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Too Much Love Will Kill You", "Butterflyz", "I Still Believe", "No Lie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Sweet Love", "Started from the Bottom", "\"Can You Feel the Love Tonight (from \"\"The Lion King\"\")\"", "Buzzkill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Tony Montana", "Playboys of the Southwestern World", "No More Sorrow", "Ashley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Drake?", "answers": ["Somebody to Love", "Santa Claus Is Comin' to Town", "Stronger (Pablo La Rosa's Tranceformation edit)", "No New Friends (SFTB Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Welcome to My Hood", "Kyoto", "I Want to Know What Love Is", "Made In the USA"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["I Miss You", "All Around The World (featuring Ludacris)", "Unbroken", "My Wish"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["T.N.T.", "Seven Bridges Road", "Soma", "La La Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Lightweight", "Only Girl (in the World)", "Jive Talkin'", "Life in the Fast Lane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["You're My Only Shorty", "Tommie Sunshine\u2019s Megasix Smash-Up", "Strawberry Fields Forever", "Maine Payal Hai Chhankai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Never Been Hurt", "Something", "I Love You", "We've Got It Goin' On"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Chillin", "Dreamworld", "Together", "Could You Be Loved"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Here Comes the Sun", "Magic", "For the Love of a Daughter", "Right on Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["The Everlasting Now", "Teardrops on My Guitar", "Dress On", "Believe in Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Ride Home", "I Can Transform Ya", "Something Stupid", "It\u2019s Not Too Late"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Wouldn\u2019t Change a Thing", "The Man in Black", "First Love", "I Don't Trust Myself (With Loving You)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Catch Me", "So Emotional", "Mean", "Mane Chudi Piravan Lagyo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Strangers in the Night", "Big Gun", "Hero (MetroMix)", "Lo Que Soy (This Is Me Spanish version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Billionaire", "On and On and On", "This Is Me", "Nobody's Perfect"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Manzilen Apni Jagah Hain", "Without the Love", "Mohabbat Kabhi Mai Ne (Yaad)", "Funhouse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Miss Me", "I Don't Miss You at All", "You", "Don't Forget"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Hoedown Throwdown", "She's My Kind of Rain", "Dono Ne Kiya Tha", "Give Your Heart a Break"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Wish You Were Here", "In Case", "The Name of the Game", "Kashmir"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Can't Help Falling in Love", "Something That We're Not", "Kiss Tomorrow Goodbye", "A Place for My Head"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Open Arms", "In Love With the Girl", "Hero (MetroMix)", "Nightingale"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Show Me", "No Me Digas Que No", "Fix a Heart", "Gummybear Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["A Thousand Years", "Stuck", "You'll Always Find Your Way Back Home", "Send It On"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Come", "Heart Attack", "Feels Good at First", "Dum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Rubberneckin'", "Naam Hai Tera", "Ignition", "\"Rascacielo (\"\"Skyscraper\"\" Spanish Version)\""], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["From the Inside", "Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)", "Celebration", "Neon Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Those Shoes", "Remember December", "Voulez-vous", "Rapture"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["You're Not Alone", "Body Count", "Apologize", "Really Don't Care"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Lollipop", "Something About the Way You Look Tonight", "Warrior", "Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Shouldn't Come Back", "Best I Ever Had", "Everything About You", "Hurt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Resurrection (Axwell's Recut Club Version) / Paradise", "I Want to Break Free", "Burn", "Two Pieces"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Who's That Boy", "It's a Long Way to the Top (If You Wanna Rock 'n' Roll)", "Hurts Like Heaven", "My Name Is Skrillex"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Do You Hear What I Hear", "Breaking the Habit", "Tell Me Something I Don't Know", "Cry Me a River"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Baby One More Time", "L.A. Boyz (feat. Victoria Justice and Ariana Grande)", "Public Service Announcement (interlude)", "Come Fly With Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Girls Just Wanna Have Fun", "Wada Tainu", "Abhi Mujh Main Kahin", "Who's Lovin' You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019", "Easy", "Song for You", "Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["I Know You Know (feat. Cymphonique)", "Daddy's Little Girl", "Pet Sounds", "Cleaning Out My Closet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Save The Last Dance For Me", "Just Lose It", "Don't Do That", "Tears Always Win"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Lullaby", "Sacrifice", "Back in Black", "It's a Beautiful Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["After All", "Bad Girl", "A Kind of Magic", "Almost Is Never Enough"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Rabba", "Major Minus", "Close Your Eyes", "Chalte Chalte"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Spaceship Coupe", "Ass Like That", "Phir Milenge Chalte Chalte", "You And I"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["I Like It", "Can't Stop Loving You", "Feeling Good", "In the Air Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Playboys of the Southwestern World", "I Still", "Where the Green Grass Grows", "To Love Somebody"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Crazy Little Thing Called Love", "This Is Me", "Love in Vain", "This Is It"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Home", "Heartbreak Hotel", "Unmistakable", "Given Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Holly Jolly Christmas", "If It Hadn't Been for Love", "Shakin Hands", "Tujh Mein Rab Dikhta Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["L O V E", "God Gave Me You", "Victim of Love", "When It's All Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Beez in the Trap", "Alejandro", "Peaceful Easy Feeling", "Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Catch Me", "Hold On", "I Told You So", "Mother's Little Helper"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Hung Up", "Pyar Kiya to Darna Kya", "That's Why I'm Here", "You Don't Know Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Tonight (I'm Lovin' You)", "Phir Le Aya Dil (Reprise)", "Hero", "Hollywood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Single Ladies (Put a Ring on It)", "Funny DJ", "Always on My Mind", "Rock 'n' Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Butterflyz", "Birthday Cake", "The Way You Look Tonight:", "Sweetest Goodbye"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Tera Hone Laga Hoon", "For Those About To Rock (We Salute You)", "Crazy Love", "Bodies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Me and Mrs. Jones", "Dil Hai Tumhara", "Come Together", "Girl Gone Wild"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Scream", "Teardrops on My Guitar", "Lose Yourself", "To Be Loved"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Waiting in Vain (remix 84)", "Tere Bin", "Kiss and Tell (Bonus Track)", "Haven't Met You Yet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Better Left Unsaid", "Something Stupid", "Wayfaring Stranger", "Dangerous"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["No Worries", "Die in Your Arms", "Everything", "Masterpiece"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Sway", "Don't Stop Believin'", "If You Ain't Here to Party", "Crocodile Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Dreamlover", "Moondance", "Curse of Indra", "Hello"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Bubl\u00e9?", "answers": ["Frozen (album version)", "Lost", "Perfectly Lonely", "Glad You Came"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Mine", "One Less Lonely Girl", "Personal Jesus", "Hey Hey What Can I Do"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["40 Pra", "Highway To Hell", "Don't Take Your Guns To Town", "Leave Out All the Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Now and Then", "You Are My Sunshine", "All the Man That I Need", "Street Fightin' Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Skin (Sarabeth)", "One", "The Most Beautiful Girl in the World", "Get The Party Started"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Heavy", "Ballad of a Teenage Queen", "Back That Azz Up", "Princess of China"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Wish You Were Here", "Tired of Being Sorry", "War Machine", "The General Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Super Bass", "Get Rhythm (feat. The Tennessee Two)", "Please Remember Me", "Us Against the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Pal Pal Dil Ke Pas", "Always on My Mind", "Mere Mitwa Mere Meet Re", "Orange Blossom Special"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Slow Wind", "Helter Skelter", "You're My Only Shorty", "Folsom Prison Blues (mono)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Simple", "(Ghost) Riders in the Sky", "Cold Coffee", "No Idea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Suck My Kiss", "Feeling Good", "Big Time Rush (Theme)", "Ring Of Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Innocence", "Beez in the Trap", "Solitary Man", "Entre Deux Mondes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Ruler's Back", "Crazy for You", "A Boy Named Sue", "Rock 'n' Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Lost", "San Quentin", "Turn Me On", "Eu Sou O Ursinho Gummy (Brasilian)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["I'll Stand by You", "One Piece at a Time", "LoveStoned/I Think She Knows (interlude)", "Tujh Mein Rab Dikhta Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Getaway", "Everything", "Love After War", "The Man in Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Speedin'", "Blackened", "Cocaine Blues", "Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Circle the Drain", "Farewell and Goodnight", "Sunday Morning Coming Down", "Close Your Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["How Long", "Something in Your Mouth", "Rusty Cage", "It's Now or Never"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["True Friend", "I Walk The Line", "All My Friends Say", "Song Cry"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Dazed and Confused", "I Want You (She's So Heavy)", "Without U (interlude)", "The Man Comes Around"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["God's Gonna Cut You Down", "Moscas en la Casa", "Jive Talkin'", "It's All Up to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Hurt", "Super Trouper", "Miracle", "When a Woman Loves"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["I've Been Everywhere", "1999 (LP version)", "Kahin Deep Jale Kahin Dil", "Stay Awhile"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Underneath Your Clothes", "Wayfaring Stranger", "Tomorrow", "Rock Your Body"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Like Money", "Ain't No Grave", "Doom And Gloom", "Inside Your Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Wish You Were Here", "Superman", "First Time Ever I Saw Your Face", "Trouble"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Jackson", "1999 (LP version)", "That Girl", "Treasure"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Warning Sign", "Thunderstruck", "Government Hooker", "If I Were a Carpenter"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Tere Husn Ki Kya", "Girl From the North Country (feat. Bob Dylan)", "Take a Chance on Me", "You Remind Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Here Comes Goodbye", "Southern Voice", "the Heart of Life", "Bakhuda Tumhi Ho"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Kiss Tomorrow Goodbye", "Mayberry", "Summit", "Ye Ishq Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Take Care", "The Winner Takes It All", "Part Of Me", "I'm Movin' On"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Aashke (feat. Money Aujla)", "Banjo", "Santa Fe", "Bitches Love Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Immigrant Song", "Your Love", "Backwards", "Satan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Anything But Mine", "Shattered", "Winner at a Losing Game", "Angry All the Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Bless the Broken Road", "Pehli Nazar Mein", "It's Time", "Brand New Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["The Prayer", "My Wish", "You da One", "I Would Find You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Take Me With U", "Gotta Be You", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma", "I Won't Let Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Wada Tainu", "Changed", "Rusty Cage", "Welcome to Paradise"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Red Camaro", "Step in the Name of Love", "Public Service Announcement (interlude)", "Kikli Kalerdi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["The Girl From Yesterday", "Daylight", "That's How Strong My Love Is", "Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Chillin", "Rabba Ve Mera Yaar Modh De", "It\u2019s Not Too Late", "Why"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["He Ain't the Leavin' Kind", "Next Contestant", "Midnight Rambler", "Sunday Morning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Strange Clouds", "I Melt", "Jaan", "Kasam Khake Kaho"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["The Beautiful Ones", "Still Getting It", "A Kind of Magic", "Every Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["I Wanna Go", "Enfant de L'homme", "If I Ain't Got You", "Fast Cars and Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Life Is a Highway", "Wheel in the Sky", "Poetic Justice", "You Make Me Wanna..."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Dance for You", "Orange Blossom Special", "Good Vibrations", "Take Me There"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["This'll Be My Year", "Prayin' for Daylight", "For the Love of a Daughter", "Livin' on a Prayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Take You", "Feels Like Today", "The Power of Love", "Give It 2 Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Exodus", "When a Woman Loves", "Unstoppable", "Sous le vent (feat. Garou)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["The Call", "Photograph", "Summer Nights", "After All These Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Come Wake Me Up", "Can't Help Falling in Love", "Doolin-Dalton", "Welcome to My Hood"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Soul Survivor", "Put It in a Love Song", "James Dean", "Me and My Gang"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Stand", "Up All Night", "Glitter in the Air", "Osito Gummy Bear (Mexican)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Forever", "Queen of California", "What Hurts the Most", "Just Give Me a Reason"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Santa Claus Is Comin' to Town", "That's More Like It", "Heart Attack", "Easy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Natalie", "Here", "I'll Still Kill (feat. Akon)", "Don't Rain on My Parade"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["Rumour Has It", "These Days", "Kiss You", "American Idiot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["The Everlasting Now", "Skin (Sarabeth)", "Hard Knock Life (Ghetto Anthem)", "Tum Mujhe Yun Bhula Na Paoge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Rascal Flatts?", "answers": ["No Such Thing", "How Long", "The Day Before You", "Iridescent"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Hold It Against Me", "A Milli", "Esperanza", "Taken"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Lucky", "Treasure", "Painting Pictures", "Til I Forget About You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Count on You (feat. Jordin Sparks)", "Kiss & Tell", "Pushing Me Away", "3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Born to Make You Happy", "The World's Greatest", "Somebody to Love", "L O V E"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Yeh Jo Halki Halki Khumariya", "You Drive Me Crazy", "409", "If I Never See Your Face Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["One Love / People Get Ready", "Pirate Flag", "Oops!...I Did It Again", "High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["There Goes My Baby", "Muckalee Creek Water", "We Will Rock You (with Beyonce & Pink)", "Hello"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["When I Was Your Man", "Piece Of Me", "Gotham City", "One And Only"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Till the World Ends", "I Wanna Grow Old With You", "See You Soon", "Brooklyn Go Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["I Love Rock'n Roll", "I Get Around", "Something in Your Mouth", "One Drop"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Be True to Your School", "When You Love a Woman", "Words", "Criminal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Who Says You Can't Go Home", "Isaiyarasi (feat. S. Rajeswari & S. Janaki)", "Break The Ice", "Aha Aha"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["My Prerogative", "Man Dole Mera Tan Dole", "Us Against The World", "The Sweetest Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Chura Ke Dil Mera", "Someday (I Will Understand)", "I Wanna Grow Old With You", "Battery"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["When I Close My Eyes", "More Than That", "I Wanna Go", "8 Mile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Hole in My Head", "Sometimes (radio edit)", "Love Me", "Kiss and Tell (Bonus Track)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Triumphant (The New Iberican League Radio)", "Freakshow", "I Started a Joke", "Achilles Last Stand"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Toxic", "Girl Can't Help It", "Take My Drunk Ass Home", "Ab Mujhe Raat Din"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Give Me All Your Luvin' (Party Rock remix)", "Bottoms Up", "Inside Out", "Drive My Car"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["(Drop Dead) Beautiful", "Ride Home", "Smack That", "Ten Times Crazier"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Write Your Name", "Don't Let Me Be the Last to Know", "Satisfya", "Roop Tera Mastana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Everytime (album version)", "At Last", "I Want to Hold Your Hand", "Warrior"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Happy New Year", "Be True to Your School", "I'm Not a Girl Not Yet a Woman", "Remember High School"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Some Beach", "Perfectly Lonely", "From the Bottom of My Broken Heart", "How Forever Feels"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Gasoline", "Tere Bin", "Gunwalk (Feat. Gudda Gudda)", "I Can\u2019t Tell You Why"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["If U Seek Amy", "Honeymoon Avenue", "Can U Believe", "Give It 2 Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Turning Tables", "Life Is a Highway", "Fat Bottomed Girls", "Stronger (Pablo La Rosa's Tranceformation edit)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Baby One More Time", "Nothing Like Us", "Nothing Even Matters", "The Other Side (Feat. Cee Lo Green And B.o.B)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Got 2 Be Down (feat. Faith Evans)", "If I Ain't Got You", "Our First Time", "Overprotected"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Batdance", "Saajna (unplugged)", "Famous", "Gimme More"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Boyfriend", "I'm a Slave 4 U (Thunderpuss radio mix)", "Anything But Mine", "Raa Raa Raa Gumma Raa Thulle Komma"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Put Your Hearts Up", "Do Somethin'", "All Over Again", "Chandaniya (Lori Lori)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Half of My Heart", "Jam", "I Love You", "Big Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Man in the Mirror", "Complicated (Tom Lord-Alge mix)", "Nazar Se Nazar Tum", "Beez in the Trap"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["You Rock My World", "The Man Who Never Lied", "Antes de las seis", "Windows Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Stop & Erase", "Billie Jean", "Aston Martin Music", "Video Phone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Ride Home", "This Is It", "Higher Ground", "Waiting on the World to Change"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Do You Think About Me", "For Whom the Bell Tolls", "One More Night", "Heal The World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Earth Song", "Welcome to the Farm", "Fingerprints", "All Nightmare Long"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Get Down", "One Time", "The Way You Make Me Feel", "(Ghost) Riders in the Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Hurts Like Heaven", "Neon", "Under The Bridge", "Remember the Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Liberian Girl", "Shut Down", "Shake It Up", "Free Fallin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Freedom", "Dirty Diana", "Ruffneck (Full Flex) (Munchi Anonymous Revolution remix)", "Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Bichdann", "Stranger in Moscow", "Starships", "Maine to Khadi Chhat Ke Upar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["You Are Not Alone", "Sad", "Roop Tera Mastana", "I Like It That Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Heartache Tonight", "From the Bottom of My Broken Heart", "In the Closet", "Play Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["U + Ur Hand", "Lovesong", "Rock With You", "Lost Without U"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Bad", "Sacrement", "Dear Mr. President (From I'm Not Dead Live - Wembley Arena)", "Better Than I Used to Be"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Nobody Does It Like You", "Ghosts", "Kootthu Onnu", "Waka Waka (Esto es \u00c1frica) (K-mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Ben", "I Can\u2019t Tell You Why", "We Will Rock You (with Beyonce & Pink)", "Lovers in Japan (acoustic version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["She Ain\u2019t You", "Burning Love", "Sad but True", "Smooth Criminal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Never Learn Not to Love", "SexyBack", "Our First Time", "Hollywood Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["We Can Work It Out", "Imagine", "Beat It", "If I Were a Carpenter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Chillin", "Pound the Alarm", "Crush", "Will You Be There"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Bad Girls", "Chaska", "America", "Dangerous"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Don't Stop 'Til You Get Enough (album version)", "Slow Wind", "Yara Seeli Seeli", "Sad but True"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["They Don't Care About Us", "No More Sorrow", "One More Night", "Celebration Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Abhi Mujh Main Kahin", "Naturally", "Yeh Dil Aur Unki Nigahon Ke Saaye", "Thriller"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Right Now (featuring David Guetta)", "Up", "Wanna Be Startin' Somethin'", "God's Gonna Cut You Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Dive", "Take Me There", "Smile", "Disarm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Black or White (album version)", "Dive", "Please Remember Me", "Mississippi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Human Nature", "California Dreaming", "SOS", "That Should Be Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Pehli Nazar Mein", "God Is a DJ", "I Just Can't Stop Loving You", "Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Goodbye Time", "Give in to Me", "Remember High School", "Best for Last"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jason Aldean?", "answers": ["1999 (LP version)", "Drivin' Around Song", "Maine Payal Hai Chhankai", "Black Ice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Jason Aldean?", "answers": ["Asphalt Cowboy", "Our Song", "Life Is a Highway", "My Old Friend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Whataya Want From Me", "Longview", "I'll See You Again", "You Can Finally Meet My Mom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Ten Years Gone", "Take Me Home", "Written in the Stars", "Liquor Store Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Gummy Bear Instrumental", "God Bless America", "All by Myself (Spanish version)", "Swear It Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["When You're Looking Like That", "The Power of Good-Bye (album version)", "Unfaithful", "O Duniya Ke Rakhwale"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Mirrors", "Poppin'", "Safe", "Move On"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["You Raise Me Up", "Hey Girl", "I Need You Tonight", "Who Says You Can't Go Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Ain't That a Kick in the Head", "Keep You Much Longer", "Right by My Side", "Far Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["My Love (feat. T.I.)", "Peli Waar", "If I Let You Go", "From the Inside"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Don't Be Cruel", "Home", "The Last Time", "I Need You Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Achha Lagta Hai", "Still Getting It", "What About Now", "In My Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["If You Ain't Here to Party", "Hold Your Head Up", "Us Against The World", "The One That Got Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Allah Hoo", "Soledad", "Tell Me Baby", "There's a Place for Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Panjaban Theme", "I Will Always Love You", "I Lay My Love On You", "Daddy's Little Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["The Truth About Love", "Home", "I Have a Dream", "Brooklyn Go Hard"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["I Wanna Grow Old With You", "Hurts Like Heaven", "Live to Tell", "I'd Rather Go Blind"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["World of Your Own", "The Beautiful Ones", "The Beginning Is the End Is the Beginning", "The Way You Look Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Seasons in the Sun", "Butterfly", "Cleaning Out My Closet", "Show Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["My Love (radio edit)", "Unchained Melody", "Look At Me", "The Fame"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Lullaby", "I'm Your Angel", "More Than Words", "Didn't We Almost Have It All"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Total Eclipse of the Heart", "Yo\u00fc and I", "Our First Time", "Love After War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["(Ghost) Riders in the Sky", "Smile", "Angel", "Crazy for You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)", "The Song Remains the Same", "John", "Queen Of My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Unbreakable", "Runaway Baby", "Turn Your Lights Down Low", "Ever Ever After (record version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["La La Land", "The Reason", "Someday When I Stop Loving You", "Tum Dil Ki Dhadkan Mein"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["En Ti Dej\u00e9 Mi Amor", "Every Day", "The Zephyr Song", "The Real Slim Shady"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Miss You", "Bitches Love Me", "Right Thru Me", "Ashley"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Mandy (live at the O2)", "International Love", "Crazy Love", "Everything's Not Lost"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["I'll Just Hold On", "Lose Yourself", "You Shook Me All Night Long", "Fool Again (2000 remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["God Is a DJ", "Kal Ho Na Ho (Kal Ho Na Ho)", "Give Me Love (True Tiger Remix)", "Flying Without Wings"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Orange Blossom Special", "I Know You're Gonna Be There", "The Rose", "Stupid Hoe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["Fucking Die 2 (\u20ac\u20ac Cooper mix)", "All Summer long", "Happy New Year", "Uptown Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Westlife?", "answers": ["The Way I Am", "Hard to Say I'm Sorry", "I Love You", "Got 2 Be Down (feat. Faith Evans)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Take Me Home", "Hit the Lights", "Cabron", "Take It to the Head"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Kanday Utay", "Janam Janam Ka Sath Hai Tumhara Hamara (Bheegi Palken)", "Oh Love", "Can't Stop Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["I Want", "Colours", "Man in the Mirror", "Wherever I May Roam"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Ramble On", "Son of Man", "God Is a DJ", "Mann Ki Lagan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Speedin'", "Mayonaise", "Another Day In Paradise", "\"Rascacielo (\"\"Skyscraper\"\" Spanish Version)\""], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Good Girl", "I'm a Slave 4 U (Thunderpuss radio mix)", "In the Air Tonight", "The Scientist"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Don\u2019t Hold the Wall", "Sympathy for the Devil (original)", "Enfant de L'homme", "Faint"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Something Like That", "Every Day", "I Want to Break Free", "I Told You So"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Thank You for Loving Me", "Mississippi", "Strangers Like Me", "Le Ja Tu Mujhe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Kiss & Tell", "Who Wants to Live Forever", "Both Sides of the Story", "Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Fallin'", "Yaadan Teriyan", "The Edge of Glory", "Against All Odds (Take A Look At Me Now)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Locked Up", "Easy Lover (duet with Phill Collins)", "No Me Digas Que No", "Stuck"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Holiday", "Saajna (unplugged)", "Entre Deux Mondes", "Today Was a Fairytale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Adada Vaa", "I Wish It Would Rain Down", "Count on Me", "I Could Have Lied"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Stole My Heart", "Faith Won't Fall", "You'll Be in My Heart", "Single Ladies (Put a Ring on It)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Super Bass", "O Holy Night", "LoveStoned/I Think She Knows (interlude)", "A Groovy Kind Of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["One More Night", "Tere Husn Ki Kya", "The Power of Good-Bye (album version)", "Open Arms"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["The One", "Love Song", "Next Contestant", "You Can't Hurry Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Candle in the Wind", "Two Worlds (finale)", "My Oh My", "Mahiya Ve"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["I'm with You", "Telephone", "Drive By", "Something Happened on the Way to Heaven"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["New Divide", "Gal Sun Ja", "So Small", "Je Veux Savoir"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Santa Fe", "True Colours", "Big Pimpin'", "Chelsea Rodgers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Sussudio", "Castle", "Uska Hi Banana", "Because We Can"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Right Now (featuring David Guetta)", "Talking To The Moon (Acoustic)", "I Don't Care Anymore", "All Too Well"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Phil Collins?", "answers": ["Born This Way", "Do You Remember", "I Need a Doctor", "Bounce Billo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["First Time Ever I Saw Your Face", "I Promise You", "Drop the World", "Unfaithful"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Crush", "God's Gonna Cut You Down", "Cry Me a River", "Climax"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["We Can Work It Out", "I Know You Know (feat. Cymphonique)", "Falling Down", "Heavy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["My Dilemma", "When I Look to the Sky", "Amplifier", "Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down", "Never Let You Go", "Candle in the Wind 1997", "Yakeen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Violet Hill", "I'm with You", "Middle of Nowhere", "Chamak Challo Chel Chabeli"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Tera Mera Pyar Amar", "Spanish Eyes", "Tell Me Something I Don't Know", "Sex Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Pal Pal Teri Yaad", "That's More Like It", "Come", "Qott Ghusian Da"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Zindagi", "As a Blonde", "The Baby", "Show Me What You Got"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Hush Little Baby", "Off the Chain", "A Kind of Magic", "It Had to Be You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["A Year Without Rain", "On My Own", "Make It Rain", "I'm Your Funny Bear (Gelatine club mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["I Want Love", "Sex Therapy", "Needed Change", "Sick of You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Bandz a Maker Her Dance", "I Don't Miss You at All", "You Don't Know Jack", "Love Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Folsom Prison Blues (mono)", "Cabron", "I Like How It Feels", "Love You Like a Love Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Fight Fire With Fire", "Young", "Easy Lover (duet with Phill Collins)", "Ghost of You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Intuition (feat. Eric Bellinger)", "Over the Hills and Far Away", "Something Happened on the Way to Heaven", "Crash My Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Never Gone", "Secret", "I Got U", "Over Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Round & Round", "Touch My Body", "My Love", "\u2026and Justice for All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["The Best Damn Thing", "Miraksam", "Spotlight", "Aaja We Mahiya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["One Drop", "Outlaw", "Rabba Ve Mera Yaar Modh De", "Birthday"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Strangers Like Me", "Money Make Her Smile", "Little Honda", "We Own the Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Brooklyn Go Hard", "I Won't Apologize", "Strawberry Fields Forever", "Express Yourself"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Every Teardrop Is a Waterfall", "Naturally", "L O V E", "Leaving"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Distance and Time", "More", "Sloop John B", "Suck My Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Hit the Lights", "Gypsy", "Figure.09", "Man in the Mirror"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Somewhere in Brooklyn", "Sacrement", "For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "Kiss & Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Bug Hunt (Noisia remix)", "One in a Million", "Stop & Erase", "Last Night on Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Summer Love/Set the Mood (prelude)", "Ojos As\u00ed", "Knockin' on Heaven's Door", "The Way I Loved You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Dance for You", "From the Bottom of My Broken Heart", "Fucking Die 2 (\u20ac\u20ac Cooper mix)", "Never Learn Not to Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Countdown", "California Girls (stereo)", "Don't Cry for Me Argentina", "The General Lee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Barbara Ann", "Ronan", "Bodies", "In The Ghetto"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Locked Out of Heaven", "Speechless", "Surfin USA", "Renegade"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Little Saint Nick", "The A Team", "Blue Suede Shoes", "Listen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Schei\u00dfe (DJ White Shadow Mugler)", "The Beginning Is the End Is the Beginning", "Rani Tu Mein Raja", "Wendy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Blackened", "As Tears Go By", "Shut Down", "Lonely"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Blind", "Countdown", "Sloop John B", "Glitter in the Air"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Never Say Goodbye", "In My Room", "Tere Bin", "Witchy Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["All Summer long", "Public Service Announcement (interlude)", "The Power of Love", "New Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Take Care", "For Whom the Bell Tolls", "Better as a Memory", "Be True to Your School"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["What Goes Around.../...Comes Around (interlude)", "The Winner Takes It All", "Surfer Girl", "Supergirl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Little Deuce Coupe", "Batdance", "Hakuna Matata", "DJ Got Us Fallin' in Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Start All Over", "Kiss Me", "Eleanor Rigby", "409"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Las de la Intuici\u00f3n", "Bounce Billo", "Kokomo", "Get Up Jawani (feat. Shah)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Don't Worry Baby", "Jab Jab Phool Khile: Pardesiyon Se Na Ankhiyan Milana", "(You Want To) Make a Memory", "Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Cherub Rock", "Hawaii", "My Life", "Do Pal Ka (Veer Zara)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["International Love", "The Show Must Go On", "Pet Sounds", "Saanson Ne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Stupid Hoe", "Wouldn't It Be Nice", "Welcome to the Farm", "Michelle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["California Dreaming", "As Long As You Love Me", "Girls Got Rhythm", "We Weren't Born to Follow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Lonely", "Let It Be", "Good Vibrations", "Angry All the Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Can U Help Me", "Forever", "Straight Through My Heart", "Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Yeh Raaten Yeh Mausam", "I Get Around", "Ten Times Crazier", "Who You'd Be Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Tunnel Vision", "Trapped in the Closet Chapter 1", "Little Honda", "Something in Your Mouth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Lady Lynda", "Turning Tables", "Gimme Shelter", "Sweetest Goodbye"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["That Girl", "God Only Knows (live)", "Ol' Red", "Always"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Nothing Even Matters", "I'll Never Break Your Heart", "100$ Bill", "That's Why God Made the Radio"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["I Can Hear Music", "Rusty Cage", "Granddaddy's Gun", "I Didn't Know My Own Strength"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Do it Again", "Run the World (Girls)", "Savin' Me", "Someday (I Will Understand)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by The Beach Boys?", "answers": ["Surfin' Safari", "Orange Blossom Special", "Rabiosa", "Zindagi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["His Mistakes", "You Should Be Dancing", "Waka Waka (Esto es \u00c1frica) (K-mix)", "Strange Clouds"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Electric Feel", "Tragedy", "For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "You Don't Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Dil aisa kisi ne mera toda", "Superstar", "Don't Forget To Remember", "Just a Feeling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["The Age of Worry", "Dirty Dancer", "Nights on Broadway", "Dreaming With a Broken Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Khalbali", "The Ocean", "One", "Stay"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["You Win Again", "St. Anger", "Lollipop", "Who Are You When I'm Not Looking"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Superwoman", "Massachusetts", "Thinking About You", "Bring On the Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Everything Has Changed (feat. Ed Sheeran)", "For Whom the Bell Tolls", "You And I", "Lost"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["No Leaf Clover", "Spicks and Specks", "Taarif Karun Kya Uski (From Kashmir Ki Kali)", "WEEKENDS!!!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["I Just Can't Wait to Be King", "S.O.S.", "No Idea", "Stayin' Alive"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Don't Cry for Me Argentina", "Allah Kare", "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap", "Words"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Everything's Not Lost", "Moment 4 Life (feat. Drake)", "Love So Right", "Miss You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Beam Me Up", "Beautiful", "Where Do Broken Hearts Go", "Love You Inside Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Islands in the Stream", "Les Mis\u00e9rables: Stars", "All Back", "Ronan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Syndicate (Skrillex remix)", "New York Mining Disaster 1941", "Little Lady", "Make You Feel My Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["My Dilemma", "Come", "Somebody's Me", "I Started a Joke"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["You Are Not Alone", "Bichdann", "Melody Fair", "Apologize"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Stand Up", "Closer Than Close", "Guitar", "Vipassana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Computer Blue", "You Really Got Me", "Medley (How Deep Is Your Love / Jive Talkin' / Stayin' Alive)", "Mohabbat Kabhi Mai Ne (Yaad)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["A Thousand Suns: The Full Experience", "Worldwide", "How Can You Mend A Broken Heart", "Stupid Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Aaj Mausam Bada Beimann Hai (Today the Weather Plays Tricks on Me)", "Space Bound", "Too Much Heaven", "Tailgate Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["First of May", "I Look to You", "Million Dolla Baby", "She's on Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["The Other Side (Feat. Cee Lo Green And B.o.B)", "Wish You Were Here", "Poppin'", "Out of My Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["\"How Deep Is Your Love (from \"\"Saturday Night Fever\"\")\"", "Don\u2019t Hold the Wall", "I Wanna Go", "Inconsolable"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["More Than a Woman", "Numb", "Inhale Deep", "Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["The Truth About Love", "Angel", "Jive Talkin'", "You and Tequila"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Diva", "Lying From You", "Flash's Theme", "To Love Somebody"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["As Tears Go By", "A Year Without Rain", "You Know It's Christmas", "Run To Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Dil To Bachcha Hai", "Saving All My Love For You", "I'm Still Standing", "Night Fever"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Alone", "Patteya Geya", "Whenever You Remember", "Wanna Love You Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Immortality", "Mar Jani Jhanjar", "Mermaid", "One of Those Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Bee Gees?", "answers": ["Emotion", "Saawali Si Raat", "I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)", "Tony Montana"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Bless the Broken Road", "Ooh La La", "Fly Me to the Moon", "First of the Year"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Beam Me Up", "Family Portrait", "La Tortura (alternate Spanglish version)", "O Bekhabar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Life in the Fast Lane", "Somewhere I Belong", "I'm Not a Girl Not Yet a Woman", "Teri Meri"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Naam Hai Tera", "Muskura", "Wanna Be Startin' Somethin'", "Don't Say Alvida"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Apologize", "1999 (LP version)", "Through the Never", "Yeh Kya Hua"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Miss Me", "Ye Ishq Hai", "Oh Africa", "Naturally"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Longview", "Ajnabi Hawaayein Bekrara Bahein", "Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "Brahms' Lullaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Chamak Challo Chel Chabeli", "Patteya Geya", "Pal Pal Teri Yaad", "Jaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Picture to Burn", "Mahi Ve", "Pyar Ke Baatein", "The Best Damn Thing"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Can't Be Tamed", "Trying Not to Love You", "Believe in Me", "Kyun"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Chandaniya (Lori Lori)", "Over Again", "Love Takes Time", "One of Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Wave", "Tera Ishq Bada Teekha", "Jam", "Easy Skanking"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Feels Good at First", "Can't Stop", "Tere Liye", "High Hopes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Breakfast Can Wait", "Not Afraid", "Saans", "To Love Somebody"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Shoot to Thrill", "Dolna", "Shut Down", "Fool Again (2000 remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Cowboy Boots", "To Love Somebody", "Jaadu Hai Nasha Hai (female)", "Something in Your Mouth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Inevitable", "Fireman", "Kaise Mujhe", "Haven't Met You Yet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Castle of Glass", "O Saathi Re", "Paris", "Practice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Kaun Hoon Main", "Fantasy", "Tujh Mein Rab Dikhta Hai", "Heartbreak Warfare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Raabta (Kehte Hain Khuda Ne)", "Confessions (interlude)", "Javert's Suicide", "Esperanza"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Tere Bin", "Mar Jani Jhanjar", "Here Comes the Sun", "Waiting on a Friend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["The First Noel", "Baby I", "Wouldn't It Be Nice", "Saibo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Umbrella (feat. Jay-Z)", "Bang a Drum", "Achha Lagta Hai", "Show Me What You Got"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Dosed", "Magic", "Teri Ore", "Mentiroso"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Shreya Ghosal?", "answers": ["Radha", "I Will Always Love You", "When a Man Lies", "Do I"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Mother's Little Helper", "Gunwalk (Feat. Gudda Gudda)", "Tera Ishq Bada Teekha", "You Make Me Want To"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Lyin' Eyes", "Apologize", "Sacrement", "D\u2019yer Mak\u2019er"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Ankh Ladake", "Tera Ishq Bada Teekha", "World of Your Own", "You Don't Know Jack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Daddy's Little Girl", "Cold Coffee", "Sorority Girl", "Take It Easy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Venice Queen", "What It Takes to Win", "Country Man", "Zindagi Ye"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Too Damn Young", "Who Knew", "Faithfully", "Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Hard to Concentrate", "Tu", "East Jesus Nowhere", "Everytime I See You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Hard as a Rock", "Crash My Party", "My Same", "Try"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Do I", "Count On Me", "Saawali Si Raat", "I Have a Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["I Could Die For You", "True Colours", "Kiss Tomorrow Goodbye", "Suite from Miss Saigon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["What Country Is", "Starfish and Coffee", "Nazar Se Nazar Tum", "Meet Virginia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["I Know You Know (feat. Cymphonique)", "Drunk on You", "Stay (featuring Mikky Ekko)", "Mamma Mia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["All My Friends Say", "Billie Jean", "Sure Be Cool If You Did", "Don't Stop The Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Buzzkill", "A Thousand Years", "I Like It", "Thinking of You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["The Way You Make Me Feel", "Country Girl (Shake It for Me)", "Diary", "Wait Til You See My Smile"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Right Above It", "Young Forever", "Butterflyz", "We Rode in Trucks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Help", "Clocks", "Love You Inside Out", "Drinkin' Beer and Wastin' Bullets"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["I Know You're Gonna Be There", "Next Contestant", "Kuch Is Tarah", "Fantine's Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Painting Pictures", "Ride On", "By the Way", "In Love With the Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["If You Ain't Here to Party", "Better Than I Used to Be", "Bad Medicine", "Hey Jude"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Take My Drunk Ass Home", "Wave", "Be With You", "Satyam Shivam Sundaram"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Tailgate Blues", "I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)", "Sing Together", "By the Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Baby I\u2019m a Star", "Me and You", "Chanda Ki Doli Mai (Chanda Ki Doli)", "Someone Else Calling You Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Slow Down", "More", "Suntan City", "Emotions (Mariah Carey cover)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["After All", "Little Bit Later On", "Written in the Stars", "Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["The Edge of Glory", "Rain Is a Good Thing", "Ek Ajanabee Haseena Se", "Immortality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["First Love Song", "Boulevard of Broken Dreams", "Jingle Bells", "You'll Be in My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Purple Rain", "Hold My Hand", "Welcome to the Farm", "Give Me All Your Luvin' (Party Rock remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Concrete Jungle", "Here Is to Never Growing Up", "Stars Dance", "I Don't Want This Night To End"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Harvest Time", "Good Vibrations", "A Year Without Rain", "Bleed It Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Naughty Girl", "Who Are You When I'm Not Looking", "Muckalee Creek Water", "Jingle Bells"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Love Me Do", "Lady Lynda", "Garaari (feat. Meet Malkit)", "Ponmeri"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Thalaattu Ketka Nanum", "Thunderstruck", "Confessions (interlude)", "Pendu Jatt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Chup Kar Ke", "Fernando", "Te amo", "Try and Love Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Open Arms", "Punjabane", "Express Yourself", "Crash My Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["My Love (radio edit)", "Disturbia", "Chaska", "Crawling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Brown Rang", "Money Make Her Smile", "Quiz\u00e1s", "Finally Found You (Papercha$er's Remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Right Thru Me", "Faith Won't Fall", "Truck", "Lullaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["High Hills", "My Way", "Jag Jeondeyan de Mele", "Who Owns My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Aise Na Mujhe Tum Dekho", "Barbara Ann", "Popular Song", "Begani Naar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Husn Di Botel", "Princess of China", "Believe in Me", "Autumn Leaves"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Whole Lotta Love", "Soldiers", "Head Banger (feat. Escape)", "I've Got You Under My Skin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Bad", "Angreji Beat", "Tere Liye", "I Got U"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Bleed It Out", "The A Team", "Satan", "Don't Rain on My Parade"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Good in Goodbye", "Panjaban Theme", "Teach U A Lesson", "Hot 'n' Cold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Goliyan", "Falling Down", "Jackson", "How Will I Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Chamak Challo", "Until It Sleeps", "My Friends", "When I Close My Eyes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Viraaniya", "Get Up Jawani (feat. Shah)", "Sick of You", "Love So Right"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Party on My Mind", "Up All Night", "Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "Daddy's Little Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Starships", "Mere Sapnon Ki Rani", "Sun Rabba", "Streets of New York (City Life)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Heartache Tonight", "Change My Mind", "Our Song", "Aashke (feat. Money Aujla)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Know Your Enemy", "Zero", "Brain Stew", "Kikli Kalerdi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Fall", "Rani Tu Mein Raja", "Love of My Life", "Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Reptile\u2019s Theme", "Too Damn Young", "Part Of Me", "Mood Kharaab"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Let Me Love You", "We Made You", "Yaad", "I Look to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Sing for the Moment", "Beautiful", "Immigrant Song", "Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Stupid Girls", "Lonely", "I'm a Slave 4 U (Thunderpuss radio mix)", "Sunburn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Dil Kya Kare", "Patteya Geya", "A New Day Has Come", "Stars"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Sambhle (feat. Manak Ali)", "Big Night", "Rusty Cage", "Kal Ho Na Ho (Kal Ho Na Ho)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Stop & Erase", "Mouj Baharan", "The Catalyst", "The More I Drink"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["You Are Not Alone", "Chup Kar Ke - Remix", "Sunday Morning", "Colours"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Mera Dil Bhi Kitna Pagal Hai", "Everytime (album version)", "Moon River", "Two Worlds (finale)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Don't Worry Baby", "That's Life", "Fingerprints", "Kasam Khake Kaho"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Baazigar O Baazigar", "Honey Bee", "Thinking About You", "Broken-Hearted Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Teenage Dream (Glee Cast version)", "Faith Won't Fall", "Surfin' Safari", "Jaan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["I Want You (She's So Heavy)", "Ankhon Se", "Stop & Erase", "A Dedication"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Love So Right", "Dive", "Ek Ladki Ko Dekha", "Do You Know? (The Ping Pong Song)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Free Fallin'", "Never Say Goodbye", "Crash My Party", "Tere Chehre Pe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["The One", "Candle in the Wind 1997", "Aankhon Ki Gustakhiyan", "Unbroken"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Dreaming With a Broken Heart", "One", "Mohabbat Dil Ka Sakoon", "Give It Up to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Las de la Intuici\u00f3n", "Spaceship Coupe", "Tujhe Dekha To", "Don't Stop The Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Dulhan Hum Le Jayenge", "Breaking the Girl", "Dirty Dancer", "We Belong Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Tera Mera Pyar", "Take It All", "Hard Knock Life (Ghetto Anthem)", "Turn Your Lights Down Low"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["U.N.I.", "Teenage Dream", "Tees Maar Khan", "Mere naseeb mein ae dost"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Achilles Last Stand", "Surfin' Safari", "Too Bad (Diggla mix)", "Meri Zindagi Mein Ajnabee"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Tum Dil Ki Dhadkan Mein", "You're My Only Shorty", "Strawberry Bubblegum", "The Adventures of Rain Dance Maggie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Bangarang", "Jab Se Tumko Dekha Hai Sanam", "Girls Got Rhythm", "Austin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Dil Hai Tumhara", "I'll Just Hold On", "Lost One", "By Myself"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["I Wanna Grow Old With You", "Chura Ke Dil Mera", "My Way (live)", "Thalaattu Ketka Nanum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Natalie", "All Around The World (featuring Ludacris)", "Street Fightin' Man", "Chamak Challo Chel Chabeli"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Kumar Sanu?", "answers": ["Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain", "The Song Remains the Same", "Dil aisa kisi ne mera toda", "Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Super Bass", "Beast of Burden", "Fade to Black", "Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["The Way I Loved You", "Fireball", "Fearless", "Leaving"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Out of My Mind", "You're the Devil in Disguise", "Count on You (feat. Jordin Sparks)", "Sacrifice"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["New York Mining Disaster 1941", "Va Va Voom", "Deewana Hoke Hum (Jan)", "Mermaid"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Turn Me On", "Happy People", "That's All She Wrote", "Addicted to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Take Care", "Drivin' Around Song", "Starships", "You Don't Fool Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Last Friday Night (T.G.I.F.)", "Freestyle", "My Best Friend", "Tommy Chong"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Obsessed", "Desensitized", "Did It on\u2019em", "Take It All"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Speechless", "Roman\u2019s Revenge", "Breaking the Girl", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["I'm So Paid", "Love", "Marilyn Monroe", "We Don't Care"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele", "Without You", "Welcome Home (Sanitarium)", "Take It to the Head"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Dirt Off Your Shoulder", "Pal Pal Dil Ke Pas", "If You're Reading This", "Pound the Alarm"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Take It Easy", "Easy", "Halfway There", "Right Thru Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Get Up Jawani (feat. Shah)", "Seasons in the Sun", "Bottoms Up", "The Power of Good-Bye (album version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Make It Bun Dem (Electro Body trance remix by Sthilmann)", "Feeling That Way", "Kill the DJ", "Right by My Side"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["The Boys", "Buffalo Soldier", "I Believe in You and Me", "Hero (MetroMix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Heavy", "Beez in the Trap", "Ni Nachleh (feat. Spyder)", "Pop That"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["4 Minutes", "Who Says", "Monster", "Diva"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Knockout", "Uptown Girl", "'Till I Collapse", "Love the Way You Lie (piano version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Paris", "Fly (feat. Rihanna)", "Sparks Fly", "Small Bump"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Time Is on My Side", "Check It Out", "SOS", "The Boys of Fall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Tell Me Something I Don't Know", "One Vision", "Where Them Girls At", "Do Somethin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Whip It", "God Gave Me You", "A Groovy Kind Of Love", "Something About the Way You Look Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Immigrant Song", "Save Me", "The Last Time", "Around The World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Sk8er Boi", "Mahiya Ve Soniya", "You the Boss (album version) (Explicit)", "Dazed and Confused"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Moment 4 Life (feat. Drake)", "No", "Where the Green Grass Grows", "21st Century Breakdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["I Hope You Find It", "Massive Attack", "Chasing Pavements", "Trust Issues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Magical", "Freedom", "Until the End of Time", "Schoolin' Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["The Rose", "Stupid Hoe", "Hard as a Rock", "Dirt Off Your Shoulder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Not Even the King", "Heartbreak Hotel", "Letting Go (Dutty Love)", "Ordinary Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["You Are My Sunshine", "Miss You", "As a Blonde", "Your Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["A Place for My Head", "High School (feat. Lil Wayne)", "Revolution", "Head Banger (feat. Escape)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Practice", "O Holy Night", "The Age of Worry", "Don't Let Me Be the Last to Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Jaane Ya Ali Ali Ali", "Made In the USA", "Vultures", "Lightweight"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Lost Without U", "No Idea", "Queen of California", "Troublemaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["We Belong Together", "Rumour Has It", "Hold It Against Me", "Clarity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Shadow Days", "The Prayer", "Garaari (feat. Meet Malkit)", "Teardrops on My Guitar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Edge of Desire", "To Live Is to Die", "Justify My Love", "Take Me With U"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Shake It Up", "In Repair", "The End", "World of Your Own"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Unbroken", "Feeling That Way / Anytime", "Holiday", "Dreaming With a Broken Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Tell Me Something I Don't Know", "Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)", "Perfectly Lonely", "Lean on Me (Glee Cast version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["I Don't Trust Myself (With Loving You)", "Look At Me", "Don\u2019t Let Me Down", "Mayonaise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Human Nature", "Je Veux Savoir", "Heartbreak Warfare", "Bullet With Butterfly Wings"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Waiting on the World to Change", "Hasta ma\u00f1ana", "You Belong With Me", "One"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Californication", "Who's Lovin' You", "Born and Raised", "When You're Looking Like That"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Bed of Roses", "Nothing Compares 2 U", "Hey Daddy (Daddy's Home)", "Belief"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Don't Blink", "Slow Dancing in a Burning Room", "I Wish It Would Rain Down", "Stutter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["One Thing", "Poetic Justice", "Still They Ride", "Half of My Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["I Won't Let Go", "Hero", "Bounce Billo", "Daughters"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Love You Inside Out", "Why Georgia", "Fever", "Fifteen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Let It Snow! Let It Snow! Let It Snow!", "Back To You", "Gypsy", "Tragedy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["No Such Thing", "I Feel for You", "Up All Night", "Yeah 3X"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["I Learned From You", "Freestyle", "Free Fallin'", "Wake Me Up When September Ends"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Ab Tumhare Hawale Watan Sathiyon", "Hard to Say I'm Sorry", "Hold Your Head Up", "Gravity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Rabiosa", "Separate Ways", "Do You Know? (The Ping Pong Song)", "Your Body Is a Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Punjabane", "Sale el sol", "Stop This Train", "Can't Stop Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Love Will Remember", "Say", "Mera Jeevan Kora Kagaz", "Ye Ishq Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Neon", "Enter Sandman", "Ballad of a Teenage Queen", "Koi Humdum Na Raha"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Tangerine", "Who Says", "More", "Kiss Tomorrow Goodbye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Last of the American Girls", "Strawberry Bubblegum", "Fall", "Something Like Olivia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Sweetest Goodbye", "Itsy Bitsy Bikini", "Into the Groove", "In Your Atmosphere"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Tell Me Something I Don't Know", "The Lazy Song", "Girls Got Rhythm", "the Heart of Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by John Mayer?", "answers": ["5AM In Toronto", "Funky Monks", "St. Patrick's Day", "Send It On"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["What Goes Around.../...Comes Around (interlude)", "Maula", "Every Day", "You Had Me From Hello"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Beam Me Up", "Dosed", "Lyin' Eyes", "Bounce"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Moby Dick", "Shot Through the Heart", "Summer Love/Set the Mood (prelude)", "Chalte Chalte"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Shapath", "LoveStoned/I Think She Knows (interlude)", "Back to Your Heart", "High Hills"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Shadow Days", "Fireball", "That Girl", "The Saints Are Coming"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Pusher Love Girl", "When I Come Around (album version)", "Right In", "God Gave Me You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Let the Groove Get In", "Celebration Day", "For Whom the Bell Tolls", "Kiss Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["DJ Got Us Fallin' in Love", "La Tortura (alternate Spanglish version)", "Empire State of Mind", "Body Count"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Blue Ocean Floor", "Fight Fire With Fire", "Saans", "Jump"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Eye", "Government Hooker", "Hey Daddy (Daddy's Home)", "Rock Your Body"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Mama's Song", "Through the Rain", "Tunnel Vision", "You Had Me From Hello"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Dress On", "When Doves Cry", "Never Let Me Down Again", "Little Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Who Are You When I'm Not Looking", "Love Will Keep Us Alive", "Se\u00f1orita", "Stuck"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["You Are My Sunshine", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)", "She's My Kind of Rain", "Cry Me a River"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Where the Green Grass Grows", "Mirrors", "Imagine", "In These Arms"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["My Love (feat. T.I.)", "Gundello Godari", "You Don't Know", "Run to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Fine China", "Fantasy", "Suit & Tie", "Tu Jaane Na"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Le Ja Tu Mujhe", "Like I Love You", "Outlaw", "Bye Bye"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["I Want It All", "When I See This Bar", "Don\u2019t Hold the Wall", "Try Sleeping With a Broken Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Famous", "Marvin's Room", "Strawberry Bubblegum", "The Day Before You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Pretty Lil Heart (feat. Lil Wayne)", "Tony Montana", "Until the End of Time", "Girlfriend"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Over", "Birthday", "Run To Me", "(Another Song) All Over Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Escape", "Lovin' Touchin' Squeezin'", "Flat on the Floor", "I'm Lovin' It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["I'm Alive (Humberto Gatica mix)", "Sun Rabba", "SexyBack", "Over Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Take You Down", "Hole in My Head", "Without You", "Saajna (unplugged)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Lost Without U", "Don't Let Me Be the Last to Know", "Seek & Destroy", "(Oh No) What You Got"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Drive My Car", "True Colours", "4 Minutes", "Cherish"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Country Man", "Give Me All Your Luvin' (Party Rock remix)", "Bad Girls", "Losing My Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Stay", "Back That Azz Up", "Could I Have This Kiss Forever", "Sexy Ladies/Let Me Talk to You (prelude)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Monster", "Makes Me Wonder", "FutureSex/LoveSound", "Wait Til You See My Smile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Gummi From Bom Bom Bay", "Spaceship Coupe", "What About Now", "Beautiful"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Take It From Here", "You And I", "Too Bad (Diggla mix)", "Soul Survivor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "I Can't Make You Love Me", "Pairon Mein Bandhan Hai", "My Happy Ending"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["If I Never See Your Face Again", "Wild Horses (alternate)", "Make You Feel My Love", "If Everyone Cared"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Girls Got Rhythm", "Turning Tables", "Enchanted", "Batdance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Crazy for You", "Longview", "What I've Done", "Radha"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Rumour Has It", "Candle in the Wind 1997", "Stand Inside Your Love", "Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["California Girls (stereo)", "Cold Shoulder", "Magic", "Kal Ho Na Ho (Kal Ho Na Ho)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Best for Last", "It's Me Bitches (remix)", "I Don't Want This Night To End", "Waiting in Vain (remix 84)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Pop That", "No Worries", "If It Hadn't Been for Love", "Something in Your Mouth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["I Like It", "I Found a Boy", "Harder to Breathe", "Waiting for the End"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Someone Like You", "Firefly", "Country Man", "Love After War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Who Says You Can't Go Home", "Voulez-vous", "Inside Your Heaven", "I'll Be Waiting"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Escapar (Escape)", "One And Only", "Mississippi", "Street Fightin' Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["It's Me Bitches (remix)", "Tired", "Lucky Strike", "Mockingbird"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Papers", "Hiding My Heart", "Off the Chain", "Feels Like Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["She's Got It All", "Ours", "Chasing Pavements", "Bleed"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Bad Reputation", "I Got You", "Painting Pictures", "I Have a Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["She's Got It All", "Hammer to Fall", "Right as Rain", "Welcome to the Farm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Wada Na Tod", "Set Fire To The Rain", "Two Pieces", "Mannequin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["The Call", "Rolling In The Deep", "Eyes Open", "Achilles Last Stand"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Koi Humdum Na Raha", "L.A. Boyz (feat. Victoria Justice and Ariana Grande)", "First Love", "Un-Thinkable (I'm Ready)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Intro", "Hometown Glory", "Don't Be Cruel", "Strawberry Fields Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Woh Lamhe", "My Life", "Take It All", "Love Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Anywhere For You", "Fool That I Am", "Believe It or Not", "Hello"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Highway To Hell", "Immortality", "My Same", "Not Like the Movies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Ek Pagla Meri Gali Ka", "Every Teardrop Is a Waterfall", "Ruffneck (Full Flex) (Munchi Anonymous Revolution remix)", "Daydreamer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Tattooed Heart", "Now and Then", "Shine", "Someone Else Calling You Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["As Tears Go By", "He Won't Go", "Sweet Dreams", "Middle of Nowhere"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Nikita", "Stiff Upper Lip", "As a Blonde", "Skyfall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Melt My Heart to Stone", "Touch My Body", "Piya O Re Piya", "Mera Dil Bhi Kitna Pagal Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Fix a Heart", "Don't You Remember", "Stand Inside Your Love", "Alguien soy yo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Adele?", "answers": ["Lovesong", "B.E.A.T.", "God's Gonna Cut You Down", "Believe It or Not"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Ballad of a Teenage Queen", "Make You Feel My Love", "Kiss Kiss", "Dreamlover"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Down to Earth", "Feeling That Way", "I'm Every Woman", "Honey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Without You", "Haal Kya Hai Dilon Ka", "Made In the USA", "Lucy in the Sky With Diamonds"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Fantasy", "Taarif Karun Kya Uski (From Kashmir Ki Kali)", "\u2026and Justice for All", "Stayin' Alive"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Sacrement", "God Bless Amerika", "We Belong Together", "Walking Contradiction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["I Miss You", "Vision of Love", "Yeh Zindagi Ke Mele", "Our First Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Any Kind of Guy", "Allah Hoo", "Through the Rain", "I'm Your Angel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Tumbling Dice", "Mehndi Laga Ke Rakhna", "Hero", "Renegade"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Wall to Wall", "My All", "Show Me What You Got", "(You Want To) Make a Memory"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Tum Dil Ki Dhadkan Mein", "Forever", "Better Than I Used to Be", "Breaking the Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Basket Case", "Rubberneckin'", "Like Money", "Heartbreaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["You Remind Me of Something", "Good Riddance (Time of Your Life)", "I Still Believe", "Call Me Maybe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Sweetest Goodbye", "After All These Years", "Run To Me", "Triumphant (The New Iberican League Radio)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["The Girl From Yesterday", "Obsessed", "L O V E", "Snow (Hey Oh)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Angels Cry", "Drunk on You", "My Way", "Slow Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Last of the American Girls", "You Are My Sunshine", "Not Like the Movies", "Always Be My Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Drive My Car", "Chelsea Rodgers", "All I Want for Christmas Is You", "When I Get You Alone"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Everybody Hurts", "Hollywood", "Young Forever", "Butterfly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["When You Believe (From the Prince of Egypt)", "Doing It Wrong", "You'll Never Know", "Everytime I See You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Open Arms", "Orion", "They Don't Care About Us", "I'm Not a Girl Not Yet a Woman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down", "Party in the U.S.A.", "One Sweet Day (feat. Boyz II Men)", "Painting Pictures"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Dance for You", "Main Hoon Na", "\"Almost Home (Music from the Motion Picture \"\"Oz the Great and Powerful\"\")\"", "Southern Voice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Ride On", "Die in Your Arms", "Touch My Body", "Tera Mera Pyar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["O Holy Night", "Right by My Side", "Remember December", "The Truth About Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["I Want to Break Free", "Christmas (Baby Please Come Home)", "Mohabbat Kabhi Mai Ne (Yaad)", "To Be Loved"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Secret", "Tere Chehre Pe", "I Want to Know What Love Is", "Mann Ka Radio"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["The World's Greatest", "Oh Africa", "I'm Your Baby Tonight", "Love Takes Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Antologia", "Never Gone", "Emotions", "Take a Chance on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Give It Away", "Gummi From Bom Bom Bay", "I Want", "Bye Bye"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["You're My Best Friend", "Wild Horses (alternate)", "All I've Ever Wanted", "Sacrifice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Santa Claus Is Comin' to Town", "No Idea", "I Just Had Sex", "Chhod De Sari Duniya"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Against All Odds (Take a Look at Me Now)", "Never Been Hurt", "Marilyn Monroe", "2012"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Me and Mrs. Jones", "Back in Black", "I Feel for You", "Sad but True"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Shot for Me", "Big Balls", "Satisfy My Soul", "Heart Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Leader of Men (acoustic)", "God's Gonna Cut You Down", "Fix You (edit)", "High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["T.N.T.", "Aap Ki Khatir", "True Colors", "Can U Believe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Medley (How Deep Is Your Love / Jive Talkin' / Stayin' Alive)", "Hard as a Rock", "I Surrender", "Touch Me (Gummib\u00e3*R)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Girls Got Rhythm", "The Saints Are Coming", "One", "Love the Way You Lie (piano version)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["War Machine", "Doin' Dirt", "Everything", "Wasted Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Pretty Maids All In A Row", "Dancing Queen", "Losing My Way", "Fire Your Guns"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Balle Balle", "HYFR (Hell Ya F*****g Right)", "Young Girls", "Have a Drink on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["For Those About To Rock (We Salute You)", "Hollywood Tonight", "Sweet Dreams", "Teeth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Madhuban Mein Radhika Nache", "Are You Ready", "Nothing Even Matters", "The Memory Remains"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Shoot to Thrill", "Blue", "Treasure", "Burnin\u2019 and Lootin\u2019"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["All Too Well", "Alejandro", "Mississippi", "Big Gun"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Stiff Upper Lip", "If It's Love", "Man in the Mirror", "Crew Love (featuring The Weeknd)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Let it Out", "Never Again", "You and Tequila", "Black Ice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["I Could Have Lied", "Born to Make You Happy", "Thunderstruck", "Got 2 Be Down (feat. Faith Evans)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Whole Lotta Rosie", "Keep Holding On", "Southern Voice", "As Long As You Love Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Whenever Wherever", "Apologize", "Ride On", "Love After War"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Anybody Seen My Baby", "Kyoto", "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap", "Gotham City"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Soul Rebel", "Hum Kis Galli Ja Rahe Hain", "You the Boss (album version) (Explicit)", "Who Made Who"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Step in the Name of Love", "You Shook Me All Night Long", "Feels Like Today", "Coca Cola Braunu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Rock 'n' Roll Train", "Ghosts", "Supergirl", "Favorite Girl (live) (acoustic)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Les Mis\u00e9rables: Stars", "The Show Must Go On", "Hells Bells", "Feel Like a Rock Star"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Anybody Seen My Baby", "Teach U A Lesson", "Rock and Roll Ain\u2019t Noise Pollution", "Ishq Ki Gali"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Jhoom Jhoom", "If You Want Blood (You've Got It)", "Countdown", "Starfish and Coffee"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Wild Horses (alternate)", "Love on Top", "Across the Universe", "Touch Too Much"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Change My Mind", "Islands in the Stream", "Ever Ever After (record version)", "Moneytalks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["I Wish It Would Rain Down", "Circle of Life", "\"Can You Feel the Love Tonight (from \"\"The Lion King\"\")\"", "Let There Be Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["A Boy Named Sue", "Edge of Desire", "It's a Long Way to the Top (If You Wanna Rock 'n' Roll)", "Listen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["The Jack", "Last First Kiss", "Gummi From Bom Bom Bay", "Bounce"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["I Love You", "Zindagi Ye", "Sparks Fly", "Jailbreak"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Highway To Hell", "Starfish and Coffee", "Dancing Queen", "Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Little Girl", "Kiss & Tell", "Both of Us", "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Leader of Men (acoustic)", "Given Up", "Take Me There", "Fly to Your Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Austin", "Slow Down", "Fingerprints", "Spicks and Specks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Lyin' Eyes", "Primordial Music", "Troublemaker", "Save the Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Wanted Dead or Alive", "Crush", "So Emotional", "Can U Help Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["I Got U", "Dosed", "This Is Me", "Aeroplane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["A New Day Has Come", "So Small", "Disappear", "Are You Ready"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Summer Wind (feat. Julio Iglesias)", "Party in the U.S.A.", "Separate Ways (Worlds Apart)", "Whoa Oh!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Like a Champion", "The Lazy Song", "You're My Best Friend", "Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Parler \u00e0 mon p\u00e8re", "Try", "Ab Mujhe Raat Din", "Stars Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Magical", "I'll Be Alright Without You", "Abhi Na Jaao Chhod Kar", "Pendu Jatt"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Hole in My Head", "Forget Forever", "Why Georgia", "Poetic Justice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Baby I\u2019m a Star", "B.E.A.T.", "Uska Hi Banana", "Zindagi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Butterfly", "Nobody Does It Like You", "Rock n\u2019 Roll (Will Take You to the Mountain)", "First Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Love Will Remember", "Scary Monsters and Nice Sprites (Zedd remix)", "Aap Ki Ankhon Mein", "Suntan City"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Write Your Name", "True Love", "Google Google", "Kisi Roz Milo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["The Last Night of the World", "Hurt", "I Like It That Way", "So What"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Come & Get It", "Red Ragtop", "Aeroplane", "Doom And Gloom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["I Won't Apologize", "As a Blonde", "Kill EVERYBODY", "Rolling In The Deep"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Revolution", "Santa Claus Is Comin' to Town", "When the Sun Goes Down", "Stop & Erase"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["I'll See You Again", "Falling Down", "Pon de Replay", "Oh Africa"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["The Scientist", "Life Is a Highway", "My Wish", "Cruella De Vil"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Everything Is Not As It Seems", "Tere Bin", "Punjabane", "I Wish"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Somewhere With You", "Nagada Nagada", "Jaadu Hai Nasha Hai (female)", "Send It On"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["I Promise You", "Be Intehaan", "Feels Good at First", "Fool in the Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["He Ain't the Leavin' Kind", "Shake It Up", "When It's Time", "Sick of You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Against All Odds (Take A Look At Me Now)", "Kabira (Encore)", "I Still Believe", "The Way I Loved You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Ave Maria", "Jaadu Hai Nasha Hai (female)", "Gold Rush", "Birthday"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Lyin' Eyes", "Otis", "Love Me", "Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Castle", "Bang a Drum", "Run to You", "Clocks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Tired of Being Sorry", "Lay All Your Love on Me", "Si Te Vas", "Tell Me Something I Don't Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["Batdance", "I Don't Miss You at All", "Toxic", "Drunk on You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["White Privilege", "Kasam Khake Kaho", "I Miss You", "I Kissed a Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Tujhe Dekha To", "Granddaddy's Gun", "Don\u2019t Hold the Wall", "B-Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Off That", "Wing$", "Forever", "Faith Won't Fall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["The Four Horsemen", "Pound the Alarm", "Castle", "Saawali Si Raat"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Otherside", "Stay Stay Stay", "Needed Change", "Chakna Chakna"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Get It Right", "Dosed", "Gold", "Unakkum Enakkum"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Naughty Girl", "Love After War", "Life Is Cinema", "I'm Alive (Humberto Gatica mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Gal Sun Ja", "Wish You Were Here", "I Could Have Lied", "Tommy Chong"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Smile", "To Be Loved", "My Oh My", "Mera Dil Bhi Kitna Pagal Hai"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Let There Be Rock", "Speed of Sound", "Trouble", "White Walls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Kyun Chor Gaye Rastay", "Irish Celebration", "Look Around", "Scream"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Witchcraft", "One Sweet Day (feat. Boyz II Men)", "The End", "Stand"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["These are the Days of Our Lives", "Bush Song", "Ahista Ahista", "Come Wake Me Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Like Money", "Never Gone", "She Don't Like the Lights", "Same Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Les Mis\u00e9rables: On My Own", "Vole", "Can't Hold Us", "Heart Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["A Wake", "Give in to Me", "Money Make Her Smile", "Ready"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["After All", "Wayfaring Stranger", "Tu", "I Said Hey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Cowboy Boots", "Hurt Somebody (feat. French Montana)", "Bad Romance", "Wake Up Call"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Granddaddy's Gun", "More", "Party in the U.S.A.", "Penis Song"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Something About the Way You Look Tonight", "Dazed and Confused", "O Sahiba O Sahiba", "Intro"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Hold Your Head Up", "Don\u2019t Stay", "Nobody Does It Like You", "I'm Still Breathing"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Exodus", "Dum", "Animals", "Ten Thousand Hours"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Did It Again", "Don't Rain on My Parade", "Vipassana", "Sk8er Boi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Written in the Stars", "Walking Contradiction", "Inhale Deep", "You Can't Hurry Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Aashiq Banaya Aapne", "Thrift Shop", "For Once in My Life (rehearsal)", "Gimme! Gimme! Gimme! (A Man After Midnight)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Why Georgia", "Escape", "Adore", "Stay at Home Dad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Cleaning Out My Closet", "Because You Loved Me", "Computer Blue", "The Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["If You Want Blood (You've Got It)", "Fake ID", "It's Time", "Landslide"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Soldiers", "Crash My Party", "Baby I\u2019m a Star", "The Adventures of Rain Dance Maggie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Sexy Ladies/Let Me Talk to You (prelude)", "Dancing Queen", "Man Dole Mera Tan Dole", "Remember High School"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Ego", "Tees Maar Khan", "Whole Lotta Rosie", "Fireman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Love Song", "Thinking of You", "Nothing Even Matters", "After All These Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["We Are the Champions (Digital Remastered)", "Supergirl", "Marry You (Glee Cast version)", "I'm Your Baby Tonight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Hoedown Throwdown", "Rollacoasta (feat. Estelle)", "Parler \u00e0 mon p\u00e8re", "We Will Rock You (Digital Remastered)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Flash", "Lag Ja Gale Se Phir", "He Won't Go", "Tell Me Baby"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Blue Moon", "Celebration", "Thalaattu Ketka Nanum", "One Vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Take Me Home", "Innuendo", "Muckalee Creek Water", "X.Y.U."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Deuces", "One", "Who Wants to Live Forever", "Cameras / Good Ones Go Interlude"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Princes of the Universe", "(Drop Dead) Beautiful", "The Last Time", "Kiss & Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Tere Chehre Pe", "The Show Must Go On", "Mera Jeevan Kora Kagaz", "You And I"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Fireman", "You Don't Fool Me", "The Storm Is Over Now", "Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Come Together", "Don't Stop Me Now", "Everything's Not Lost", "Bang a Drum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Hammer to Fall", "I Like It That Way", "Slipping Through My Fingers - Me and I", "Welcome to the Farm"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["I Was Born to Love You", "Locked Up", "Song for You", "No Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["2012", "Another One Bites The Dust", "Come Fly With Me", "Summer Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Dreamworld", "Circle of Life (The Lion King)", "I Want to Break Free", "Something Stupid"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Too Much Love Will Kill You", "If It Hadn't Been for Love", "Slow Wind", "Don't Rain on My Parade"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Stone Cold Crazy", "In Love With the Girl", "Always Be My Baby", "Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["The Beautiful Ones", "Love of My Life", "W.T.P.", "Fall (Live At the Bedford)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Rock and Roll", "Sun Zara", "Justify My Love", "Bohemian Rhapsody"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Lightweight", "Livin' on a Prayer", "Fix You (edit)", "Save Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Man Down", "Shakin' It 4 Daddy (feat. Nicki Minaj)", "Get It Right", "A Kind of Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["She will be loved", "Cama De Rosas", "Flash's Theme", "Stand Inside Your Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["I Want It All", "Knockin' on Heaven's Door", "Bad Romance", "Lay Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["All Too Well", "My Life", "Bicycle Race", "Black Dog"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["I Will Be", "D\u00eda de Enero", "Radio GaGa", "Fireball"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Somebody to Love", "Believe It or Not", "Ben", "Just to See You Smile"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Triumphant (The New Iberican League Radio)", "I Will Always Love You", "Can't Help Falling in Love", "Crazy Little Thing Called Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Sunburn", "Killer Queen", "S.O.S.", "Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Saanson Ne", "You're My Best Friend", "Thuy's Death / You Will Not Touch Him", "Life in the Fast Lane"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Yaar Da Makaan", "To Be Loved", "Fat Bottomed Girls", "Lemme See"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["These are the Days of Our Lives", "All the Man That I Need", "I Don't Miss You at All", "Dreaming With a Broken Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Needed Change", "Koi Hota Jisko Apna", "Heaven for Everyone", "Mann Ka Radio"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which of the songs was recorded by Queen?", "answers": ["Begani Naar", "Is This the World We Created...?", "Green Eyes", "Funny DJ"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}